Chapter 1: HP vs Childhood

Seventh Horcrux

Chapter 1: Harry Potter vs. Childhood

I am Lord Voldemort, and I was one step away from conquering Wizarding Britain.

October 31st, 1981 began as a fairly normal day – arranging raids, crucioing incompetents, lazing about on my throne – yet it seemed that everything my followers did irked me.

Bellatrix crouched at my feet, sneaking glances and occasionally emitting dreamy sighs – exactly the sort of behavior that caused me to turn myself into a nose-less snake. Rabastan Lestrange was playing a game called Curse the Recruits, the recruits were screaming, Nott was paging through one of my Dark tomes, and Lucius had disappeared to go brush his hair or something. There were worse ways to spend Halloween, I supposed.

"M-my Lord!" a nasally voice cried, its owner scurrying towards my throne. "I have information on the Potters."

I paused for a moment, contemplating the Death Eater's words. The Potters were Dumbledore's minions, the ones with the prophesied child. They'd defied me three times. I should know; I keep a list of these things.

"Speak quickly, then," I snapped, "I don't like to be kept waiting."

The short Death Eater cowered at my feet, and I noted that he was particularly talented at cowering.
"I'm s-s-sorry, my lord. I've gained their trust, as you ordered me to, and I can tell you that…" – he took a shuddering breath – "the Potters may be found at Godric's Hallow."

He rattled off the proper address, stumbling over every other word. The man was clearly incompetent, but he had been useful.

I said, "I am immensely pleased with this information…"

What was his name again? I narrowed my eyes at the still shivering man's unremarkable, brown hair. That was the trouble with giving all your followers masks. They all looked so similar. After a moment of silence, I murmured, "My faithful servant."

"Thank you, my l-lord," he simpered, bowing again and again. By the fifth time, I'd become peeved and, with an idle flick of my wand, slammed him into the stones.

"You are dismissed."

The bleeding man stumbled from the room.

Seizing the opportunity to escape my followers, I gracefully rose to my feet.

"I shall be busy for some time. Do not kill any of your fellow Death Eaters without my permission" – I sternly eyed Bellatrix – "We hardly need a repetition of last Valentine's Day."

Bellatrix bowed her head sullenly. "Yes, my lord."

After a moment, she perked up. This was almost certainly a bad thing. "May I help you dispose of the blood traitors, my lord?"

Her dark eyes widened and she batted them at me. Disgusting. Bellatrix looked almost like a little child begging for a puppy. Observing the manic grin twitching to life on her face, I resolved to never again use Bellatrix and the word puppy together in the same sentence

"No," I said a touch too quickly.

Clearing my throat, I clarified, "This is a simple mission for I, the Dark Lord Voldemort. Your addition would be unnecessary."

I turned away from my pouting follower. Bellatrix was a wonderful asset: loyal, powerful, and bloodthirsty. Yet her eagerness could be grating. I walked quickly down the gloomy hallway, swept through the heavy door, and – my ears popping as I exited the wards – apparated mid-stride.

I appeared in the middle of a quiet street in the village known as Godric's Hollow. I had been here once or twice before to observe Dumbledore's residence. Know thy enemy and all that.

It was still fairly early in the night and a few trick-or-treaters wandered between houses. They stole glances at me and my, to quote them, bloody brilliant costume.

None of them so much as glanced at one particular cottage, though smoke drifted from its chimney. Considering children and their gluttonous fixation on candy, I could only presume I'd found the correct address.

I didn't bother with the subtle approach. In a moment, the door was blasted off its hinges and the screaming had started. Again, I'd like to stress that this had, so far, been a perfectly normal day.

The father was quickly dispatched, and I merrily climbed the staircase, following the hysterical sobs of mother and child. I'd never considered myself a violent man, but there is a certain satisfaction in winning, even if my opponents are severely outmatched. So what if I liked to draw it out a bit?

The Potter woman flung her arms out in a pitiful shield. She looked feral, eyes wide, limbs shaking. "Not Harry! Please, no, not Harry. I'll do anything!" she cried.

I offered her a chance to live because, contrary to popular belief, I can be nice. I'm also quite the conversationalist when my companion isn't trying to lick my boots. Seriously, who does that? But I digress.

The Potter woman had finally used up my patience, and I killed her with an Avada Kedavra. I laughed, the sound nearly drowning out the baby's sobs. So this was the child of prophecy, was it? Pathetic.

"Avada Kedavra," I said. The baby watched the spell curiously. He screamed, I cackled, and the room turned green.

Suddenly, I experienced a sensation that felt suspiciously like dying horribly and lost consciousness. My memory of the next few years is rather confused.

That day – October 31st, 1981 – marked the end of my reign and of the First Wizarding War. It also began my second life. This time, I was going to do things a bit differently.

I am Harry Potter, former Dark Lord.

In retrospect, I have absolutely no idea how Horcruxes work.

I probably shouldn't have made one, let alone five, based on only three paragraphs of description which mainly centering on the mechanics of the ritual and not the effects. But I had limited access to the Restricted Section, at the time, and I was a very enthusiastic youth.

I had originally assumed that they would make my body invulnerable, but that was clearly not the case.

Perhaps they bound me to the world, allowing me to possess those weaker than myself. Obviously, the Potter child had succumbed to my greater force of will. I supposed that made as much sense as anything.

On that note, what about the prophecy? This would be easier if I knew it in its entirety. It was possible that I'd already fulfilled the blasted thing. My body was incinerated by my reflected spell. Did that count as being vanquished? I was Harry Potter, now, and I could hardly vanquish myself.

My questions would go unanswered for some time.

The Dursleys immediately sensed my evil. This was particularly impressive since I took several months to properly remember my time as a dark lord, yet they deemed me a monster upon arriving on their doorstep.

Amid the humiliation of diaper changes, tentative steps, and lisping words, I took great satisfaction in my caretakers' building horror. Even as a baby, I could still strike fear into the hearts of filthy muggles.

It started small as I relearned the art of wandless magic. Forget to feed little Harry and Dudley's bottle explodes. Insult him and your tongue starts to swell up. Go ahead, lock him in a cupboard. He will always find his way out, and you will somehow find your way in.

Even misfortunes that could not possibly be my fault, such as Vernon's demotion at work, were attributed to my malice. I, of course, never argued against anything that made me seem more powerful.

The Dursleys eventually decided that they feared my dark presence more than Dumbledore's threats. They dropped me off at the orphanage, the firehouse, and deep in the wilderness. They even called Child Protective Services on themselves. Repeatedly. Yet I was always back by morning.

I blame Dumbledore.

I was five years old when Petunia Dursley realized that she would never be rid of me. I know this because she began sobbing while insisting that she would never be rid of me.

Thick as they were, the Dursleys eventually realized that the only way to live unharmed was to accommodate my desires. It was the childhood I had always dreamed of.

During those early years, I had a lot of time to think.

From a few expeditions into the Wizarding World, I cobbled together the state of things. I had obviously vanished, and my followers had either been arrested or rejected me. Meanwhile, everyone believed that Harry Potter was an amazing and incredibly talented child (a not inaccurate belief).

I'll admit that I'd grown weary of being a Dark Lord. It was boring, the Death Eaters were annoying, and I had no particular interest in reigning over a nation of mindless sheep. There was a certain charm to fighting against Dumbledore – the wily fool – and murder is a good stress-reliever. But perhaps it was time to discard my previous life. This new identity could open doors that my previous self had foolishly closed long ago.

It was time to return to my first dream:

Teaching.

To be honest, I hadn't planned on the whole Dark Lord thing. It just sort of happened.

I'd always wanted to be a professor, either of Defense Against the Dark Arts or just of the Dark Arts. The latter wasn't exactly taught at Hogwarts, however, and Hogwarts was my first true home. My greatest desire was to return to it and live there. Forever.

With my original Horcruxes created and hidden away, I might have become as much a fixture of the school as poor, idiotic Binns. That dream was crushed by Dumbledore. His first official act as Headmaster was to deny me the position. After a very strenuous job interview, I might add. Offended and heartbroken, I cursed the DADA post and stormed out of the castle.

So there I was: depressed, unemployed, and increasingly intoxicated. I slumped across the Hog's Head's bar, accompanied by a few of my old Slytherin buddies. We were reminiscing, telling racist jokes, and complaining about all the Muggleborns stealing our jobs. At some point, we got onto the topic of the abysmal education provided by Hogwarts. Turning away a young, eager, intelligent – if slightly evil – job applicant showed a startling lack of foresight.

"Kids nowadays don't know anything," I slurred. "I bet the six of us could take out every one of the half-wits they're graduating and show them exactly how much they suck at defending against the Dark Arts. Then they'd have to hire me."

That's the last thing I remember of that night.

A few days later, I woke up in an alley with a pounding headache. By the time I'd gotten home and downed a hangover potion, The Prophet had arrived. In my drunken haze, I'd killed six Ministry workers and declared myself the Dark Lord Voldemort (I never would have picked that name had I been sober).

Once you've done something like that, it's exceedingly difficult to get a job around children. I know. I tried.

The next several years were spent struggling to legitimize my movement. I commissioned uniforms, made inquiries with Europe's darker creatures, cobbled together an ideological banner with which to rally new recruits...Recreating the Dark Mark alone took me nearly six months. Natural genius aside, I have no idea how I managed that while smashed.

My power base was entrenched in the Pureblood, Slytherin alumni as my drinking companions benefitted greatly from convincing their allies to join me. Not only were they tied to my will with dark magic, but they were also desperate to cover up the details of our drunken escapade. An embarrassment like that would be a crippling blow to their rapidly declining oligarchy.

In retrospect, the situation could have been worse. I might have joined forces with dozens of pompous fools and admitted cowards, but at least I was their leader and therefore best.

I stroked the parchment of my Hogwarts letter with fondness.

The youngest Dursley nearly wet himself at the deranged smile on my face. That was an expression usually reserved for our little "chats" (These usually involved quite a bit more screaming than chatting. Still, I always healed him at the end, so it's not like he has anything to complain about).

My "loving" relatives were more than happy to ship me off to Hogwarts where I would be far, far away from them. The desire was mutual. Even with training, the three were barely tolerable.

If I'd known the scar would be this much trouble, I would have worn a hat. I slammed the door shut on a particularly persistent fan. Sure, I liked groveling as much as the next dark lord, but for a stranger to actually try and kiss my robes? Honestly! Whatever happened to keeping a respectful, reverent distance?

Wandlessly locking the door of the shabby, silent shop, I took a moment to catch my breath.

"Good afternoon," a voice murmured. I practically jumped out of my skin. How in Merlin's name had he snuck up on me?

"Mr. Ollivander," I said to the pale eyed, elderly man. Nearly fifty years had passed since I'd last seen him, yet he hadn't aged a day. Clearly I wasn't the only immortal wizard in Britain. I quashed the urge to ask him how he'd done it.

"Yes, yes. I thought I'd be seeing you soon. Harry Potter." He spoke my name with a strange emphasis.

While I pondered the wandmaker's dark secrets, the man chattered inanely about nothing in particular. His mask of absentminded insanity was admirable. He handed me one wand and another and another still. Before I could even give them a wave, he snatched them from my hand. He proceeded to do this with every wand in the bloody shop. If I hadn't been certain he'd taken precautions against such paltry attacks, I might have stabbed him with one of his wares. I was Lord Voldemort, for Merlin's sake! I could easily force the cooperation of even an unsuitable wand.

An unsettling glint appeared in Ollivander's silvery eyes. Mumbling to himself, he dug out a holly wand. It hummed beneath my fingertips, warm to the touch. Unconsciously, I smiled at the familiar sensation and swung the wand around in a rain of colorful sparks.

Wrapping it up, he muttered. "Curious…curious…"

I was beginning to suspect something was curious. I inquired, with careful politeness, "Curious?"

"Curious," he agreed. He rambled on about my wand for some time before finally coming to a point. "It is very curious indeed that you should be destined for this wand when its brother – why, its brother gave you that scar."

"What a coincidence," I squeaked.

He stared at me intently, and I could feel my stomach drop. He knew. I could see it in his watchful eyes, the taunting tilt of his head. Ollivander knew exactly who I was or, more precisely, who I wasn't. My gaze darted to the wrapped wand in his hand. If I was fast, I could probably grab it, kill him, and run in a minute, maybe less. I'd have preferred to avoid murder for a few more years, but desperate times call for desperate measures.

Seemingly unaware of my frantic thoughts, Ollivander continued, "I think we must expect great things from you, Mr. Potter…After all, He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named did great things – terrible, yes, but great."

…Was he supporting me? That sounded suspiciously like a compliment. I said, "Thank you, sir, for the help."

"Anytime, Harry Potter," the man rasped.

Stepping into the train station as the Dursleys' car squealed away, I had never been happier. I was returning to Hogwarts, and it had been far too long since I'd been home.

A/N: I've posted this previously on Space Battles (under the same username, in fact). I've moved this edited version over here since it's a more permanent and easily-found location. Though I appreciate people who seek to defend my literary honor, please, my dearest darlings, do not accuse me of plagiarizing my own work.

For first time readers: I wholly believe that this story improves with time. Scenes (and years) get longer, characters better settle into their skins, and plotlines diverge more from canon.

It's been a great delight writing this and a far greater one sharing it with you all. Enjoy.

Chapter 3: HP vs Gilderoy Lockhart

Seventh Horcrux

Ch. 3: Harry Potter vs. Gilderoy Lockhart

I woke up to two bulbous eyes staring at me from the foot of my bed. Grabbing my wand, I growled, "Trying to kill me, eh?"

The house-elf gaped. "Dobby is not trying to kill the Great Harry Potter; Dobby is only trying to save him. Dobby…"

Dobby. I knew that name from somewhere. I hummed, my wand still pointed at the house-elf. "You're Lucius's elf, the one who used to serve those fantastic cakes!"

"The Great Harry Potter knows about Dobby?" the pitiful creature said, eyes filling with tears.

It wasn't that impressive, really. House-elves were simply less prone to failure than their owners and therefore died significantly less often.

"So, which Malfoy sent you then? The older or the younger?"

"No one sent Dobby. Dobby went on his own. Dobby wanted to warn the Great Harry Potter – "

"House-elves don't just go places. Really, though, which one is trying to kill me? I'd have guessed Lucius, but Draco might be making another go at it."

"They is talking about terrible things at Hogwarts –"

"Both of them, then?" – I paused thoughtfully – "Yes, of course, Malfoys always travel in packs."

"Dobby –"

"Yes, thank you for this valuable information. If you'll excuse me, I need to plan."

Pulling at his ears, Dobby popped away. That was one of the most helpful assassination attempts I've ever experienced.

"Tut, tut – hardly any of you remembered that my favorite color is lilac."

Lockhart sighed gustily, golden curls flopping with a dramatic shake of his head. His exasperation lasted only a moment, however, and he was soon back to grinning like a loon.

The Weasley rolled his eyes, grumbling about frauds. Of course, the boy was far too dense to realize that it wasn't his accomplishments that Lockhart was faking – it was his personality. After all, it is common for truly powerful wizards to hide their cunning behind a mask of harmless incompetence. Just look at Dumbledore.

I, too, had once doubted Lockhart's claims, for even I would hesitate to take on an entire island of vampires, no matter how many stakes I was using as hair curlers. Nevertheless, a small amount of research revealed that Lockhart was quite reputable.

Besides, Dumbledore would hardly hire someone as idiotic as Lockhart pretended to be. No, he was clearly more than he appeared.

Lockhart went on to prove his worth as a professor by releasing a batch of Cornish Pixies and hiding under a desk. By withholding support, he forced students to think on their feet and problem solve without relying on an authority figure to do everything for them.

This was true Defense Against the Dark Arts.

For the first time in decades, I feared that Dumbledore had hired a professor talented enough to break my curse. Gilderoy Lockhart would have to die.

I approached Hermione, Ron trailing at my heels. She was cheerfully chatting with Nearly Headless Nick, the ghost of Gryffindor House. I found it telling that the ghost of Gryffindor had been violently murdered while the ghost of Slytherin was a violent murderer.

"You shouldn't let them upset you," she said, "People are just awful when they're in groups. They like to exclude people, you know, especially on technicalities. It makes them feel important, and it's well-known psychological phenomenon…"

"I suppose," Nick said morosely.

Hermione reached out a hand to pat him on the shoulder, realized what she was doing, and yanked her hand back. She sniffed. "I'm quite certain the Headless Hunt isn't nearly as fun as you'd think, anyway."

"Hermione, are you talking to ghosts?" I asked. "It's useless, you know. They're like paintings – not really sentient – so there's no point bothering with them."

"But you spent three hours arguing with a painting just last week," Ron very rudely interrupted.

I glared at him. "Yes, and, if it was capable of changing its mind, it would have that realized I was right. We learned a valuable lesson about the idiocy of paintings, and I think we've all grown since then."

Hermione giggled, sharing a traitorous grin with Ron. "Yes, well, I was just speaking with Sir Nicholas about ghosts and their very rich culture."

"I can hear another Hermione rant coming on," Ron groaned.

She ignored him, going on excitedly. "He's invited us to his two hundredth Death Day Party!"

"So we can go to a ghost party with rotted food but we can't go to the Halloween Feast?" Ron whined.

"Oh, hush, Ronald. You could have gone by yourself. Besides, Sir Nicholas' Death Day Party was a wonderful learning experience," Hermione chided.

He snorted. "Yeah, I learned that I never want to go again."

"…rip…tear…kill…"

I stopped in surprise. The Basilisk? If she was slithering around, it meant that someone else had been meddling in my Chamber of Secrets.

"…time to kill…"

"NO!" I hissed, "Bad snake! No killing."

Hermione glanced back. "Are you okay, Harry?"

"Oh, yes, I'm perfectly alright. Just, erm, clearing my throat. Probably shouldn't have tried the food at Nick's party…"

Shortly afterward, we stumbled upon a petrified cat and a bloody message telling everyone that the Chamber of Secrets had been opened.

This was exactly like what I did in my sixth year, down to the curl of my S's. This new "heir" was only a pale and pathetic imitation of my former glory.

Filch accused me of being the Heir of Slytherin (technically true), Dumbledore got me out of trouble through the power of favoritism, and Hermione began a new research project.

That night, I snuck into the girls' loo and changed the password needed to enter the Chamber of Secrets.

I leaned up against the cauldron, glancing about the abandoned loo. Myrtle had long since disappeared down the toilet in tears. Her death was accidental, just a case of poor timing. I might have felt bad about it if she'd had the dignity to just die.

"So, Hermione, you want to explain what we're doing here?"

She grinned, giving the potion a final stir and going into teacher mode. "This is Polyjuice Potion, or it will be in a month. It'll let us sneak into the Slytherin Common Room and ask Malfoy if he's the Heir of Slytherin."

I frowned. "Hermione, of course he's the Heir of Slytherin. Everyone's the Heir of Slytherin."

She wilted, confusion wrinkling her brow. "Come again?"

"Look, Slytherin lived a thousand years ago, right?"

"Nine-hundred and ninety-four."

"Right. A long time. I'm not sure if you've noticed, but the wizarding population is kind of tiny. Everyone is related to everyone, so everyone's related to Slytherin. In fact, the only people in the school who are not the Heirs of Slytherin are you and the other Muggleborns. Also, possibly Ron."

"Yeah!" the redhead yelled, sparking a wail from Myrtle's toilet.

"…Salazar had standards."

The grin melted off his Weasley face. He said, "But it's still probably Malfoy, isn't it? I mean, him and the other Slytherins are the only ones who believe in all that blood purity stuff."

I snorted. "If Malfoy were the Heir of Slytherin, he'd be bragging about it. All the time. He would be right here, in our faces, bragging."

"We're in the girls' loo," Hermione said.

"Like that would stop him. He would follow us into the girls' loo just to brag about it. I mean, honestly, this is Malfoy we're talking about here. There are two things he mentions in every conversation: his father and his money. If he were the Heir of Slytherin, there would be three things he'd mention in every conversation."

Hermione pouted. "So, that means we don't need to brew an illegal potion with stolen ingredients, knock out three of our classmates, tie them up in a closet, sneak into the Slytherin Common Room, and interrogate Malfoy?"

I gaped at her. "Was that your plan?"

I fear that Hermione may be the most evil of us all. That is concerning since I am a retired Dark Lord.

I stormed to the girls' loo, cloak snapping menacingly behind me. There had been another attack. This one targeted a student who aspired to be my minion, one day. Though I had no particular fondness for Creevey, I also didn't have enough minions to start losing them to my own giant monsters.

What was worse, however, was the imposter's apparent ability to guess my password. I suppose "Slytherin's Locket" wasn't the most unique password, so I changed it into something less obvious.

Malfoy's summoned snake launched itself onto one of the students. Oh, sure, I could have stopped it, but I didn't really care. Besides, our medicine is pretty good; he would probably be fine.

The real question is why no one else did anything. There were plenty of people around – Severus, Lockhart, the other students – and, as far as they were concerned, I was just a stupid second year who most certainly couldn't speak to snakes.

Taking advantage of my opponent's distraction, I disarmed him and hopped off the stage. I do so love winning.

"Hey, Hermione," I asked, "Who's the kid with the snake on his face?"

"Justin Finch-Flechley," she murmured. My minions flinched at the boy's screams.

"Everything burns!" my…erm, Malfoy's victim cried.

"Who?"

"He's a Hufflepuff."

"Oh, that's alright then."

I had finally finished reading all of Lockhart's books and had determined that I was doomed. He was talented in hand-to-hand combat, as evidenced by his battle against seven werewolves while wandless. He had mastered battle magic as well, tearing through smaller dark lords with ease and routinely using spells I'd never even heard of.

Worse still were the skills that he had neglected to name. For instance, several of his fights had occurred simultaneously, while on opposite sides of the planet. Many would assume that this was a printing error or proof that Lockhart was lying, but I was not so naïve. To someone with my knowledge of dark magic, it was obvious that Lockhart was a master of the Multis Me cloning spell, which was outlawed three centuries ago for inducing madness in its caster.

He even hinted at this in the title of his newest book Magical Me.

I also worried that he would see through my Harry Potter persona. An actor of his caliber would no doubt recognize such actions in another.

Lockhart constantly assigned me detention in order to better observe my actions. Even outside of class, he paid me particular attention, sending knowing smiles in my direction and giving me tips on how to be more famous. My few attempts to implement this advice ended disastrously, leading me to the conclusion that he was attempting to sabotage my reputation.

I would have to orchestrate his demise very carefully.

How in Merlin's name did the imposter guess the password was Horcrux?!

"You've got to admit this is a load of bullocks," Ron said, waving his arms around at the chaotic scene in front of us.

Dwarves swarmed the Great Hall, chasing down errant students and occasionally tackling them to deliver often-humiliating Valentines messages. I crouched beneath the Gryffindor table, hiding under my invisibility cloak, while Ron and Hermione sat in front of me.

"It does seem a bit…silly," Hermione hesitantly admitted.

I said, "It's a training exercise."

"Not every stupid thing Lockhart does is a training exercise, mate," Ron foolishly declared.

"That's where you're wrong. This, for instance, tests our stealth, and I am clearly winning."

"That's because you're using the cloak to cheat," he said.

I raised my eyebrows, realized I was too invisible to silently display my condescension, and sighed. "Using an advantage that no one else shares to surpass your competition is not cheating. It's being intelligent. You would know that if you paid attention in Defense."

I hissed the new password, "Open. Open. Open. I am Lord Voldemort and you will open for me!"

How the imposter guessed that one, I couldn't even imagine. Perhaps he was an accomplished Legilimens. I trudged through the Chamber, towards the fool who had dared to attack my new Bellatrix. Hermione was currently lying stiff in the Hospital Wing, unable to serve me for months!

A hissed "Salazar" released the basilisk.

"Ssstay behind me, and close your eyesss."

"Yesss, Massster."

I waited in the Chamber. Eventually, my fellow Parselmouth would come, and I would be there to catch him when he did. I settled into a cross-legged position and waited. It was very dark in the Chamber and impossible to tell if the castle had awoken, yet.

"Tempus."

3:37 AM

There was a leak from the ceiling, splashing water directly onto my head. I moved. It followed. I sometimes hate this castle.

"Tempus."

7:50 AM

Slytherin's statue failed to respond to insults regarding his heritage, appearance, or ability. It did attack when I cast the Killing Curse at it, however, and proved fairly susceptible to blasting curses. I transfigured the mound of rubble into a chair, Slytherin's scowling face hovering above my own.

"Tempus."

1:15 PM

"I'm hungry," I said.

The basilisk hissed, "I haven't eaten in three hundred years."

"It's been at least eighteen hours for me," I commiserated. Sometimes, I think that no one understands my suffering as well as the basilisk.

Really, what was wrong with this new Heir? He should be here, by now. It had been at least half a day. I hadn't even changed the password! Still, I couldn't just up and leave. I was invested, by Merlin, and I wasn't going until the imposter was put in his place. My resolve was unwavering.

"Tempus."

1:55 PM

"I'm still hungry…Wait, I have a brilliant idea," I said. "All I need is a house-elf."

I smirked. "House-elf!"

Nothing happened for several minutes. I muttered, "Alright, maybe I need a name, something stupid like Flimsy or Floppsy."

I looked around: Still no food-bearing slave. What was the name of that assassin, again? Ah, right. "Dobby!"

The bedraggled creature popped in front of me, his eyes widening. "The Great Master Harry Potter sir is calling Dobby?"

"Feed me," I said.

He came back after a few moments, several plates floating around him. My eyes lit up. "Is that duck?"

"Master Lucy is wanting duck for dinner," he said.

I was impressed. "You stole from him?"

The house-elf shifted uncomfortably. "Dobby did not steal. Dobby just gave snack to very powerful guest."

I frowned. "But I'm not his guest, right now."

Dobby proceeded to slam his head against the ground. Shrugging, I dug into my meal, eating with all the table manners of a Weasley. Afterwards, I looked down at where a very dazed Dobby sprawled on the stone.

"Oh, right, and can you grab a peacock for my friend?" I gestured towards the basilisk.

After that particular bit of entertainment, I settled down to wait more comfortably.

"Tempus."

4:30 PM

Bored out of my mind, I drowsed under my invisibility cloak.

I awoke to hurried footsteps and squinted through the cloak's starry cloth as a small, robed figure walked inside. The red hair was unmistakable. Whipping the cloak off dramatically, I leapt to my feet.

"You!" I exclaimed. "I should have known. You Weasleys, always so righteous, always in Gryffindor, are the true heirs of Slytherin. You've lain in wait for generations, hiding your true cunning behind a veil of idiocy. But, now, I see you for the Pureblood fanatics you have always been."

The youngest Weasley gaped at my brilliant deductions. "…What?"

I took a moment to smugly survey my opponent. The girl looked shocked. One pale hand had dropped her wand in surprise and her other clutched something to her chest. A book? I frowned. It looked familiar, though it was far too thin to be anything I'd read recently.

"Oh, don't feign innocence, Weasley. It's obvious that you're all Slytherins. After all, every Weasley has been in Gryffindor for generations. Even the Gryffindor family didn't all go to Gryffindor! And your constant breeding is clearly a desperate attempt to produce Parseltongue from your impure blood."

The Weasley laughed. "You think Ginny Weasley could open the Chamber of Secrets?"

Her eyes trailed across me languidly. "So you're the great Harry Potter. I don't believe we've been introduced. My name is Tom Riddle."

Suddenly, I recognized the book.

"Diary?" I shouted. "What in Merlin's name are you doing here?"

She (he?) hissed, "How dare you address me so disrespectfully? I am Lord Voldemort!"

"You're going to regret that name in a few years," I said, "and I'm the real Lord Voldemort. You're just my horcrux."

Diary sneered. "You're Lord Voldemort? No, I think I'm Voldemort."

I narrowed my eyes. No diary was going to defy me. "Well, at least I'm not in the body of a girl. I certainly don't remember being confused about that when I was in school."

"I'm only using her body-"

I cut in, "Whoa, there. She's only twelve. I don't remember being confused about that, either."

His Weasley eyes flashed with fury. "You'll regret that," he hissed. With a smirk, he turned to the Basilisk.

"Attack."

"No, don't do that," I ordered in Parseltongue.

The Basilisk has no way of identifying the "one true heir of Slytherin." It's a snake, not some magical lineage device. As such, it follows any command given in Parseltongue.

Diary glared. "Attack him!"

"Don't do that," I ordered. "In fact, never attack me. And don't listen to any of his orders, either."

"That isn't fair," he grumbled.

I sighed, wishing my younger self was less of an idiot. "Diary, we are a dark lord."

Diary snatched up the Weasley girl's wand. "I don't need the Basilisk for this, anyway. I wonder…if we were to fight, who would win?"

I glared. "Me."

"Really? I don't think so."

"You stop this nonsense and get back in your diary, young man."

The Weasley girl smirked. "Of course, you could always join me. I might let you rule at my feet -"

"Avada Kedavra," I said, pointing my wand at the diary. The Weasley collapsed as the book glowed green and the soul inside screamed. The Horcrux was destroyed. Or released, or something like that.

It was a necessary evil. I had enough competition without another me running around.

I had assumed that, upon the destruction of my soul containers, I would notice. They're tying me to this world, after all, so I should feel something when they disappeared.

Yet I did not.

This meant that all of my Horcruxes could be destroyed and I would have no idea.

That is a problem.

I dumped the Weasley in the girl's loo. She'd wake up in a few hours, exhausted and suffering from amnesia. Obviously, she'd come up with some explanation and forget about it, in typical Weasley fashion.

I threw my invisibility cloak on as I hurried out of the loo and snuck back into Gryffindor tower. I'd never understand why the portrait would let students pass who were clearly out after curfew and invisible. The foolish portrait would probably let a Death Eater in, if one knew the password…Come to think of it, she was letting the Dark Lord in, now, so that would actually be a step down.

I crept into the Second Year boys' dormitory, slipped off the invisibility cloak, and threw open the Weasley's curtains.

"Spiders!" he cried, jolting forward. He relaxed upon realizing that I did not, in fact, possess eight eyes. "Oh, Harry. You're back."

"Yes, yes," I grumbled. "Did you avoid suspicion, as I ordered?"

Ron grinned. "Yeah, I told everyone you were sick."

"And no one questioned that?"

"Nah, McGonagall just said you should go to the Hospital Wing if it got bad. Dean, Seamus, and Neville thought it was weird they never saw you, but I just said you were sleeping under your invisibility cloak again…"

"That is something I would do," I muttered.

"…and no one wanted to wake you after last time," Ron said, shivering slightly.

"I don't know why you're still complaining about that. The scars weren't even permanent."

"Where were you, anyway?" Ron followed me to my trunk, where I tossed my cloak.

"The Chamber of Secrets. As usual, I solved everything."

I'd hoped that would be the end of it since Dumbledore and Hagrid were kicked out of the school on the same day I went hunting for the imposter. Hermione's petrification was the last of them, and they'd arrested the man who was previously blamed. Everything seemed perfectly resolved, to me.

I'd feel bad about using Hagrid as a scapegoat, but he did almost burn down the Forbidden Forest, the previous year.

Come to think of it, I didn't feel guilty about my previous actions, either.

Hagrid wasn't technically expelled for being the Heir of Slytherin. He was expelled for keeping a man-eating spider in the school. Which, to be fair, he did.

Unfortunately, the groundskeeper's obvious guilt was not enough to stop the incompetent fools at the Ministry from nearly ruining my magical education. Again.

My minion and I tracked down Professor McGonagall, the acting headmistress, in her office.

"You can't close the school!" I exclaimed, the Weasley echoing me.

McGonagall's lips thinned. "The Board of Governors has determined that Hogwarts is no longer safe for students."

"There hasn't been an attack in weeks. I'm sure we're fine," I said.

"Mr. Potter," she snapped. "There is a deadly monster in the school."

"It can't be that deadly if it didn't kill anyone," I argued.

"Petrifications are no laughing matter, and it's only prudent to close the school before the monster kills a student, as it did fifty years ago."

I snorted. "One death every fifty years? We lose more students than that to the moving staircase."

Ron gaped at me. "We do?"

"What do you think happened to the Perks girl?" I asked. It really was a wonder Ron hadn't accidentally strangled himself, which I'd like to add would set his death toll equal to my basilisk's.

McGonagall sighed. "Any death is too great a risk."

"But we caught the Heir, already," I whined.

She frowned. "It has only been three weeks, Mr. Potter. There is no proof that we've caught the Heir."

"But everyone knows that it's Hagrid's fault."

Honestly, if we weren't going to blame him, why arrest the oaf at all?

Professor McGonagall sighed heavily. "The school is closing, Mr. Potter. I'd suggest you get used to the idea. Now, please leave my office. I have work to do."

I stormed from the office, Ron at my heels like a good minion. "How dare they? As if they can close my school without my approval…Fine, they want a monster; I'll give them a monster."

"Um, Harry?"

"Quiet, Ron. I'm scheming," I said.

After a few moments, I worked out my plan. "We need to go into the Forbidden Forest and bring back an Acromantula."

Ron frowned. "A what?"

"A giant spider."

"What?! But why?"

"To stop the school from closing down, of course," I said.

"I thought you said you took care of everything." His Weasley mind struggled to keep up with my brilliance.

"No, no, I just took care of the Heir. You clearly weren't paying attention," I said breezily.

"But-"

I huffed in annoyance. "Let me put this simply: To keep the school open, we need to kill Slytherin's monster. The monster is in the forest. To kill it, we have to take it in the school."

There, that was a close enough approximation of the truth. Most importantly, it was the explanation that would convince my minion to assist me, or at least keep him too confused to argue.

Ron shrugged. "Okay."

"Alright, we're agreed then. We go into the forest tonight. How is your Stunning Spell?"

"I never learned the Stunning Spell," he said.

"Then you get to be bait," I said.

He was always going to be bait, but I figured he'd agree more easily if he thought it was his fault.

"Erm, mate, are you sure about this?" Ron asked, trudging through the Forbidden Forest.

I floated next to him on a school broomstick and sighed loudly to ensure it would be heard through my invisibility cloak. "Ron, when have I ever been wrong about anything?"

"What about –"

I quickly interrupted. "That was a rhetorical question."

"I still think this is a bad idea," he muttered. "Spiders are bloody terrifying."

"Didn't you pay attention to the Hat? Gryffindors aren't afraid of things. If you wanted to be afraid of things, you should have gone to Hufflepuff."

Ron nodded sullenly. No one wants to be a Hufflepuff.

We followed the spiders deep into the forest, and, at last, found one of the larger acromantulas. From black-furred leg to yellow eye, it was about the size of a horse, its fang as long as my arm. That should be intimidating enough.

I whispered, "Ron, that's it."

"I-it's so big," he stuttered.

"You have to get its attention," I said. "Wave your arms or something."

Ron stood completely still, utterly failing at fading into the greenery. Hufflepuff. I cleared my throat and yelled, "HEY, SPIDER! I, THE REDHEADED BOY TO YOUR LEFT, AM VERY DELICIOUS!"

Was that so hard? The acromantula turned, clicking, and scuttling towards Ron. He ran away, the spider hot on his trail and me flying beside them. Demonstrating admirable stamina, the Weasley made it all the way through the forest and well onto the grounds before panting, "Harry, where should I go?"

I smirked beneath my cloak. "The Defense classroom, of course. Lockhart will take care of it."

"I would like to take a moment to commemorate the loss of Professor Lockhart who died courageously fighting Slytherin's Acromantula," Dumbledore said.

I bowed my head along with the rest of the Great Hall. Lockhart was a brilliant man and a better teacher. It was a pity he chose to oppose me.

After no more than a second, Dumbledore clapped his hands and cheerfully remarked. "Now, let's move on to happier matters. It's time to award the House Cup!"

I listened raptly. Hufflepuff was in fourth place – naturally – with Gryffindor well above and Ravenclaw slightly ahead. Slytherin was set to be the winner.

Dumbledore sighed. "Yet I find myself once again needing to award points for special services performed for the school. To Mr. Ronald Weasley and Mr. Harry Potter, for locating Slytherin's monster and saving the school, I award one hundred points…each."

There were shocked gasps and mutinous mutters from Slytherin.

"This is ridiculous!" I cried. "You're not even trying to hide your favoritism."

"Now, Mr. Potter…" Dumbledore said.

"No! I refuse to accept this."

"Twenty points from Gryffindor for talking out of turn," Snape drawled.

I said, "Thank you! At least someone is trying to be fair here. Until this is righted, I declare a hunger strike."

With that, I strode from the Great Hall, doors slamming shut behind me with an echoing boom. Gilderoy Lockhart would have approved.

"Harry, I brought you some food," Hermione called, pushing into the boys' dormitory. "I think it's very noble what you're doing for the Slytherins, but you really shouldn't neglect your –"

She paused upon noticing the plate of turkey, tin of biscuits, tub of gravy, bowl of salad, various desserts, and assorted other food items hovering in the air around me. "…Oh, you're eating."

I said, "Of course I'm eating. I can't just starve myself every time Dumbledore does something immoral. I'd be starving myself all the time."

Hermione frowned. "But you said you were going on a hunger strike."

"Yes, I definitely said that." I took a bite of biscuit, taking care to swallow before speaking again. I'm not a Weasley.

Hermione sighed and said, "Where did you get all of this, anyway?"

"Ah, want some for yourself, eh?" – I grinned – "Never let it be said that I am not a generous ma-friend. Come Dobby!"

The house-elf popped beside me. "Master Harry Potter sir is wanting more?"

Hermione gaped at the hideous creature. "Are you okay?"

I chewed my mouthful of turkey thoughtfully before answering. "Well, it's a bit on the dry side, and I wouldn't mind a fork. But I suppose I'll survive."

"No, not you," she snapped, and turned to Dobby as her voice softened, "Hi, I'm Hermione. What's your name?"

"Dobby is Dobby," he said nervously, pulling at his ragged pillowcase.

"What exactly are you?" she whispered.

"Dobby is a house-elf."

She smiled widely, as if interacting with a small child. "And how did you get all this food? Did you make it yourself?"

"Dobby is good cook. Dobby took it from the kitchens for the amazing, very kind Harry –"

"He stole it from the Malfoys," I added helpfully.

Dobby's eye twitched violently, and he set about trying to bash his head in with the biscuit tin. I scowled. "Hey, I was using that!"

The house-elf helpfully switched to slamming himself against the floor.

Hermione said, "Please stop doing that!"

I said, "Hermione, there's really no use trying to talk him out of it. He'll probably just hurt himself more, later, for making you go to the trouble."

"But why?" Hermione sniffled.

I shrugged. "That's just how house-elves are."

Honestly, I think they may actually like that sort of thing, but there are some things you just don't tell a twelve-year-old girl. I do have some decency.

She bit her lip but dropped the subject. "There was something else I wanted to ask you, actually. I just didn't have time what with making up all the classes I'd missed."

"And getting O's in all of them, I'm sure," I said. There was a loud crack.

"Is he…?"

I said, "It was probably the floor. Dobby, fix the floor before you leave."

"Yes, Harry Potter sir," he squeaked.

She continued. "Um, alright then. Well, I was just wondering about Slytherin's monster. I was looking it up in the library before my petrification, and I was really quite certain it was a basilisk."

I laughed for a good, long while. When Hermione's ideas seemed sufficiently mocked, I said, "Hermione, that is completely ridiculous. Do you know how rare those are? Besides, it was definitely an acromantula. Everyone saw it."

"Well, I saw the creature's reflection in my mirror, and it only had two eyes."

"Are you sure? It was a pretty big spider, Hermione. You might have only seen two eyes, but there were six more above them."

She shook her head. "And I've read Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them twice now. Acromantulas don't petrify people. Basilisks do."

I reached forward to pat her on the shoulder. "It was an enchanted spider, obviously."

"I guess that makes sense," she said in a voice that implied that it really didn't make sense at all. "I still can't believe Hagrid wanted to kill Muggleborns, though."

I shook my head regretfully. "Honestly, I'm surprised it took so long to arrest him. He did the same thing fifty years ago. Fifty years of biding his time, pretending to be an idiot, only to finally strike…we should all hope to be as Slytherin as Hagrid."

"Why would we want to be Slytherin at all?" Hermione asked.

I smiled, hoping it wouldn't twitch too noticeably. "That's not important right now. Dobby, bring us cakes!"

"Yesh, 'arry Potta shr," the house-elf slurred, popping away.

My two months of exile in the Muggle world were not as terrible as they might have been.

The Dursleys continued to acknowledge my superiority and ability to injure them at any time, and my minions kept me well informed of news in Wizarding Britain. During my trips to proper civilization, I began tentatively researching Horcruxes and similar rituals. It turns out that making them solely based on the information obtained from one crumbling tome was probably a bad idea.

Most importantly, however, it allowed me time to work on my newest project:

Sporting with Spiders, the final installation in Lockhart's book series.

Sure, the brilliant adventurer wouldn't be writing it, and all the royalties would go directly to me. But I think that's how Lockhart would have wanted it.

Chapter 6: HP vs Alastor Moody (Pt 1)

Seventh Horcrux

Chapter 5: Harry Potter vs. Alastor Moody (Pt. 1)

I paced my room at the Dursleys, wand spinning between my fingers. Dumbledore had warned me to stay inside for fear of Sirius Black, and I had reluctantly abided by his request. But the Muggle world was exhausting, and – worse yet – incredibly boring.

The Weasley's old owl thudded against my window, scratching the glass weakly. I scrambled toward it in a horribly undignified manner and swung open the window, causing the owl to fall into my room. He was probably dead.

I shrugged and grabbed the message from his twitching claws.

Hi Harry,

Has Hermione been on you about doing homework? She's completely mental. We've got a whole month left!

Did you hear that the Cannons won their last game? It's the third time this season. The twins say it's a fluke, but I think they've really got a chance at the Cup.

I skimmed the rest of the letter. Apparently, Ron's rat was eaten by a grim or something. See, this is why I miss the wizarding world. When I leave, even Ron has adventures without me. I scowled, returning to the letter.

Mum's been asking when you're going to visit. If you want, you could probably come for the rest of the summer…

I didn't read the end of the letter. I was too busy packing.

"Harry!" That was my only warning as I stepped from Mr. Weasley's car and was viciously attacked. I stood still and waited for Hermione to stop hugging me.

"Hello, Hermione," I said. "Ron."

Ginevra also peeked at us from the doorway. But, since she was attempting to be discreet, I pretended not to see her.

"Hey, mate," Ron said.

His mother bustled over, beaming. I think she wanted to hug me as well, but I'd already gotten my wand out. She kept her hands clasped atop her chest. Smart of her – which made sense since she was only a Weasley by marriage. "Harry! Oh, it's so nice to finally meet you. I've been telling Ron to have you over for years."

"I didn't want to impose," I said.

She smiled sweetly. "No imposition at all."

A loud ding echoed across the yard. With a harried look, the Weasley matriarch said, "Now, lunch will be ready in a few minutes, so don't stay out here too long."

As she left, Ron turned to me. "You didn't want to impose?"

"Well, no, it seemed rude."

"Mate, that doesn't sound like you at all. When have you ever cared about being rude?"

I shrugged, tucking my wand back in my pocket since the danger of Weasley affection had passed. "I was under the impression you lived in a shoebox."

His Weasley mouth dropped open and stayed that way for some time. "What?!"

"That's what Malfoy said," I said peevishly.

"He was just being an insulting git like he always is," Hermione said.

I frowned and observed Ron with unshielded confusion. "But, if he was lying, why did you get so upset?"

Ron went on sputtering for a while, waving his hands around as if to illustrate some incomprehensible point. I turned my attention to a thoughtful Hermione, which could only lead to trouble. She stared at the place where Mr. Weasley's car was parked. "Why didn't you mention that your family were Muggles?"

"Oh, I prefer not to talk about them. They're really quite insufferable," I said.

"What do you mean?" Ron asked, finally recovered.

"They just are" – I shrugged – "You would understand if you met them."

Hermione said, "Harry, if you were raised by Muggles, then where do all of your biases come from?"

"I have legitimately no idea what you're talking about."

"You have no respect for Hufflepuffs, and sometimes you just completely disregard Muggles like they aren't even people" – Hermione cocked her head, giving me a suspicious look – "Your family is alright with you coming here, right? You didn't just decide they were unimportant and go off without telling anyone?"

I tried to cut in on her completely unwarranted paranoia. "Hermione –"

She rambled on. "Because that really seems like something you would do."

I huffed, insulted. "I told them. And I'll have you know they were very happy to see me go. There was hugging and everything."

She giggled. "Aw."

"I wasn't involved," I said, hoping she wouldn't get any ideas. "They also had a party."

"That sounds nice," Hermione said.

"I wouldn't know. It was after I left."

Hermione seemed quite stunned and failed to respond. Since the conversation was clearly over at that point, I wandered inside in search of lunch.

"Now she insists I've been 'emotionally neglected.' Whatever that means."

Ron nodded. "Yeah, 'Mione can be kind of weird about stuff like that.

"It's like the house-elves all over again," I grumbled, "except I'm the house-elf. And she's trying to kill me with her deformed mittens."

"What does that –"

"It's a metaphor, Ron. Don't strain yourself trying to make sense of it," I said.

I paced the floor of Ron's room, bursting with agitated energy. Usually, when I felt like this, I would relieve my tension by destroying something. But magic was not permitted over the summers, and I refused to break things with my hands like a Muggle.

"She'd probably forget about it if we got out of the house for a bit," Ron said.

I stopped pacing. That seemed reasonable, for a Weasley suggestion. As much as Hermione struggles to care about things that are traditionally immoral, a quick distraction usually causes her to lose interest.

Ron continued, "I bet even a couple of days would do it."

"I'm listening."

I woke up early the morning after the World Cup – no surprise since I'd spent most of the previous day sleeping. Ron had been rather upset at Hermione's and my disinterest in the game – insisting upon waking me up every ten minutes and snatching Hermione's book from her hands – but he forgot our "betrayal" easily enough after the Cup's climactic finish. At least, I presume it was climactic; I slept through it.

I left my invisibility cloak and other blankets crumpled on the couch as I wandered towards the tent's kitchen. The fridge was well stocked, but I'd never cared for cooking.

"Dobby," I snapped.

The house-elf arrived a few minutes later, looking nervous. "Yes Great Master Harry Potter sir?"

"You're late," I said.

"Dobby is sorry, so very sorry!" he cried, slamming his limbs violently against the floor in what might charitably be referred to as a bow. "Master Lucy came home very late, and he wanted me to fetch him pain potions. I did not want to be making him angry."

"Don't let him order you around so much," I ordered.

Dobby nodded, ears flapping and eyes shining rebelliously. This is why I don't keep house elves: The risk of betrayal is far too great. I continued, "Now, bring me whatever Lucius is having for breakfast."

Ginevra stumbled upon me half hour later, as I was polishing off some sort of giant egg set on a silver plate.

"Harry?" she gasped, then shouted, "He's right here!"

A stampede of Weasleys and a lone Hermione stumbled, bleary-eyed from their rooms. Hermione cried indignantly, "Where have you been?! We were worried sick."

I frowned, confused and quite displeased with the feeling. "It's not like I don't usually sleep under the cloak."

Hermione's fists clenched, and she hissed, "You weren't in your bed."

"If I was in my bed, then that would destroy the whole point of sleeping invisible." I said.

She gave a little screech of frustration, while Mr. Weasley said, "I'm glad you're safe. I suppose you couldn't find us during the attack?"

"Attack?"

One of the Weasley twins spoke, voice filled with the appropriate amount of awe. "You slept through a Death Eater attack?"

After a further ten minutes of failing to communicate (entirely the Weasleys' fault) I found out that a group of Death Eaters had come to wreak havoc, torment Muggles, and generally have a good time. I had slept through it, a skill I'd acquired during my reign of terror.

It was nice, I reflected, to see the Death Eaters taking the initiative. Perhaps they were paying homage to their fallen leader.

I don't know why else they would attack a Quidditch game.

At the Head Table, Dumbledore began his start of term speech. First, he happily informed us that the Dementors had been removed due to our foreign visitors – apparently Beauxbatons takes a dim view on the consumption of their students' souls. Then, he turned to the topic of horrible deaths, as he does every year. I wasn't paying much attention, consumed by my thoughts.

The Triwizard Tournament had finally returned to Hogwarts. It hadn't been around when I was a student, or I would have another trophy to add to my collection. In fact, it hadn't been around for two centuries. Trust Dumbledore to revive a dangerous, Gryffindorishly reckless competition. Still, it fit well in the narrative of Harry Potter, vanquisher of the Dark Lord and future Hogwarts professor.

As we stood to leave the Great Hall, Ginevra at our heels, Ron snatched some sweets from the table.

Hermione sighed dramatically. "Do you really need more sugar, Ronald?"

His words were mangled by a mouthful of food. "Ima gwwing boy."

She wrinkled her nose. "You don't need sugar to grow; you aren't a bacteria. And that's disgusting!"

"You're dis –"

"I'm going to win the Triwizard Tournament," I declared.

"What?!" Hermione shrieked, once again paying attention to me. As is only appropriate. "Harry, that's even worse than your usual ideas. People die doing things like this."

I shrugged. "It can't be any more dangerous than going to school usually is."

Ron frowned, jogging to keep pace with us as I sped up with enthusiasm and Hermione with righteous anger. "I dunno, Dumbledore thinks it's dangerous, and he hires werewolves as professors."

I said, "I still think I'll be fine."

"Well, you can't enter anyway," Hermione sniffed. "It's seventh years and older, no exceptions."

"That doesn't seem very fair. Even if we start doing it regularly again, it isn't due for five more years. I'll have graduated by then. Then I'll never get the chance to compete."

"It's for your own safety," she said.

"The Goblet wouldn't choose me if I couldn't compete." At least, I didn't think it would. How did that work? "But it can hardly judge if I don't put in my name."

"They'll put up protections to stop you," Hermione said with a desperate sort of hope.

"I'll get around them," I assured her.

"I'll help, Harry," Ginevra said.

"Ah, yes, I'd forgotten about you."

We had reached the common room by then, going inside with a muttered, "Flobberworm."

The familiar, red room, filled with chattering students, greeted us. I took the only available chair, earning an insolent glare from Hermione and a "Hey!" from Ron. Ginevra stood without complaint, which nearly made me regret my decision. I took a deep breath.

"Look, Ginevra, we have to talk about this" – I waved my hand vaguely – "following us thing. I didn't say anything before because we were at your house, and you should be able to stalk whomever you like at your house. But this is my house."

"It's a school, Harry. It's nobody's house," Hermione said as she dug out her Transfiguration book, intent upon reading it for the third time before term.

I ignored her, of course. "Now, I appreciate your stepping in last year. You made a perfectly suitable substitute for Ron. But Ron's back, and he has seniority."

Ginevra pouted, asking, "Why can't we both be your friends?"

I shook my head. "We're already perilously close to a Weasley majority. I can't have the two of you stalemating."

"It's not like we're the same person," Ginevra said. "I'm different from my brothers."

"See, now you sound exactly like Ron," I said. "This just isn't going to work. Right, Hermione?"

Hermione didn't even look up from her textbook. "I don't have a problem with Ginny."

"Right, Ron?"

"Yeah," he said, elaborating at his sister's betrayed look. "Sorry, Ginny, but you're my little sister and these are my friends. You should go spend time with your own friends."

Ron paused for a moment. "Uh, you do have friends, right?"

Ginevra frowned but didn't answer. Several seconds passed.

"Ginny?" Ron asked nervously.

"I'm thinking," she snapped.

Hermione finished reading another twelve pages before Ginevra spoke again. "…Yes."

"Good," I said. "Then go and spend time in their company, earn their trust, fashion their loyalty, and when the time is right –"

"You're starting to sound like a Slytherin, mate," Ron said.

"Right, yes. What I meant to say was: Have fun. Also, leave."

Professor Moody's magical eye had locked upon me the moment I entered the classroom, and it hadn't moved yet. He was suspicious of me, I could tell, and I forced my face to remain impassive as he explained the topic of today's lesson:

The Unforgivable Curses.

Still, I couldn't entirely quell my enthusiasm. They were my favorite curses, after all.

"So…do any of you know which curses are most heavily punished by wizarding law?" Moody asked, narrowing his eyes at the class as if one of us was going to burst into tears and confess to a heinous crime.

My hand shot up, followed tentatively by Hermione's. Moody barked, "Go on, Granger."

"The Imperius Curse," Hermione said, "It forces the victim to follow the caster's orders."

"Good," he said. Moody pulled out three cages, each holding a spider. He turned his wand upon one of them and forced it to dance. A few nervous giggles greeted its performance, though none of my classmates took their eyes from the arachnid.

"Think it's funny, do you?" Moody asked. "You'd like it, would you, if I did it to you?"

"No, sir," Longbottom squeaked, shaking his head so quickly that it seemed ready to fly from his shoulders.

"Good, that's next lesson" – Moody laughed – "Anyone else know one? Another illegal curse?"

My hand returned to the air, but at least one of Moody's eyes looked to the back of the room. "You, in the back."

Now he was just toying with me. I should have expected as much from an old friend of Dumbledore.

Longbottom said tentatively, "The Cruciatus Curse."

"Your name's Longbottom?" Moody asked gruffly.

Longbottom attempted to hide under his desk. This might have been more effective if Moody couldn't see through it. He enlarged the second spider, sparking terrified gasps from several students. A few slightly less terrified gasps came when he tortured it using the Cruciatus.

"And the last one?"

Unable to hold back any longer, I shouted, "Avada Kedavra! The Killing Curse. It lets you kill things."

"Yes, I suppose you would know about that," Moody said, giving me an unsettling smile.

He was on to me. He was on to me, and Dumbledore had already given him permission to cast Unforgivables on students.

Moody continued, "You are the only survivor of that curse."

I laughed weakly. "Yes, of course. I'm not sure why else I would know it."

"Not like those bloody snakes," Ron grumbled. "I bet they've been casting them since they were in diapers."

Moody smirked, gave a nod to Ron, and cast Avada Kedavra on the final spider. As my classmates breathed a collective sigh of relief at the arachnid's death, Moody's eye almost popped out of his head to watch me closer.

I hoped my curse would strike early this year.

I tilted my head, examining the age line surrounding the Goblet of Fire. My sixty-eighth birthday was coming up, so it should let me through. Carefully, I nudged my foot against the line, feeling an ominous force pushing it back.

Clearly, it responded to physical and not mental age. Of course, the Weasleys had artificially aged themselves and been thrown back regardless. Perhaps it required both? Or possibly Dumbledore had enchanted it to only allow Seventh Years in. Yes, I decided, that seemed reasonable.

It was probably for the best that I couldn't walk right through. That would raise all sorts of suspicions. No, I would have to take a more subtle approach.

"Wingardium Leviosa," I said. The parchment on which I'd scribbled my name smoothly levitated forward yet started shivering as it crossed the age line. Not far from the Goblet, it stopped altogether, crumpled into a ball, and ricocheted back. The ball bounced off my forehead.

Lip curled, I tossed the piece of parchment in the air and snarled, "Ventis."

It tumbled towards the Goblet atop a spiral of wind which knocked over several unsuspecting passersby. It then returned at equal speed, again hitting my forehead.

I was crouched on the stone floor, putting the last touches on my latest attempt to enter the tournament, when Ron and Hermione interrupted me an hour later.

"'Bout time. We've been looking for you all over. Hermione thought you were in the library." Ron made a face that was – for once – intentionally stupid.

"Harry spends plenty of time in the library," Hermione said. "It's not my fault you like to pretend he's some sort of Quidditch fanatic."

"He's coming around," Ron said with an offended look. "He practically begged me to organize a game last year, and he went to the Cup with us."

"Two instances is hardly evidence of a trend, Ronald," Hermione said.

"Sure it isn't, 'Mione" – Ron faked a cough – "Jealous."

"I'm not jealous," Hermione mumbled, "and you know I hate that nickname."

Grinning, Ron turned his attention to me. "What are you doing on the floor?"

"Beating the age line," I said. I added another slash of ink onto the stone. It was a little wobbly and looked more like a dragon than a unicorn, so I vanished it.

Hermione leaned over to peek at my work. She gasped. "Those are NEWT level runes. You don't even take Ancient Runes!"

"You aren't the only one who reads, Hermione," I said.

She glanced triumphantly at Ron. "I told you."

"So, what's it do?" Ron asked.

Hermione cleared her throat. "Well, I've only read about it in passing, mind you. It's a very complicated work, though not all that uncommon among Curse Breakers who need to move something that they can't touch, or in cases where other means of magical transportation might damage an object. It makes extensive use of the rune –"

"Yeah, but what does it do?"

Hermione sniffed haughtily. "I was getting to that. It's used for teleporting things."

"Dunno why you can't just say that," Ron muttered. "Always have to go off on some –"

"AT LAST!" I cried, rising from the ground. "I've completed it. Oh, sure, Dumbledore protected against physical intrusion and simple spells. But he could never have prepared for something so intricate, so far above anything he would expect of a mere child. But I am more than that. I am Harry Potter, and I will not be thwarted by the likes of him."

I smirked, dropping the ball of parchment atop the rune and laughing as it popped away. My eyes darted to the Goblet. The parchment appeared directly above it, only millimeters from the top. But it didn't fall.

It flew backwards and onto my forehead.

As it fell to the ground, my eye twitched.

I hadn't experienced such intense fury since the dementor incident. I snatched up the crumpled parchment and blindly flung it at the Goblet. It traveled uninterrupted as it passed the age line, bounced against the Goblet's interior, and fell inside.

Ron gaped. "You can just throw it in?"

"Of course," I said. "They would never think to protect against the most base, mundane, Muggle methods. After all, who would stoop so low?"

I smirked, congratulating myself on my astounding success. "Ron, bring me more paper. In fact, bring me all the paper you can find. Ink, too."

Ron scurried off to do my bidding. Hermione, always questioning my decisions, asked, "Why do you need paper?"

"I have to put my name in more times, obviously," I said.

She pursed her lips. "No, you only need to put your name in once."

"Yes, that is what they would have you believe," I said, "but I've contemplated this thoroughly. No one knows how the Goblet works or why it chooses the student it does. Oh, sure, sometimes it picks a great fighter with unmatched cunning, but, others, it picks someone whose name was put in as a joke or a Hufflepuff."

In retrospect, I was being redundant.

"So?" Hermione asked.

"It's a lottery."

Hermione rolled her eyes. "That's ridiculous."

"No, believing that a big cup can choose the greatest champion based on a name on a slip of paper is ridiculous. What's it do, analyze the handwriting?"

"It's very advanced magic," Hermione said.

"Or it picks a name at random. What do you think is more likely?"

Ron raced towards me, a stack of parchment in hand. "Got 'em."

I nodded. "Good, now get more."

He took off again. I tore a strip of parchment off a sheet, scribbled my name, and shoved it into Hermione's hands. "Make use of your terrible, Muggle origins and start throwing."

"And, from Beauxbatons, Fleur Delacour," Dumbledore said. A haughty witch in powder blue flounced towards the back room.

Hermione shot me a triumphant look. "See? Both of the champions were their schools' favorites to win, and they're each very talented. It's not a lottery."

I laughed, admiring her pigheaded attachment to an obviously incorrect theory. "That's probably because they were the only ones who entered."

"Are you sure?" Hermione asked.

"I spent eight hours camped out next to the Goblet yesterday. I'm pretty sure."

"Finally," Dumbledore said. "For Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry…"

A third slip of parchment shot into his hands atop a jet of green flame. "…Harry Potter."

"Told you," I said, standing to take a bow.

A wave of disgruntled whispers echoed across the Great Hall. I don't know why any of them were surprised. Honestly, who were they expecting? A Hufflepuff?

A Durmstrang student gasped. "They can't actually let him compete. He's a Fourth Year!"

A Seventh Year Hufflepuff sighed. "It's always the bloody Gryffindors."

"He must have cheated!" Draco Malfoy cried.

"Yeah, he cheated," one of the Weasley twins shouted. "What did you think he was doing in the Great Hall yesterday – making paper airplanes or something?"

I smirked. "I am the best at cheating, or I wouldn't have been chosen by the Goblet."

"That doesn't make any sense," a Beauxbaton student said.

I ignored them, sauntering towards the door where the previous champions had exited. Suddenly, the Goblet flared again, and Dumbledore cleared his throat. "It appears to be Harry Potter again…in different handwriting."

"Merlin's tit, Harry broke the cup!" Ron yelled.

I said, "I hope it doesn't do that with all the entries."

Dumbledore appeared troubled. "My boy, just how many times did you put your name in?"

"Oh, three hundred or so. A lot bounced off the rim, so it was difficult to keep track," I admitted.

"How the hell did you manage that?" someone shouted from the Slytherin table.

"It was a lot easier once I got the house-elf production line going," I said. "I never thought I would be so grateful for Hermione's literacy program."

"I didn't start that so they'd be better slaves," Hermione snapped.

"And yet that was still the result," I said. The harder she struggled against her naturally evil tendencies, the greater the eventual damage became. It was awe-inspiring, really.

I left Hermione to her anger and followed the other champions.

Twenty minutes later, we were still waiting in the same room. Delacour actively ignored me, while Krum's abortive attempts at conversation faltered before the shouting going on a few feet away. I watched in amusement as the judges squabbled over my entry.

With her champion's fervent support, the Beauxbatons Headmistress insisted that competing against a fourteen-year-old wasn't very sporting. I personally had no problem beating children a third my age. The event organizer, Crouch, was similarly worried that Britain would be at a disadvantage.

In contrast, Igor Karkaroff feared the overwhelming power implied by the night I vanquished myself. It was hard to say if that was a sign of his intelligence, cowardice, or paranoia. Or perhaps he'd simply seen that Dumbledore was twinkling again.

"Now, now, there's nothing to be done but let him compete," Dumbledore said. "The Goblet of Fire is magically binding, and the boy was chosen by it."

"Twice," I added helpfully.

"We wouldn't want him to lose his magic, or even his life, because we were trying to protect him," he continued, smiling serenely.

They couldn't argue with Dumbledore – no one ever can for long – so the judges begrudgingly agreed to let me compete and stormed off to sulk elsewhere. Their champions soon followed.

"Lemon drop?" Dumbledore asked.

I shook my head, unwilling to risk whatever concoction he'd devised to punish me for this latest scheme.

"No one ever wants my lemon drops," he sighed dramatically. Dumbledore popped a lemon drop in his mouth, winked at me, and left as well.

Severus sneered at me from the corner of the room, sweeping forward only when everyone else had left. "You really are exactly like your father – an arrogant, conceited, reckless fool with no regard for your own or others' safety. But even he would not have been so moronic as to enter a dangerous magical competition. Repeatedly."

I gave him a lazy smile. Bantering with Severus was such fun. "Well, what can I say? I'm a typical Gryffindor, not a slimy Slytherin like you."

Severus's eyes flashed with fury, and he leaned in so close that spittle flew at my face. "Do you think this is a game, Potter?"

"Technically, it's a tournament," I said.

Severus drew back, almost physically reigning in his emotions. He was silent for several moments, his lip curled in disgust at what he was about to do. "I think it's about time you were actually punished. Twenty points from Slytherin."

My eyes widened. "You can't do that! I'm not even in that house."

Severus smiled cruelly, drawling, "Five more for your cheek," as he walked away.

"I don't understand," Hermione asked as we made our way towards the common room. "Why doesn't he just give you detention?"

I chuckled. "Oh, he tried that back in First Year. So long as he's there, I rather enjoy them, and, if they're unsupervised, I try to brew Felix Felicis and leave him to clean up the resulting poisons. The detentions are inevitably more of a punishment for him than me."

We passed through the portrait entrance. Inside, a party was in full swing. They'd been planning this ever since the tournament was first announced because the Hogwarts champion was obviously going to be a Gryffindor.

A cheer erupted when the partiers spotted us, and someone shoved a butterbeer in my hand. I grinned, announcing, "My plan has finally come to fruition. Snape has decided to take points from Slytherin every time I annoy him. We are going to sweep the Cup for the NEXT FOUR YEARS!"

A second cheer went up, and a few people slapped me on the back. They soon turned their attention towards a keg of Weasley-smuggled firewhiskey. As we jostled our way through the crowd, Hermione said, "Harry, you weren't actually planning…"

"Nope."

"So you've just suddenly stopped rooting for Slytherin?"

"I came to a very important realization today," I said. "It doesn't matter what color the Great Hall is during the Leaving Feast or who gets bragging rights for the next year. What matters is that I am the one who decides."

"There is something seriously wrong with you," Hermione murmured.

"Thank you," I said. "Speaking of something seriously wrong, there's Ron!"

Ron sat in a bright-red armchair, an island of misery among the jovial crowd. He stared morosely at the contents of a textbook. Something was obviously amiss. Ron doesn't read.

"Ron?" Hermione said softly. "Are you alright?"

Ron shrugged, muttering, "Yeah, I just…well, I was just hoping it would be me."

I plucked the book from his lap before he became confused and tried to eat it or something. "You had your twelve chances, Ron. It's no one's fault that the Goblet chose me in its lottery. Except possibly Dumbledore."

"You can't blame Dumbledore for all your problems, Harry," Hermione sighed.

I shook my head. "This is different. I'm blaming him for Ron's problems."

A/N: Seventh Horcrux is now completed on SpaceBattles, with omakes being posted every couple of days. As always, the link is on my profile.

Chapter 8: HP vs Alastor Moody (Pt 3)

Seventh Horcrux

Chapter 5: Harry Potter vs. Alastor Moody (Pt. 3)

It was breakfast time, but Hermione wasn't eating. She held my golden egg in her hands, staring down at it with pinched lips. "I can't believe you're just ignoring this. I mean, really, Harry, this is a very dangerous competition. You can't just throw away opportunities to prepare yourself."

"I don't need the help, and I've always despised riddles," I said.

"It probably isn't even that hard!" Hermione cried. "I could solve it for you, and Viktor's already figured it out. I could ask him –"

"No, Hermione. That would be cheating."

"You cheat all the time," Hermione said.

"That's true," I admitted. "But I cheat in ways that require skill and dedication. Asking a competitor is just pathetic."

"It's not like he's a Slytherin or anything." Ron glared at the green table, as he often does.

I could tell that Hermione hadn't entirely given up by the way she frowned down at the egg, not even noticing when Ron stole her biscuit. She absentmindedly paid an owl for the day's Prophet, and the owl stole Ron's newly-acquired biscuit. Ron was shouting at it when one of our classmates – Lavender Brown – leaned over.

"I hate to be the bearer of bad news," the blonde crooned in a way that said quite the opposite, "but you might want to read that paper."

Startled, Hermione opened it and let out an indignant squawk. "What is wrong with that Skeeter woman?!"

"What did she do?" Ron asked.

"She wrote about me, and she's talking like I'm some sort of" – Hermione wrinkled her nose – "seductress."

She cleared her throat, quoting, "The rather plain girl has been working her way through Hogwarts' most eligible bachelors. First, she led on likely Triwizard Tournament winner Harry Potter. Then, she had an infamous tryst with Draco Malfoy" – Ron choked on his mouthful of food – "Now, she's moved on to seventeen-year-old Bulgarian National Quidditch Team seeker, Viktor Krum. With two Triwizard competitors under Miss Granger's thumb, this reporter has to ask: Could a certain veela be the next champion charmed?"

"That…that…" Hermione's fingers were white as she clutched the golden egg. "I won't let her get away with this."

With a fervent gleam in her eye, Hermione stormed from the hall, not even noticing that she still held my prize from the First Task. I almost felt sorry for Skeeter. She had no idea who she'd trifled with when she'd revealed Hermione's latest scheme.

"You alright, mate?" Ron asked, nervously peering into the black depths of the lake as we waited for the Second Task to begin.

"Absolutely fine," I declared.

"You can be, um, underwater? Without dying?"

"I'm Harry Potter," I said flatly, "and you're starting to sound like Hermione."

Ron shuddered at the comparison. "Right. Sorry, mate. It's just that I've heard drowning really sucks, and Hermione is…wherever she is."

Hermione had disappeared, no doubt busy plotting against her newest enemy. There hadn't been time to find a substitute, so it seemed that Ron was attempting to fulfill both roles. This would have been admirable if he wasn't failing so spectacularly.

I surveyed the area. Spectators milled about the lake, sometimes poking a foot in only to hastily withdraw it once they felt the frigid water. The Weasley children had consumed a large portion of the stands, as per usual, and Ron headed towards them.

Moody was stalking about, glaring at everyone who looked slightly suspicious. This list included Karkaroff, Severus, and me. Draco Malfoy practically fell into the lake in an attempt avoid him. The boy had been suprisingly timid since his return from Christmas break. Clearly, his confidence was shaken by Hermione's rejection.

The current object of her affections waved me over from his place at the starting line. Krum asked, "Do you know vhere Er-my-o-knee is?"

I shrugged. "Probably in the library plotting against Skeeter. It's the sort of thing she does."

Krum nodded, chuckling. "You did not find the clue?"

"I didn't need to," I said. "It's just water."

One of the judges – a pompous ministry worker whose name I hadn't bothered learning – cleared his throat. "Everyone is ready to start, then?"

Krum nodded, but Delacour and I merely shot the judge disdainful looks.

The judge looked nervous. "Alright. The Second Task will start on my whistle. The champions have precisely an hour to recover what's been taken from them. The task begins in 3…2…1."

He blew a whistle, and I immediately whirled around to face Delacour. I shouted, "Silencio!"

She was sputtering soundlessly when I left. It was possible she would manage to overpower my spell and regain her voice, provided she knew the countercharm. But Beauxbatons had a poor reputation for nonverbal magic, and a slight delay would give me a head start in the race.

I jumped over the lake, casting the Ebublio Jinx at my chest. A large bubble full of air surrounded me, as I sunk into the lake. I cast the Aqua Eructo Charm, causing a jet of water to shoot from my wand. This propelled me forward, deep into the water and towards the merpeople's song.

I continued like that for some time. The Ebublio bubble protected me from the freezing lake water and various nuisances, such as Grindylows. As time passed, however, it grew thinner and more fragile.

Eventually, I realized that I was being followed. A glance backwards revealed an enormous shark coming after me. It was clearly charmed to attack competitors. A severing charm sent it hurtling towards the bottom of the lake, clouds of red floating in its wake.

Not long afterwards, I encountered the first roughly-hewn, dilapidated homes of the merpeople village. The hideous creatures peered out at me from their glassless windows, their grey-skinned faces framed by seaweed-like hair. I never tried to recruit the mermen in my previous life, primarily because they creep me out.

In the town square, a whole crowd of them were gathered. They continued to sing, yellow eyes watching as I ended the Ebublio bubble and replaced it with a Bubblehead Charm. A great, stone statue of a merman towered at their center, three girls tied to his tail – Hermione, Ginevra, and a young blonde.

I paused before them, considering the situation. Clearly, there was one hostage for each competitor. But who was mine?

If I had to choose one to save, it would undoubtedly be Hermione. Yet she had gone to the Yule Ball with Krum, just as Ginevra had with me.

The hostage wasn't based upon one's Yule date, however, because I was fairly certain that Delacour had not gone with a little girl. Beyond that, it was entirely possible I had interacted with the child before and simply didn't remember.

I refused to lose points for rescuing the wrong person. Hermione or Ginevra were both perfectly reasonable options, and the little girl wasn't out of the question, either. At that point, it was just easier to take them all.

I threw a blasting curse at the base of the statue's tail. Suddenly, the merpeople stopped singing. They raised their spears and approached me. I was surrounded.

"While that does explain Mr. Krum's unfortunate injury and your decision to take all three hostages – destroying a merperson relic in the process – I'm afraid I still don't understand what you did afterwards," Dumbledore said, looking very tired.

This was a small improvement over the rest of the judges, who appeared livid.

"It was a perfectly logical decision," I insisted. "The mermen were using their environmental advantage against me. So I took it from them."

"You banished all the water in the lake. You truly don't consider that excessive?" Dumbledore asked.

"Not at all. Besides, I figured the spectators would have a better time if they could actually watch the task. Really, I was doing you all a favor."

Dumbledore said, "But the merpeople are unable to survive on air for more than a few minutes. You greatly endangered their lives, my boy."

I raised an eyebrow. "They greatly endangered mine first when they attacked me with spears, and, really, a few less mermen is hardly a problem. They kill more students than the moving staircase…and we all know what I did to the moving staircase."

The denizens of Hogwarts simultaneously shivered, though the foreigners seemed rather perplexed. Karkaroff scowled. "Viktor Krum also had gills at the time, and he was already injured by your attack."

"And my Fleur was fifty feet in ze air when ze water disappeared!" Madame Maxime said, "and zat is after ze 'orrible boy cast a Silencing Spell on 'er."

"There weren't any rules that said I couldn't attack the competition. Honestly, I thought that was the entire point," I said.

"It was a race, not a duel," Karkaroff said.

"Yes, exactly, and I won," I said. "In fact, I'm the only one who brought his hostage back at all…whichever one she was."

"Ginevra Weasley," Dumbledore said.

I shook my head, dismayed by their ridiculous expectations. "How was I supposed to guess that? We aren't even friends."

Some distance across the grounds, a still-dripping Ginevra said, "We will be!"

I shivered. This was beginning to remind me uncomfortably of the Bellatrix situation. "And I'm not sure why you think it's my responsibility to protect everyone. It's your competition. You should have expected I would do something like this."

Moody grunted, "That's why I put up the splash guard."

"See, why can't you all be like Moody?" I asked. We all turned our attention towards the ex-auror, who was currently shimmering with no less than twenty protective charms.

Dumbledore sighed. "Could you return the lake water, now that the task is over?"

"I would do that," I said, "except that I'm not entirely sure where I sent it."

Meanwhile, at Privet Drive

Petunia Dursley stood knee-deep in the flooded street, staring blankly at what was once her house. The front door had floated to the very end of her waterlogged lawn. Every window was broken, and what little she could see of her immaculate carpets and organized kitchen was entirely ruined. She didn't dare to think of what had happened to the garden.

As she picked up a floating photograph of baby Dudley, Petunia wondered – for a moment – where her life had gone so wrong. But the answer was obvious:

The moment she accepted Harry Potter into her life. This was all his fault. Things usually were.

With a firm set to her mouth and her spindly fingers curled into a fist, Petunia trudged towards her home in the hope that some of her previous life was still salvageable.

They were, she decided, moving.

"Holy harpies! Have you seen this?" Ginevra Weasley cried, ruining a perfectly peaceful breakfast.

Ron's head jerked up, and he asked, "Muh? Wha's it?"

"You're talking with your mouth full again, Ronald," Hermione chided. She hadn't even stirred at Ginevra's exclamation, idly reading a book on Charms.

Ginevra waved the morning Prophet at us so that it rustled a bit. "They printed a retraction! I didn't even know they could do that."

"It must have been a grievous error to prompt them to admit a mistake. They've probably offended hundreds of wizards, or perhaps a truly powerful group," I said thoughtfully. "What was the article about? The Wizengamot? Dumbledore? The Dark Lord?"

"Um, it was about Hermione, actually," Ginevra said. "Skeeter says that she trusted the wrong source, Hermione actually wasn't dating everyone in school, and Skeeter felt 'compelled to correct this mistake due to her journalistic integrity.'"

I slowly turned to face Hermione, who had returned to her book with a pleased smirk on her face. "Hermione…what did you do?"

"Who says I did anything?" Hermione sniffed. "Maybe Rita Skeeter just realized that she made a mistake –"

Even Ron snorted in response to that. "Yeah, right. I'm with Harry: You did something."

"It's pretty obvious," Ginevra agreed.

Giggling, Hermione glanced around nervously but nodded. "Well, alright. We probably shouldn't talk about this here, though. It's rather public."

"Behaving like a Slytherin, 'Mione," Ron said.

"Don't care, Ronald," she said in a sing-song voice. She was positively giddy. I was beginning to feel legitimately concerned for Rita Skeeter.

Hermione stood. "Shall we go, then?"

I shook my head. "No need. Muffliato."

The surrounding conversations turned to an insect-like buzzing. Hermione sat back down and asked, "Ooh, is that an anti-eavesdropping charm? I've read about those."

"I'm well aware that you've read about everything, and, yes, it is an anti-eavesdropping spell. The only people who can understand our conversation now are the three of us."

My point was punctuated by a sudden and loud buzzing from across the table as Ginevra realized that she was not included in the charm. Ron edged away from his rapidly-reddening sister. "So how'd you do it?"

Hermione said, "I was out on the grounds, practicing an animagus detection charm. It seemed like a good idea after the attack from Sirius Black that Harry never told me about" – she glared at me before resuming – "Imagine my surprise when it came back positive. Apparently, Rita Skeeter has been skulking around as a beetle. So I caught her in my hand – "

"You squished her, didn't you?" I asked. Suddenly, everything was very clear to me: The retraction, Skeeter's claims of journalistic integrity, Hermione's inexplicable good mood…

She sputtered. "W-what? But…Harry, she just published an article."

"Polyjuice potion. It would allow you to impersonate her for long enough to get the article through, and it would also keep anyone from knowing she was missing, obscuring her time of death. Since she died in her animagus form, there isn't a corpse. It's the perfect crime."

"I would never –"

"It's not like you haven't done something like this before," I said. "Don't you remember Second Year? I shudder to think what would have happened if we hadn't stopped you."

Hermione growled low in her throat. "You are just horrible sometimes!"

"I'm not the one who killed a reporter," I said.

"Uh, I don't think she killed anyone," Ron said. "Right, Hermione?"

"Obviously," she huffed. "I'm just threatening to report that she's an illegal animagus. I also kept her in a bottle for a while."

I frowned. "For how long?"

"A couple of days," Hermione said.

"Did you feed her?" I asked.

Hermione paled. "It didn't really occur to me."

"You gave her water at least…" I said.

"Um…"

I shook my head, caught between admiration and shock. "And now you're blackmailing her? I don't know why you didn't just kill her quickly. It would have been kinder."

I have a great distaste for most forms of torture. My only exception to this is Crucio, which is much cleaner and does not have as many long-lasting side effects. Well, unless the victims are driven insane. I rarely kept prisoners long enough to reach that point, however, and opted to kill as often as possible. Further, I sought to never leave a child orphaned for more than a few minutes.

And people said I was immoral!

Ron said, "That doesn't seem fair. It's not like she meant to hurt her."

"Intention is irrelevant. Besides," I said, "who knows when Skeeter will try to retaliate. She could be here right now. Listening."

We fell into a wary, thoughtful silence. The only sound was the persistent buzzing of Ginevra Weasley.

"I feel a sense of impending doom," I declared.

"Isn't that how you always feel?" Ron asked.

"This is stronger than usual."

I glanced around the area surrounding Dumbledore's enormous maze with a thoughtful air. Moody limped outside, glaring at anyone who dared to look at him for more than a moment. I turned my attention swiftly away.

Ginevra hovered nearby. She had ingratiated herself with a group of younger Hufflepuffs, but she was clearly paying more attention to Ron and I than her companions.

Dumbledore, Karkaroff, and Madame Maxime were arguing about something at the judge's table. Hermione stood nearby, spoke a few words, and then fled their continued shouting. For a moment, I wondered if she and Dumbledore were collaborating on an insidious plan. But, no, that was ridiculous. Hermione would never share her power with Dumbledore.

Delacour was chattering in animated French with her family. Krum, though surrounded by his own family, seemed distracted. His eyes darted around uneasily and his mouth was set in a firm line.

Hermione, hurrying back from the judge's table, said, "Maybe you wouldn't be so nervous if you'd actually prepared for the task."

I scoffed. "I'm not nervous, Hermione. I'm suspicious."

"Paranoid," Ron muttered.

I turned to Hermione. "Right, speaking of Moody, I want you to watch him. I think he might try something today."

Hermione rolled her eyes. "Harry, Moody isn't going to –"

"For Merlin's sake, Hermione! For once in your life, try to save a friend instead of killing him," I snapped.

Her lips twisted in an ugly manner, but the girl begrudgingly turned her attention towards Moody. I cleared my throat and spoke to Ron. "And you should watch Krum. He seems suspicious."

"Harry!" Hermione cried.

"I knew you wouldn't be objective about this. That's why I've entrusted the task to Ron."

Ron grinned, looking pleased with himself.

Ginevra sidled a little closer to us. "I can watch Fleur."

I waved her off. "Do whatever you like."

While Ginevra busied herself with her useless idea, I would observe the most likely candidate: Dumbledore. I glared at him as he sat perfectly calm amid his fellow judges' bickering, smug beneath his white beard and floral robes. Despicable.

"What were you doing over there, anyway?" Ron asked Hermione.

"Oh, um…" Hermione suddenly fell into a coughing fit, and I edged away from her. I had no intention of catching some sort of Muggle disease.

She cleared her throat and spoke primly. "Sorry about that. I must have gotten a bit of a cold during the last task."

"But it's been four months," Ron said. Even without moving my gaze from Dumbledore, I could picture the wrinkling of his Weasley face.

"Certain viruses are able to incubate for long periods, and my immune system was heavily compromised. I just went over to ask Dumbledore about the Ancient Runes curriculum. I was confused about…the order in which certain runes are taught, but he explained it to me."

"That's nice, Hermione," I said absentmindedly. Dumbledore's skeletal hand gripped his wand, and he rose smoothly. Moody had migrated to his side – something I would have been aware of earlier if Hermione had been taking her sentry duties seriously.

Dumbledore pointed his wand towards himself, and I suppressed my disappointment when he only cast a Sonorous Charm. His voice echoed across the grounds, drawing everyone's attention. "Much as it pains me to further delay this exciting event. We have decided upon a few rules for the task."

Curious whispering swept the crowd. Dumbledore peered down at a roll of parchment. "First, there will be no intentionally damaging the maze through means including – but not limited to – flooding it, setting it on fire, tearing it apart with wind or explosive magic, dismantling the runes that constructed it, or the use of fiendfyre."

"Oh come on, like anyone would seriously use fiendfyre," one of the older Hogwarts students grumbled.

Karkaroff glared darkly in my direction. "It needed to be said."

"Nor can anyone remove the maze from school grounds."

"Not even temporarily?" I asked.

"No, Mr. Potter," Dumbledore said with a merry twinkle of his eyes. "Second, any deaths that occur (whether of humans or creatures) will be examined and may lead to the loss of the championship. Further, no one is permitted to sabotage their fellow champions prior to entering the maze."

"Ooh, Fleur looks mad," Ginevra said.

Fleur did, indeed, look mad. Her clenched jaw seemed to harden her cheekbones, and a red line flushed across her face. With a string of French curses, she slashed her wand downwards.

My feeling of impending doom fell to its normal level. Krum also seemed to relax. He waved happily at Hermione.

Dumbledore said, "Third, no champion may bring a magical artifact, aside from their wand, inside the maze."

I shoved my invisibility cloak at Ron, scowling.

"Fourth, no one is allowed to summon the Cup."

Well, there went Plan A.

I suspect Dumbledore realized that, as well. Why else would he be so sickeningly cheerful? "Finally, no champion may enlist the aid of any other human or magical creature, such as a house-elf."

Oh, that was why.

I whirled around to glare at Hermione. "Oh, come on! That isn't even fair."

"Neither is using slave labor to cheat," she said.

"It wasn't cheating until he said it was."

"It was morally!"

"Don't pretend to care about morals now" – I ran a hand through my hair – "What am I supposed to do? Dumbledore just got rid of all my good plans."

"Why don't you just go and do the maze the way it's supposed to be done?" Ron said.

"Ron, that's ridiculous. I'm not some sort of Gryffin…on second thought, that's genius."

"It is?" Ron said, undermining his short burst of intelligence.

"I've been acting too much like a Slytherin lately," I said. "Yes, it's ensured my success. But what sort of victory will it be when everyone decides I'm evil and refuses to hire me in a teaching position? No, I will win this like a Gryffindor."

On fire for the third time in the past half-hour, I reflected that acting like a Gryffindor was a terrible idea. I should have known this earlier, of course, because it was Ron's.

I cast Aguamenti to put out the fire, but my impressive power made the jet of water significantly larger than I intended.

Wet and miserable, I trudged through the maze. It was at that point that I saw the sphinx. I groaned. Great, more riddles. I was beginning to wonder if the tournament was designed by a Ravenclaw.

The sphinx turned her almond-shaped eyes to me, looking far too pleased with herself considering she was almost certainly going to die at my hand.

She said, "You are very near your goal. The quickest way is past me."

I pointed my wand at the creature. "If you value your life, I would suggest you move."

The sphinx chuckled gruffly. "If you value yours, I would suggest you not attack me. Solve my riddle and –"

"Wait a second," I said. "What if I tell you a riddle, and – if you can't solve it – you let me pass?"

The sphinx cocked her head curiously. "I accept your challenge, though I warn you; there is no such thing as a riddle I cannot solve. And, when I solve it, you shall have to find another path."

"It's a good thing you won't, then. I can't afford to waste time." This was primarily because the judges refused to let me enter the maze first even though I clearly won every task.

"Your riddle?"

I nodded, taking a few moments to fix it in my head. Smirking, I began.

"Born in a garden, I live in a house.

Sleeping with lions, I'm more of a mouse.

When death comes to collect me

A hungry grim is all I see."

The sphinx was thoughtful for a few minutes, finally saying, "The answer is man."

"Wrong," I said. The answer was: Ron's dead rat. Or, alternatively, whatever I decided it was because I'm not going to play fair when my victory is at stake.

The sphinx's mouth fell open, reminding me of Hermione. "But that's impossible! The answer is clearly man."

"No, it isn't."

"Then what is the answer?"

I sighed heavily. "Look, if I had gotten it wrong, would you have told me the answer? No, because that would only disrespect my intelligence."

The sphinx attacked me then. This is exactly the reason everyone dislikes magical creatures. They go back on their deals and are just generally unreasonable.

I followed Delacour's screams. This wasn't out of any foolish, Gryffindor chivalry. It was simply the intelligent thing to do.

The maze had been suspiciously easy. Oh, sure, it was filled with all sorts of monsters and traps, but this was designed by Dumbledore. Where were the deadly creatures?

The answer was obvious: They were surrounding the Cup.

Ergo, whatever was killing Delacour was almost certainly at the center of the maze. Also, she was currently beating me, which was absolutely not okay.

I was fortunate. Delacour was only a few turns away, and a hasty point-me spell guided me to her. When I arrived, however, I paused in surprise.

The girl was not being ravaged by a dragon or clubbed by a mountain troll. She was suffering under the Cruciatius, and the one casting it was none other than Viktor Krum.

Delacour let out a final shriek and fell unconscious, unable to take the pain any longer. Rage filled my chest, and my hands shook as they clenched my wand. How dare he…How dare he…

I spat, "Hermione taught you this. Didn't she?"

How dare he take advantage of Hermione's insidious genius! Only I'm allowed to do that.

Krum turned towards me, his eyes devoid of emotion. It seemed that I had been right all along. Krum appeared to be a likable, perfectly ordinary student – like me – but he was nothing more than a cold, calculating schemer.

More importantly, he was a cold, calculating schemer who was trying to steal my victory and Hogwarts secrets. And that was simply unacceptable.

I quirked an eyebrow. "No answer? Coward. Have you no – Stupefy!"

Krum fell to the ground, body frozen. He'd never even lifted his wand.

"Well, that was depressingly easy," I muttered, already wandering off to find the Cup.

After a few more minor skirmishes with the wildlife, I found it. The Triwizard Cup gleamed in the center of the maze. I took a moment to straighten my robes and smooth down my hair so that I would look properly impressive when I emerged victoriously outside of Hogwarts. After a moment's thought, I rumpled my clothes and tousled my hair again. That way I would look more heroic.

Grinning, I grabbed my trophy and felt the familiar tug of a portkey at my navel. As the world began to twist and stretch me like taffy, I was struck by a sudden thought:

Was the Triwizard Cup supposed to do that?

A/N: I made a separate email account to catch all of the alerts I get when y'all fav, follow, or review (I am, indeed, WATCHING you all). I then forgot about that account for two weeks. In two weeks, I received four hundred and fourteen emails, among them somewhere between thirty and fifty reviews for this and other stories.

I tend to edit in short bursts of two or three chapters, when time allows, and would usually wait a little longer before posting an update. But I am more than a little emotional over the response this story has received (both here, and back...is home the right word?...back home at SpaceBattles). Let's celebrate. :)

Chapter 10: HP vs DoM

Seventh Horcrux

Harry Potter vs. The Department of Mysteries

Hermione Granger woke to a rapping sound. She yawned, grumbling softly as she padded across her bedroom and opened her window. A barn owl fluttered inside and perched on her night table, a letter clutched in its talons.

Hermione waited a moment by the window, enjoying the breeze against her face, before following the creature. She murmured, "I don't suppose this could have waited for morning?"

The owl chittered angrily, and she smiled as she retrieved the letter. "I guess not."

She felt carefully for the flaps in the darkness, opening it slowly but without the slightest tearing – almost as if she were a spy sneaking a peek at someone else's mail. She unfolded the letter, then frowned. "Blank?"

Hermione turned to the owl. "You traveled all this way just to give a blank letter? Well, I suppose it might not have been that far. Then again, I was in Scotland this morning and traveling for hours. Were you following me all that time, or did you just know that I would be here when you landed? I mean, really, how do owls track people?"

"Don't overthink it. That's the reason why we had to switch to owls in the first place."

Hermione jumped, eye darting wildly around the room before settling on where I leaned against her windowsill.

"Harry! I didn't see you there."

I frowned. "Then who were you talking to?"

I think she raised an eyebrow, though it was difficult to be certain in the dark. "The owl, of course."

"That's crazy," I said.

Hermione raised a hand, pointer finger extended and quite ready to argue with me. She lowered it, however, upon realizing that she could never win. "Speaking of crazy, what are you doing here?"

"I figured we should break into the Department of Mysteries."

"Tonight?" she squeaked.

"The guard should be light, and there won't be many witnesses. It's as good a time as any."

"So, when you said, 'I'll get you when the time is right,' you meant tonight?"

I'm quite certain she raised an eyebrow that time.

I said, "Well, I wasn't originally planning on it, but apparently the Dursleys moved. I realized that I didn't have any place to sleep, so I decided not to. I'm thinking we'll head out now, get into the Ministry before dawn, and then go grab breakfast."

"Your family abandoned you?!" Trust Hermione to latch on to the least important part of my statement.

"They'll probably be back in a few weeks, so obliviated that they occasionally forget how to breathe."

She clapped her hands over her mouth, eyes wide. I legitimately have no idea why anyone thinks she cares about things. Her acting is atrocious. "That's awful. Who would do that?"

"I dunno. Dumbledore? It's usually Dumbledore. I could find them first, I suppose, if I really wanted to, but I just don't like them that much. Now, about going to the Ministry…"

"Right, yes," she mumbled. "How did you get here, anyway? I didn't even know you had my address."

"I don't. I followed the owl."

Hermione stood there for a moment, blinking. "You what?"

"It's really simple, actually. You just write someone a letter, give it to an owl, and then fly behind them. The owl doesn't care, and they're more reliable than most tracking charms."

"Oh. Is there a way to stop owls from finding you, then?"

I shrugged. "I suppose, but I don't know why anyone would. You wouldn't get your letters."

"But, if you were a convicted felon, then people could find you this way."

"Theoretically."

"Like, Sirius Black," she said, looking a bit desperate, "Surely he's stopped owls from following him."

"I don't know why he would. He probably wants his letters, and I doubt he has a permanent address. That's just begging to be caught."

Hermione sighed heavily. "Are we getting Ron, then?"

"Oh, I've already got him. He's under the cloak, outside your window."

I paused for a moment, considering the situation. "He should probably take it off while we get on the broom, though. If you misjudged the distance and fell two stories, we'd probably have to delay our mission."

She twisted her lips thoughtfully. "The broom? As in, only one?"

"Of course. How else would we stay under the cloak? Besides, you and I aren't any good at flying, so it seems like the safest option."

"Galloping Gargoyles, Ron, keep it steady!" I shouted.

"I can't," Ron whined. "There's too much weight on it. I don't think it's supposed to hold more than one person."

"If we die, it's entirely your fault," I informed him.

Hermione poked me in the ribs, saying firmly, "We are not going to die."

I snorted. "Of course not. But, if we did, it would be Ron's fault."

"Why did we have to fly all the way to London, anyway?" Ron asked.

I rolled my eyes, though the effect was entirely lost since I was clinging to Ron's back and Hermione had her face buried in mine. "Do you have any better ideas?"

"Yeah, sure I do. We could've taken the Knight Bus, or flooed, or talked Bill into apparating us. He's visiting, and he wouldn't have snitched –"

"Enough with your whining, Ron. Don't make me regret not taking Ginevra in your place. It's not like she didn't offer."

"Why didn't you take her, then?" Hermione asked.

"She annoys me. Besides, she's willing to cover for Ron and pretend to be him, if necessary. As slowly as this is going, I suspect it will be."

Hermione's arms suddenly tensed around me. "Oh, I am going to be in so much trouble."

"What have you done this time?" I asked.

"Nothing," she snapped. "Well, just this. But my parents don't know that I'm out, and they're bound to be upset."

"Just tell them you had a surprise sleepover with Ron and me."

She giggled, the motion causing an uncomfortable tickling sensations by my shoulder blades. "You want me to tell my parents that I snuck out of the house to stay the night with two teenage boys? I think I'd be better off telling them we were stealing a prophecy to defeat Lord Voldemort. At least then they'll be too confused to be angry."

"I think that's London," Ron interrupted, steering us downward.

After three hours of wandering the city and poking our heads into telephone booths, we found the entrance to the Ministry of Magic.

We gathered under the invisibility cloak before stepping inside the red box. Nothing happened for several seconds.

"Did we pick the wrong one again?" Hermione whispered.

I shook my head. "No, this has got to be it. One of us will have to get out and dial the number."

Ron immediately shifted the cloak so that he could scramble to the phone. At our startled faces, he grinned. "I figure it's a lot like being bait."

He dialed 62442. A woman's tinny voice said, "Welcome to the Ministry of Magic. Who is this?"

Ron returned to his usual oafish demeanor. "Erm…"

"Percy Weasley," I shouted.

"What?" he squeaked.

"No one will notice the difference," I assured him.

Hermione said, "I hardly think –"

"What is your business here today, Mr. Weasley?" the voice asked.

Ron snorted. "Probably brownnosing."

"Thank you. Please take the badge and attach it to the front of your robes."

He reached down, grabbed a chunky, silver badge from the chute, and burst into laughter.

"What is it?" Hermione asked.

Ron just shook his head, which had turned bright red. With trembling hands, he affixed the badge to his robes.

"Ron, I demand that you tell me what is so funny," I said.

The redhead, still grinning, turned so that the badge faced us, it blocky letters easily legible. It read:

Percival Weasley

Meeting the Minister

Not entirely certain what was funny about that, I stayed silent. It was probably a Weasley thing.

The voice continued as we shuddered to a stop, "Visitor to the Ministry, you are required to submit to a search and present your wand for registration at the security desk, which is located at the far end of the Atrium."

Ron nervously glanced around the Ministry's hall. He muttered, "Uh, should I go to the security desk or…"

I replied, "That's what the voice said."

"But is it a good idea to just walk up to the guard with my badge saying I'm Percy?"

"Ron, trust me, no one will notice."

His eyes darted around nervously. "But –"

"I'm sorry; I thought you were a Gryffindor. I guess the Hat just put you there because of your family."

Ron immediately walked towards the security desk, head held very high. We scurried after him.

"That was a really low blow, Harry," Hermione hissed.

"I know. It was brilliant." I smirked at my own cleverness.

"There's no way the guard will actually think he's his brother."

I chuckled, raising a hand towards the guard. "Confundus."

The guard looked up suddenly, as if confused about where he was. He squinted at Ron's badge. "Percy?"

"Yes," Ron said stiffly. "Of course."

"Kind of early for you to be here, isn't it?"

"Well, you know me" – Ron let out a nervous chuckle – "I believe in punctuality. It's really important to me."

"Right, yes. I remember that," the guard said. "Go on, then."

Ron nodded, stomping away with us at his heels. He asked, "What just happened?"

"You witnessed me being right," I told him.

"Harry confunded the guard" – Hermione paused for a moment – "Actually, how did you do that? We aren't supposed to do magic over the summer."

"They can only catch you if you use a wand."

"You can do wandless magic?" Ron asked.

I said, "I can do lots of things. I'm Harry Potter."

"Of course you are," Hermione grumbled. "The Department of Mysteries is downstairs."

I beamed, slapping her on the back. "I knew you would eventually admit to working there."

"I'm not! There's a map right there." The cloak rustled as she flung her arm up to point.

"Sure it is, Hermione."

"It's right there. Just look at it. Ron, can you tell him?"

Ron frowned. "I don't see it anywhere."

"I'm pointing right at it," she cried.

"You're invisible," he said.

Hermione blinked, earlier frustration fallen off her face. "Oh. Right. I am. We should probably just go downstairs."

"…So if we just mark every door that we try," Hermione explained, "we'll know where to go when the room spins again."

"We can't mark the doors!" I cried, arms flung out so that the invisibility cloak temporarily obscured the walls. "People will know we've been here."

Hermione pouted. "It would be a magical mark, obviously."

"Like that would make any difference. This is the Department of Mysteries. They solve magical mysteries all the time."

Ron frowned, mumbling, "Actually, I think they're named that because –"

"Silence. Hermione, you're being particularly unhelpful tonight. Do you want us to be caught?"

She pursed her lips in obvious guilt. "Of course not."

"Are you sure? I know we're breaking into your workplace –"

"It isn't!"

"–but that doesn't change the fact that you're supposed to be pretending to be my friend, and selling out your friends to your coworkers is not okay."

"I…" Hermione appeared lost, for once unable to come up with a clever lie. "I'm not even sure where to start in disputing that."

"It's not worth it, 'Mione," Ron said. "So, uh, what are we supposed to do if we don't mark the doors, then?"

I flung my invisibility cloak over my shoulders. "Obviously, we open all the doors and never close them."

"Oh. Alright then," Ron said, turning the nearest doorknob like the Gryffindor he is.

We split up to open more doors in a shorter time. Behind the first was some sort of planetarium, and the second contained something which resembled Lucius's hair. The third room held a pillar and curtain. Almost immediately, I decided that I hated it. It had been a while since that had happened, and I was resisting the urge to slam the door shut when Ron spoke.

"It's kind of weird that they don't let people see prophecies about them, if you ask me."

I shrugged, still glaring at the curtain. I could feel a headache forming. "They might let you, actually. I never checked."

"You mean that we didn't need to break into the Ministry, at all?" Hermione asked, clearly unhappy about something. Perhaps she'd stumbled onto one of Dumbledore's secret and no doubt insidious projects.

"I mean that I never checked. The way I see it, asking would do absolutely no good. If we don't get caught, it doesn't matter. If it's not against the rules and we get caught, then we'll all have a good laugh about it. If it is against the rules, however, then we made the right decision and asking someone would have just put them on guard."

Hermione frowned. "I still think –"

"Bloody hell, are those brains?" Ron yelped.

"Enough, Ron. We'll get you one on the way out." I opened another door, absentmindedly casting a stunner on the creature inside.

"And we'll grab Harry a heart," Hermione said.

I furrowed my brow. "Why would I need one of those?"

"…Harry, you just made that joke," Hermione said, looking distressed. "It hasn't even been a minute."

Seeing that I'd lost all interest in responding, the girl sighed and opened another door.

"What are the chances that the right door would be the very last one we tried?" I said.

Hermione frowned. "Hm. Twelve doors. So, one out of twelve times one out of eleven, so that's –"

"I wasn't actually asking. I was just complaining," I clarified.

Ron took that as his cue. With a tired grin, he said, "Good. I can't wait to be out of here."

"I don't know what you've got to whine about," I said. "I'm the one who nearly drowned."

His Weasley face reddened. "You dragged me under, too."

"Only because you grabbed me."

"I was trying to save you!"

"Well clearly you weren't doing a very good job of it."

Hermione snapped, "Stop fighting. We need to get the prophecy before the morning rush comes in and my parents realize that I snuck out."

"Fine," I muttered.

We stepped through the doorway, and looked up. And up. And over. And over some more at the seemingly endless rows of shelves holding silvery orbs.

"Bloody hell," Ron said.

"How are we supposed to find anything in this?" Hermione fretted. "I don't see a directory anywhere."

"It might be alphabetical," Ron said.

"Possibly, but by what? Would it be under Trelawney? Or Potter? Or maybe it landed under Voldemort's name, and I don't even know what that is…"

"Riddle," I said.

"How do you know that?"

"I killed him."

"That – okay, fine, that still doesn't change the fact that there are thousands of orbs and several possible organizational structures…"

Ron laid a hand on her shoulder, laughing. "Hermione."

"Y-yeah?" she asked, sounding somewhat dazed.

"Calm down. We'll find it," Ron said. "…Probably."

"Right," she mumbled, flushing with embarrassment at her panic.

I declared, "I'm already far ahead of you both."

I raised a hand towards the looming rack of prophecies and said, "Accio the prophecy about Harry Potter."

All was silent for a moment. Then there was a sudden crash and a guttural voice. Then another and another. Then a thousand extra crashes and voices joined them as an entire shelf hit the floor. At that point, I spotted my summoned orb flying through the shelf nearest us just as the shelf to its left fell atop it.

I grabbed Hermione's arm, she grabbed Ron, and we all ran for it – my prophecy following close behind.

"Why did you do that?" Hermione cried.

"We didn't have time to figure out how they were organized," I said, pulling her and Ron into the hallway outside of the department.

"But you could have used a point-me spell or something."

"I'm not sure if I can do that wandlessly," I said. Also, I hadn't thought of it, but that didn't seem worthy of mention.

Hermione gripped my hand painfully, fingernails digging into my skin as we waited in the elevator. "You didn't even check! You just destroyed the entire roomful of prophecies."

"It was wicked," Ron whispered.

"Thank you," I said. We stepped from the elevator, confunding the night guard in passing.

"No, don't you dare encourage him, Ron," Hermione said. "This is not alright. We broke several laws tonight and destroyed irreplaceable objects, and we are going to be in so much trouble."

"Not if you don't tell your boss," I said.

She growled low in her throat. "I don't have a boss."

"Then we'll be fine," I announced, pulling the broom from my pocket and unshrinking it.

"…but, due to good fortune and quick-thinking, we were able to escape with both the prophecy and no property damage," Hermione finished, breathing a bit heavily to make up for the last several minutes of talking.

Her parents exchanged a glance. With a small nod at her husband, Mrs. Granger turned to Hermione. "Sweetie, if you have a boyfriend, you know you can tell us, right? We won't be upset."

Mr. Granger coughed.

"Well, maybe a little," she amended.

Hermione blushed, sputtering, "I…I – I do not have a boyfriend. Harry doesn't even understand what being a girl means, and Ron is…not my boyfriend. I was telling the truth, really. These things happen in the Wizarding World."

"Is this what you do at school every year?" Mr. Granger asked, scowling.

"Well, not all the time," Hermione muttered. "Usually we study."

Ron said, "Well, you do."

She elbowed him in the ribs. "But something like this happens every couple of months."

"It's slightly less often for the other houses," I said.

Hermione asked, "How do you even know that?"

"Ginevra talks to them. Merlin knows why." Also, I used to be a Slytherin, which is more about ancient secrets and politics.

"So all that tripe about a prophecy was true?" Mr. Granger asked.

"Yes," Hermione said. "I wouldn't have said it if it was a lie."

I was completely certain that was a lie.

"And you believe whatever that crystal ball says?" he continued, gesturing towards the misty orb in my hands.

"Divination is a perfectly respectable subject," I declared.

Hermione said, "We have differing opinions on that. What matters is that Voldemort thinks that the crystal ball is right, and it may possess information that will help us against him."

Mr. Granger nodded sharply. "Has it, then?"

Hermione blinked. "What?"

"Given good information."

"What does it say, hon?" Mrs. Granger prodded.

"Um…we haven't exactly heard it yet," Hermione said. "The wind was loud, and it was dark out, and Harry kept shouting that he was going to drop it."

"Ron needed to be prepared so that he could catch it."

Ron turned red, presumably with pride this time.

"We can listen to it now, I suppose," Hermione mumbled. She glanced from her parents to Ron and me, then back again.

I said, "That was a cue for you two to leave."

"No it wasn't!" Hermione cried.

"Really? Because I was pretty sure this time."

"I think you were right," Ron said.

"Thank you Ron."

"Just play it, please?" – after a moment, she repeated testily – "Please?"

"You never told me how to do it," I said.

"Fine. Tap it –"

"Of course you would know how because you're a secret –"

She raised a hand to silence me, apparently not wanting her parents to know that their lives were a carefully constructed lie to support a deeply undercover Ministry worker. "Tap it with your wand."

"Would that count as doing magic over the summer?" Ron asked.

"I'm not sure," Hermione said.

"Ron, since you brought up such an important point, I award you the honor of playing the prophecy."

"I'm not that dumb, mate."

"I don't carry my wand over the summer. So either you do it, or all of our deaths are your fault."

"Your deaths?" Mrs. Granger asked weakly.

"Harry has a dark sense of humor," Hermione said.

"Actually, I never joke. I mean everything I say," I said.

Ron paled. "You what?"

"Kidding! I was kidding." I wasn't kidding.

Ron shakily tapped the orb with his wand, and it split into two halves, a wispy Sybil Trelawney peering at us from between them. She spoke in a deep, gravelly voice.

"The one with the power to vanquish the Dark Lord approaches ... born to those who have thrice defied him, born as the seventh month dies."

I nodded. I knew that part.

"... and the Dark Lord will mark him as his equal, but he will be his own undoing ... and either must die at the hand of the other for neither can live while the other survives ... the one with the power to vanquish the Dark Lord will be born as the seventh month dies ..."

"That's great!" Ron said.

"What do you mean?" Mr. Granger asked, frowning.

"It says that You-Know-Who gets rid of himself. And Hermione thought we had to do it, too!"

Mrs. Granger said, "Um, sweetie…"

At the same moment, Hermione said, "Ron, that isn't actually what it…"

The two shared a look, and, with a tip of the elder's head, Hermione continued, "That's not what it says. It says that 'he shall be his own undoing.' It never says that 'he' is Voldemort. It could just be Harry messing his own life up because he was acting like Harry. Or it might mean that Voldemort was his own undoing because he marked Harry as his equal, which means that Harry still has to be the one who defeats him."

I growled in frustration. The prophecy might also consider us the same person (because we are). In that case, either of us is completely free to kill the other. "What's the point of a prophecy if it doesn't tell you exactly what to do?"

"No point, really," Ron said.

"I think I hate Divination now."

"I've hated it since third year," Ron said.

"Usually I would say that all school topics have merit if you actually put in effort and try to learn," Hermione said, "but Divination is just terrible."

"Like Muggle Studies," I agreed.

"Harry!" she shouted.

"It's not bigoted if I'm talking about the class. Right, Mr. Granger?"

The man smiled. "I don't know enough about the topic to say."

"See, your Dad agrees with me. Why do you have to be such a terrible daughter, Hermione? Sneaking out of the house, lying, arguing with your poor father?"

Hermione pouted, and Mrs. Granger said, "You're not a terrible daughter, but we are going to have a talk about this."

"After my friends leave, right?" Hermione asked, eyes wide and deceptively innocent.

"Alright," her mother agreed.

Hermione glanced in our direction, with some emotion or another.

"Well, I can tell when I'm not wanted," I said. "Come on, Ron."

Ron said, "Uh, I don't think she really wants us to go."

"No, she was pretty obvious about it. Besides, Ginevra has probably just finished playing herself and you during breakfast. She's no doubt exhausted."

Ron winced. "Right, yeah. Bye, 'Mione."

"Bye Ron," she sighed, staring miserably at her parents. Maybe Ron was right after all. There's a first time for everything, I suppose.

I was under attack.

"Get off of me!" I cried, shaking my body in the hopes of dislodging the arms wrapped around it. But her grip was too solid.

"Nice to see you, too, Harry," Hermione said and released me from her hug.

I rubbed at my arms in an attempt to disrupt the continued sensation of touch. Warily, I glanced around Hermione's bedroom. Her mother had shown a similar tendency towards unwarranted bodily assaults.

"Do you have to do that every time?" I demanded. "It's only been a week."

She pinched her lips, head raised haughtily. "I was worried about you, you prat. You didn't say goodbye, you didn't take your trunk, and – when I tried to send an owl – it got confused and kept circling back. Then, I sent a letter to Ron and found out that he hadn't seen you since you left to visit me. Where have you been?"

"In the trunk."

"…Sorry?"

I opened it, gesturing towards the comfortable apartment within. "It's magically expanded."

"You…you've been living in a trunk?" she said faintly.

"It seemed like a sound investment, since property values keep rising."

"How do you eat?"

"Dobby."

The house-elf appeared, only to pop away again at my dismissive gesture.

"So you're stealing, then," she said flatly.

"Dobby is stealing. I am accepting gifts," I said.

Hermione shook her head and then peered into the compartment. "I just assumed you'd be with Ron. If you'd told me that you really didn't have any place to go, you could have stayed here."

I chuckled. "That's what I've been doing."

"In the guest room, Harry!" Her hair fluffed up like a cat's coat.

I frowned, glancing outside her bedroom door. "I don't know if I would like that. Your guest room's pretty small."

She raised an eyebrow. "You've been living in a trunk."

"Which is still bigger than your guest room."

Hermione began to pace, footfalls heavy on the hardwood floor. My trunk shuddered with every step, and my bookcase rattled within. Suddenly, the girl exclaimed, "Is it smoking?"

"Well, I have to air the potions fumes sometime, or they start to build up."

I've tried to remedy the situation through spells, but that tends to set off some of the more delicate brews. I still hadn't fixed the hole in the floor from my last attempt at Felix Felicis.

"There is absolutely no way this is safe," Hermione muttered.

"You're thinking like a Muggle, Hermione," I said as I descended once again into my new home.

"I am not!" she said. "Also, there's nothing wrong with that!"

"Sure there isn't, Hermione" – I chuckled, waving my hand as the roof latched behind me – "Sure there isn't."

I hopped out of my trunk, squinting at the unexpected sunlight. I squawked indignantly, "Did you move me?"

Hermione smirked. "No."

I was clearly at the Burrow, and Ron waved at me from beside her. "You liar! Now, I'll have to ward the trunk against your meddling."

"You can't ward something against being picked up, Harry," she sighed.

I gestured sharply with my hand, missing my wand terribly. "Really? Have you ever tried? You can't just assume that everything you read in books is true, you know. Sometimes the authors are scheming. Like you."

Hermione rolled her eyes. "Yes. I'm sure. Now, Ron has something to tell you. Right, Ron?"

"Uh, right," he said. "Mate, you really shouldn't be living in a trunk."

"Don't let Hermione bully you," I said. "Your home is perfectly nice."

"It's not a shoebox!" he snapped. "Besides, this isn't like that. My uncle had one of those trunks, but the charms broke when he and all his things were inside…They had to bury him in it."

"Do you see, Harry?" Hermione said. "This is very dangerous, and you shouldn't risk it."

"Ron's uncle was probably doing something stupid –"

"Yeah, hanging around in a trunk," Ron muttered.

"–and messed up the charms. Besides, I spent half my money on this trunk, and it's non-refundable."

Hermione twisted her lips, skeptically asking, "Half your money?"

"My thousand galleons from the Triwizard Tournament."

"That's kind of a weird way to put it, isn't it?" Ron asked. "I mean, it's like you're not thinking about your parents' money at all. Weren't the Potters rich?"

I paused. "It never occurred to me to check. I'll have to inquire about this."

I retreated into my trunk to write a letter, Ron and Hermione's horrified protests following me inside.

Dear Dumbledore,

I must confess that your scheme to steal my parents' money was brilliant. Now that I have discovered it, however, I request that you return my inheritance in full. If you do this, quickly and without complaint, I shall return the hostages unharmed.

Love,

Harry Potter

Professor Dumbledore smiled benignly down at me, and I fought the urge to cower behind Ron, Hermione, or possibly Ginevra. That smile always seemed to precede a terrible loss during my time as a Dark Lord.

"I wish you had asked, earlier, my boy," he said shaking his head wearily. "I'm afraid I'd quite forgotten to give you your vault key."

Ha! Forgotten? Despite the occasional, hopeful rumor of senility, Dumbledore couldn't forget something if he had a team of Obliviators following him at all times. I twisted my face into some amalgamation of innocence, not allowing it to slip even as Ron's twitching mouth betrayed his restrained laughter. "Of course, sir. I'm just glad to have it now, really."

"Good, good. If I may be so bold, how have you been buying your books and school supplies before now?"

"The Dursleys helped me out." Not willingly, mind you, but – since they lack Ron's Gryffindor courage – they would never be so foolish as to complain about my thievery.

Dumbledore's smile grew, and it appeared as if he'd just been hit by a cheering charm. "Yes, of course. I'm glad to hear you're so close to your family. Love is wonderful, you know."

"Yes, it burns things. I recall," I said.

Ron said, "What?"

I frowned. "Don't make me order Ginevra to silence you again."

"Ah, yes," Dumbledore chuckled. "I had meant to ask. Who were the hostages you mentioned?"

"Well, I mostly added that part to speed things along."

Ron cleared his throat, and I hurriedly added, "Hermione's idea, naturally. But, in a pinch, I could always use my friends."

Albus Dumbledore's eyes twinkled. "You always can, I dare say. Now, I'm afraid I have to go attend a meeting. Good day to you all."

To my surprise, he then headed straight for the Weasleys' house, humming merrily all the way.

Hermione asked, "What sort of meeting could he mean?"

"Some weird group that's been hanging around all summer," Ron said, wrinkling his nose.

"The Order of the Phoenix," Ginevra said.

I scowled, and Hermione's eyes lit up. She said, "Oh! I read about them. They were a small group that opposed Voldemort during the War. Everybody thought that Dumbledore was a member, but no one could ever prove it. Apparently, they're very skilled in urban combat."

Ron shrugged. "I guess so. Mostly they just sit around and eat Mum's sandwiches."

Chapter 13: HP vs Dolores Umbridge (Pt 3)

Seventh Horcrux

Chapter 7: Harry Potter vs. Dolores Umbridge (Pt. 3)

It took some time to dislodge Fawkes from Umbridge and clean up the freshly-spilled cauldron of Felix Felicis. The whole process would have gone a lot quicker if the Inquisitorial Squad hadn't just stood by and laughed. At least our traitor, Edgecomb, had the excuse that she was trying to hide her pimply face.

Umbridge adjusted her badly-shredded robes. "Hem hem."

"Yes, Professor?" I asked, distracted by the phoenix digging its claws into my shoulder and hissing at Umbridge. Apparently, he liked her.

Umbridge said, "Would you like to explain, Mr. Potter, just what all of this is?"

"We weren't learning anything in class, so we decided to form a study group. We call it the Defense Against the Dark Arts Study Group for Not Failing Our OWLs. Or the DADASGNF OWLs for short."

"Most of us call it the DA," Ginevra chirped.

"Unfortunately, that's as many letters as they can remember," I said.

Umbridge smiled tightly. "I suppose I'm not surprised at this behavior from you, Mr. Potter. As I'm certain you know, this subversive organization goes against several of the High Inquisitor's proclamations."

"Are you talking about yourself in the third person? I think that's the first sign of insanity," I said. I never do that when talking about myself. Or any of my other selves.

She continued, lips pinched, "…nor has it gained my approval…"

"According to school rules, it has," I interrupted. "As your apprentice and therefore teaching assistant, I am allowed to schedule additional classes for struggling students. Which, due to your complete dearth of talent in the realm of teaching, is all of them."

Umbridge gave a breathy little sigh. "Mr. Potter, regardless of your worrying delusions, you are not my apprentice."

"See, that's where you're wrong. Hermione?"

Hermione glanced up from her place hunched over the library's table. "There are actually several passages in the Hogwarts Rulebook which ensure that professors cannot overburden their charges with out-of-class work. This includes writing assignments, such as those served during your detentions."

"We passed the allowable point for a normal student months ago. In fact, I warned you that, if you gave me one more detention, I would be your apprentice. And then you did that. According to magic, that's consent."

"It is!" Ginevra enthusiastically agreed.

"That's completely ridiculous," Umbridge hissed. "You can't just create an apprenticeship without anyone knowing about it."

"No, of course not," I said. "That would be silly. However, everyone here hates you because you're an awful person. I tried to fix that, but, upon consultation with my companions, I have come to the baffling conclusion that you just don't care. 'Everyone' luckily includes Albus Dumbledore, who signed off on my apprenticeship."

Umbridge giggled, a deeply unsettling sound. "So the headmaster is involved in this illicit –"

I growled in annoyance, Fawkes echoing the noise. "No, it's me. Entirely me. Dumbledore will not steal my credit for this."

Ginevra laid a hand on my empty, and therefore less dangerous, shoulder. "Also, it's technically on the up-and-up, since Harry's your apprentice, and you haven't forbidden him from doing anything."

Umbridge's eyes gleamed, reminding me uncomfortably of Dumbledore. "In that case, you're no longer allowed to lead this little group of yours."

"As my master, you have the right to give me that order," I acknowledged. "And I have the right to pass on leadership to my apprentice, Neville Longbottom. Neville?"

Neville grinned. "I'd be glad to. Thanks for the vote of confidence."

I shrugged. "We've only got a month left before OWLs. How much damage could you do?"

"An idiot like that," Malfoy drawled. "You'd be surprised."

Neville raised his sword menacingly. I gestured for him to stand down. "Don't worry. He's only saying that because he's in love with Hermione."

Hermione and Malfoy squawked in indignation, then glared at each other for daring to do so at the same moment. Young love: I'll never understand it.

Umbridge's face slowly grew pink as we ignored her. She cried, "I'm disbanding this group this instant!"

"You can do that," I said. "The real question is: Would that be a good decision for you?"

After the sixth time, it seemed that Umbridge had finally come to recognize when I'd set a trap for her. She raised her eyebrows. "What, precisely, does that mean?"

"You are also technically a member of the DADASGNF OWLs. I'm still not entirely sure how Ginevra got your signature, but it's on the same contract as Edgecomb's," I said.

Edgecomb peaked up at us, revealing the word SNEAK written across her face. "I'm sorry. I didn't mean to…"

I raised a hand to silence her. "Therefore, your betrayal will be met with the same consequences, along with whatever Hermione has added during this conversation…"

"I'm thirteen punishments in, but I'm still working on the loss of magic clause," Hermione said. Ron handed her another inkwell, and she stopped writing for a moment to smile at him.

"You really expect me to believe that a fifteen-year-old girl managed this?"

"Sixteen," Ginevra corrected.

"I learned a great deal from the Goblet of Fire. Also, the Ravenclaws helped," Hermione said. Edgecomb whimpered, burying her face in her hands.

Ron said, "I think she's done with the squib part."

Umbridge paled. "I shall not allow –"

"I would be careful about what you say next," I advised her. "I'm not certain what Hermione's definition of 'betrayal' is, but I have no doubt that the results will be disturbing to us all."

"She's bloody scary, sometimes," Ron said, a goofy grin on his face.

Umbridge finally acknowledged defeat. "How do I get out of it?"

"There's no way out once your signature is on the contract, since it was signed with your blood," Hermione said thoughtfully. "Of course, it only has so extensive of a range."

Umbridge's nose wrinkled as if she'd tasted something sour. "Fine. I'll leave Hogwarts."

"Oh, it's not that small. You'd need to go to the Continent, at least" – Fawkes squawked angrily, and Hermione continued – "Although I might have overpowered it a bit. Staying out of Europe would be safest."

I smirked. "You should probably go. There's a clause which allows Hermione to activate the betrayal clause at any time, and she, like Dumbledore, hates you."

Fawkes accompanied Umbridge on her way out, screeching and scratching all the way.

After the Inquisitorial Squad departed and Edgecomb returned to the Hospital Wing, there was no longer a need to present a united front.

I shooed Hermione towards the library. "Hermione, I'm your best friend and I support you regardless of who you are, but that would be a lot easier if you would stop lying to yourself and everyone around you."

Hermione laughed. "I'm presuming this isn't what it sounds like."

I sighed. Clearly I was going to have to spell this out for her. "You maimed Edgecomb."

"It'll go away when she leaves Hogwarts," she muttered. "Besides, she deserves it. Bloody sneak."

"Hermione, they used Veritaserum on her. And they only managed that because she'd gone to the Hospital Wing after Neville tried to use magic again," I said. His stubbornness would be the death of us all.

Hermione stuttered, "Sh-she what? I mean, I didn't realize that the contract would have that effect unless the betrayal was willing. I just wanted –"

"Vengeance," I finished gravely. "You wanted vengeance for an act that hadn't even been committed yet."

"I didn't want people to betray us," Hermione said.

I shook my head, sighing, "See, that would have made sense if you'd actually told people about the betrayal clause. Then, it would serve as a deterrent. But you didn't tell anyone. I know; I checked with Ginevra."

Hermione began sniffling. She always does this, hoping to distract from her misdeeds.

I said, "I think that you didn't tell anyone because you wanted someone to betray us just so you could hurt them without consequence."

"You're wrong. I'll fix Edgecomb," Hermione said. "It shouldn't be too hard to reverse-engineer…"

"No, see, this is the problem. You're trying to convince everyone that you're a good person, but you're just innately malicious. Rather than fight your inner evil, you're ignoring it. That isn't healthy."

Hermione ran away crying, still clinging to her denial.

Ron waited for Neville to wave him on with his sword before nervously approaching me. "Uh, mate, I was just with Hermione. She seems pretty upset. She says you think she's evil or something?"

"No," I said.

He grinned, speaking before I was finished. "Well, that's a relief 'cause –"

"I know she's evil."

Ron gaped. "Hermione's not evil. She's actually pretty nice."

"She usually curbs her urges," I said, "and that's admirable. But she's getting worse with time. If she keeps denying it, then people are going to get hurt. Important people. People who aren't Edgecomb."

"But she follows a lot of rules, way more than us, and she's really upset when we break them," Ron said.

I shook my head. "When Hermione does break rules, however, she has no distinction between stupid ones and basic human decency. Remember when she wanted to kidnap and interrogate those Slytherins? Or when she tortured that reporter?"

"…No."

Clearly, Hermione had already obliviated him, covering up her crimes by erasing all evidence that they'd ever occurred. Of course, she'd been wise enough not to try such tampering with me.

"Well, those things happened. Hermione usually follows the rules because she doesn't have a moral code."

"She does! She cares about House Elves and stuff," Ron said.

I snorted. "Ron, the House Elves don't care about themselves. They're perfectly happy where they are, but Hermione is interfering because of some weird Muggle rule against slavery. Someone who understood moral nuance would realize that the most humane thing is to leave them be."

Ron wrinkled his Weasley face, grumbling, "Are you doing that thing where you say something and then you argue about it and give lots of evidence. Then, later, it turns out you're just wrong and you made up all the evidence?"

"No. I'm definitely right this time," I assured him.

Ron seemed very confused and somewhat deflated. I set a hand on his shoulder, motioning Neville to do the same. He used the sword, but that was close enough.

I smiled. "Look, we all have innate parts of our nature that we may only work around. Hermione is evil, you are a Weasley, and I am so good at lying that I sometimes fool myself."

Ron's mouth fell open. "You know about that?"

"Well, yeah, people have mentioned it. I can't cite any specific examples, but I presume it's happened."

"Ron's not a werewolf!" Ginevra shouted.

Right, yes, I had often lied to cover for Ron's lycanthropy.

I continued, "The point is that Hermione, when not guided by rules, automatically does things that are incredibly cruel without even noticing."

Ron shook his head. "Right, I should probably go talk to Hermione. She'll explain why you're wrong. At least, I hope she will."

"You shouldn't think something just because she tells you to," I said.

Ron should think things because I tell him to.

The next morning, Hermione still wasn't speaking to me, stubbornly eating breakfast at the very edge of the Gryffindor table.

"She can't last for long," Ginevra assured me. "We're her only friends. The Ravenclaws are scared of her now, you've prejudiced her enough against Hufflepuffs that she's never gotten to know any, and the only Slytherin she talks to is Malfoy. The social isolation should get to her in a couple of days."

Ron said, "I wish she would talk to one of us, at least. I didn't even call her evil, really."

"She's talking to me," Neville muttered into his eggs.

Luna hummed in agreement. "She's talking to me, too, I think. But she just said that Fudge didn't have an army of Heliopaths because they don't exist. So now I'm not talking to her until she or Ron apologizes."

"Why should I have to apologize?" Ron grumbled.

I sighed, shaking my head. "Eventually, Hermione will realize that we're doing this for her own good. For now, we'll simply have to put up with her stubbornness."

An angry barn owl descended upon our table with the morning rush, clicking its beak at Luna, who smiled and gave it a knut. Ron said, "I thought your Da owned the Quibbler."

"He does," Ginevra said as Luna carefully removed the paper from the owl's claws.

"Then why do you get the Prophet?"

"Most of it isn't true," Luna said, "but it's good for a laugh."

I nodded. "Right, that makes sense. Also, I've been meaning to ask: Why are you at the Gryffindor table?"

"Hermione says that it's not against any rules" – she glanced at the Prophet – "Oh, it's about us."

Ginevra grinned, hopping a little in her seat, and took a swig of pumpkin juice.

Ron grabbed the paper from Luna, revealing the headline: Umbridge attacks apprentice; flees country; resigns in disgrace.

A very Weasley frown crossed Ron's face. "Ginny, what did you do?"

"I apologized," Ginevra said.

"You what?" I said.

"I sent a letter for you to Rita Skeeter, apologizing on the behalf of Dumbledore for lying to us all and Hermione for trying to kill her."

"Without my permission?"

"Well, I figured that, if it didn't work, we could always say that I was a minion of one of your political enemies," she said. "It did, though, so I'm your publicist now! Of course, I did have to make a few concessions to get this article through. You have to do an interview this summer, and Skeeter gets to attend our wedding."

I glanced up from the paper. "What was that last demand?"

She beamed. "You've got an interview."

"Right," I muttered. "I can do that."

Neville whistled, looking at his own edition. "There was a break-in at the Ministry, and it doesn't even get mentioned until the third page."

"Apparently, it was a total bloodbath," one of the other Gryffindors chimed in. "Probably Sirius Black's fault."

"Oh, right!" Ginevra said. "I forgot to mention that I also apologized to the Prophet's editor."

I frowned. "Huh, I don't think I've done anything to him."

"He didn't, either," she said. "He was really flattered."

I stalked about the Malfoy parlor, sneering down at the brunette kneeling on the floor. "Bellatrix, you have once again failed me. Not only were you unable to find the Prophecy, but you were also incredibly unsubtle about your search. Now everyone knows of your mission."

Bellatrix pouted. "But, my lord, I didn't leave a single witness."

"Yes, I'm aware that you killed everyone in the building" – I massaged my brow – "I'm glad you had a nice time, but that is, again, not what I asked you to do. Luckily, you can redeem yourself."

"I'll do anything, my lord," she sighed.

"The old fool is already interviewing for next year's Defense professor."

Her eyes shone as I explained my plan.

"Dumbledore is interviewing for the DADA position," I said.

Ginevra's eyes widened. "Really? I didn't hear about that at all."

I smirked. "Yes, well, I had a dream about it."

Down the table, Hermione huffed into her textbook. This was the closest she'd come to talking to me in the past few days, so I considered it progress.

I continued, "I asked Snape this morning, and he assures me that it's true. I can only assume that the dream was prophetic and that my diligent study of Divination has finally paid off."

"So you're gonna go see who the next person who wants to kill us is?" Ron asked.

I stared at him.

He shrugged. "Well, it's true. Isn't it?"

Neville frowned. "If Dumbledore hires a professor now, then does that mean that he'll be gone by this June or this time next year? Or can he go for most of next year, too?"

I shrugged. "Magic is mysterious."

"While you're visiting Dumbledore, you should probably get official backing for the DA, too," Ginevra said. "Now that Umbridge is gone, we don't have any professor sponsoring us."

"Technically, I'm still a teaching assistant until Dumbledore hires a new professor," I said. "I might be able to get something more permanent, though. Ginevra, what's the current password to Dumbledore's office?"

Ginevra grinned. "Chocolate Frogs."

The blonde witch skipped up the revolving staircase, oblivious to my invisible presence behind her. It was difficult to say if this was the result of her incompetence or my immense skill. Probably both.

I sank to the floor of Dumbledore's office, leaning against a wall as the witch flounce into a chair with an obnoxious giggle. Claws digging into my shoulder, Fawkes also watched. His beady, black eyes seemed hungry as it darted between Dumbledore and the blonde.

"Oh, I'm so glad to meet you, Headmaster," the witch gushed.

Dumbledore's eyes twinkled. "Congratulations, Miss Farfelu."

"Tee-hee," Farfelu giggled. "Why are you congratulating me?"

Dumbledore clapped his hand together, beaming. "You're our newest Defense Against the Dark Arts professor, of course!"

"I…I don't, tee-hee, understand. I thought this was an interview."

"I don't believe that's necessary, dear girl. You seem perfectly suited to the position."

Farfelu pouted. "But I'm not sure about taking it. I mean, I haven't even talked to my husband yet, and he's wanted the position forever."

"Tell him to apply next year," Dumbledore said brightly. "Although, if I recall correctly, your resume mentioned that you were unmarried."

"I am. He's…He's, um, tee-hee…dead."

Dumbledore nodded. "I see. Encourage him to apply anyway. We have quite a few ghosts on staff, and – as my dear friend Cuthbert Binns always says – being dead is no reason to stop living."

"I'll, tee-hee, tell him that," the blonde murmured. "Still, I'm not sure I'm interested."

Dumbledore manipulated his features into a crestfallen expression. "I'm very sorry, my dear, but I'm afraid you've already agreed."

Farfelu leapt to her feet, whipping out her wand to point it at Dumbledore's nose. The old man watched calmly, still smiling.

"What did you do?" Farfelu growled and then, after a short pause, added, "Tee-hee."

"It was in the contract that you signed earlier, you see."

The blonde sat down with a huff. "The one that I had to sign to get the interview?"

Dumbledore nodded. "Indeed. I'm afraid it had a clause that you would be the DADA teacher for a full school year, with your continued employment based upon my discretion."

"But that wasn't in the contract at all, tee-hee!" she cried.

"It was invisible and written in the margins. But I'm afraid that it is magically binding."

At that moment, Fawkes darted off my shoulder and out of the invisibility cloak, headed straight for Dumbledore's face. Dumbledore absentmindedly set up a shield. He turned to his new professor, explaining, "He's really very fond of me."

The blonde pushed back her chair with a loud screech, though that only garnered the phoenix's attention. It gave her a hard stare, then turned back to pecking at Dumbledore's shield.

"This is all so very sudden," she said. "I'd hoped to get a tour of the castle first and maybe meet some of my future colleagues."

"No worries, you can do all of that now that you've been hired," Dumbledore reassured her. "Severus would gladly show you –"

"I don't suppose you could spare Sybill Trelawney? I've been dying to meet her since I was just a girl, you know."

Farfelu batted her eyes, the gesture sending a familiar shiver down my spine. It was identical to a flirting Bellatrix. I should know. With all the love potions she's fed me, I've spent a cumulative fifteen minutes infatuated with her.

Dumbledore glanced in my direction but said, "Yes, I believe Sybill's class should be ending shortly. Do you need an escort?"

"Tee-hee! No, I'm fine, thanks." Farfelu skipped out of Dumbledore's office and down the revolving staircase.

Dumbledore turned his attention towards my corner of the room, quirking an eyebrow. "Mr. Potter, don't you have Potions at this time?"

I whipped off the cloak, grumbling, "I don't know why I should attend if Snape doesn't."

"He is covering for Umbridge's Defense classes and cannot attend," Dumbledore said.

"I offered to take over the class," I said. "Permanently, if possible."

"I applaud your ambition, but I cannot hire a professor who has yet to take his OWLs."

I stood up and approached his desk. "I'll have taken my OWLs by the time next term starts."

"I would prefer it if you took your NEWTs as well," Dumbledore said, obviously devising requirements solely to keep me from my dream. "Also, I've already chosen a professor for next term."

I frowned. "Oh, come on, she's obviously a Death Eater."

"Why would you think that?" Dumbledore had to raise his voice over Fawkes's increasingly furious attacks on his shield.

"Well, you hired her, for a start," I said. "You always hire Death Eaters: Quirrel, Moody, Hagrid, Lupin –"

Dumbledore said, "Professor Lupin was not a Death Eater."

I snorted. "Werewolf Rights was a founding principle of the Death Eaters. All the werewolves worked for Voldemort."

"I can assure you that Professor Lupin worked for me."

"He was probably a spy then," I said.

In fact, I'm pretty sure he was. I had plenty of spies in the Order of the Phoenix.

"And you ignored my Light professors, such as Gilderoy Lockhart," Dumbledore said.

I stared at him gravely, and even the phoenix slowed its assault. "I think we both know that there won't be any more Lockharts. He was the bravest man I ever knew."

Dumbledore sighed, smoothing down his magenta robes. "Nevertheless, I suspect that Professor Farfelu will be a wonderful teacher and may even be willing to continue your apprenticeship –"

There was a whoosh of green flame from Dumbledore's fireplace, and Severus's enormous head dourly regarded us. "Headmaster, it appears that Farfelu has abducted your Divination professor and fled the castle."

Dumbledore paused for a moment. "You're certain that someone else did not abduct both of them?"

Severus raised an eyebrow. "I presume you're going to fire her."

"I suppose that would be wise…Yes, I believe I will." Dumbledore stroked his beard to comfort himself.

Severus climbed out of the fireplace, the soot hidden by his black robes. "I suspected this would happen. I didn't warn you because I didn't actually expect you to hire her. After all, she was obviously a Death Eater."

"See?" I said. "Even Snape agrees with me, and he would know: He's a Death Eater, too."

Severus snorted. "She tried to curse a student for walking beside her, and she bears an uncanny resemblance to Bellatrix Lestrange."

"To be fair," I said. "Most wizards are related. They could just be cousins or something."

"Also, her only reference was Lucius Malfoy," he continued.

"He was quite complimentary," Dumbledore said.

Severus watched Dumbledore with a calculating glint in his eyes. "Since I am now the only applicant –"

"I applied," I said.

"The only applicant…" Severus ground out. "I presume that you will finally allow me to assume my desired position?"

Dumbledore said, "Well, I suppose. I don't know where I'll get another Potions professor, though. There aren't many Potions Masters around, these days."

There was no danger of Severus breaking the curse because he was a terrible teacher. Still, I refused to admit defeat. "I could teach Potions."

"Potter, you're failing the class," Severus drawled.

"Right, and that's not your fault at all," I said.

"You still haven't taken your OWLs," Dumbledore reminded me.

"Fine," I spat. "Divination, then. I'm great at Divination. I saw all of this coming."

"…and then they just kicked me out without even listening to what I had to say. For all they knew, I could have given a prophecy that said how to defeat the Dark Lord, but I wasn't going to tell them because they were total gits…Hermione? You're not being a very good friend right now. You've got the listening part right, I suppose, but you haven't tried to comfort me at all…I've been talking for ten minutes."

It would be a lot easier to have this conversation if she hadn't barricaded herself inside Myrtle's loo. Hermione's muffled voice called, "Go away, Harry."

"See, you're talking now, but you're also being unnecessarily cruel."

Hermione groaned.

I said, "Oh, you're still upset about the 'evil' thing. It's been over a week. I assumed you'd gotten over that by now…Hey! I know something that'll cheer you up: Voldemort kidnapped Trelawney!"

"Why would that make me happy? I'm not evil."

I idly twirled my wand between my fingers, grinning. "No, you're not thinking this through. Voldemort captured her because she's a seer. He doesn't know her like we do. He thinks she's good. He'll listen to everything she says."

More silence. I thought, perhaps wishfully, that it was a thoughtful one. "Remember what happened during my third Divination class? It'll be a lot like that, but Voldemort won't be throwing stunners. I figure he'll take out half his ranks in a week."

I had to strain to hear Hermione through the door. "Harry, why do you think that Voldemort wants Trelawney because she's a seer? Why do you think he'll listen to her at all?"

"I had a dream about it."

She snorted derisively. "Honestly, Harry, you can't assume something just because…Wait, did this dream happen before or after Trelawney was kidnapped?"

"A few days before," I said.

Hermione hummed, and I could hear her getting to her feet. "This dream involved Voldemort?"

"Yeah. Most of my dreams do," I said.

She spoke slowly. "In these dreams, are you an invisible observer or –"

"No, I'm very involved. Actually, come to think of it, I might be Voldemort" – after a moment, I clarified – "in those dreams."

I could hear Hermione's building excitement. "And this is new, isn't it? Just the last year or so?"

"They're a lot more vivid," I admitted.

The door swung open, then, and Hermione emerged with a Cheshire-cat grin. She hurried past me, shouting, "I'll be in the library!"

I smirked. I knew the Trelawney thing would cheer her up.

The Room of Requirement was quiet with only Neville, Ginevra, Ron, and I inside. There was no gaggle of practicing students, no Hermione making lesson plans, and the latest Felix Felicis brewing disaster had been mopped up a few hours earlier. Even Fawkes had returned to Dumbledore, content to watch and periodically attack him. The room darkened to match our somber mood.

"The last DA meeting," Ginevra sighed. "It's been a good run."

Neville said, "We can always do it again next year."

Ginevra giggled. "Maybe we won't have to. Our new Defense professor might actually be good!"

We all burst out into laughter, of which mine was the loudest and longest-lasting. The Room of Requirement's walls shivered merrily along with us, and we watched it fondly.

Ron said, "It's kinda pathetic that it's just us here. We could have gotten a bunch more people to come if Hermione had let me get Firewhiskey from the twins."

Ginevra sent a Stinging Hex towards Ron. Neville was technically in the way, but he automatically twisted to avoid it. Ron glared at the younger Weasley. "What was that for?"

The redhead beamed. "Hermione isn't here, so I'm covering for her."

Neville smiled, ducking his head slightly as if to hide it. "It's funny. Before, she wasn't talking to you guys because you called her evil. Now, she's not talking to anyone because she's in the middle of another project."

"Everything's back to normal, then," I said happily. "Except that Umbridge is gone. So it's better."

Ginevra said, "Can you believe we actually saved her life?"

"Wait, what?"

"Well, all the Defense professors either die or leave. We made sure that she left, so that means that she didn't die," she explained.

Neville's face darkened. "She probably would have died in the Bellatrix Lestrange attack."

That incident had actually been pretty tame for Bellatrix. Only three students were sent to the Hospital Wing.

Ron grinned. "Heh. I guess we beat the curse, then."

A dreamy voice spoke from behind us. "Actually, we were the curse."

"Luna!" I cried. "How have you been?"

"Thinking," Luna said. "I'm pretty sure I've figured out your secret."

I laughed condescendingly but quickly erected a Silencing Charm. Obliviating one person is difficult enough. I didn't need to add Neville and his insane dodging abilities into the mix. "Go on, then."

Luna took a deep breath before saying, "When you were a little baby, did Voldemort accidentally put part of his soul in you, causing both of your souls to merge, so that you have all of his memories and will never acknowledge that you're not the same person because it's too central to your self-image?"

I blinked in shock, unable to properly address the pure insanity that is Luna Lovegood. "I…no! Why would you ever think that?"

"Well, it's just that you talk about doing terrible things a lot, but then you rarely do."

"You're wrong again," I said.

Luna pouted, crossing her arms. "I give up, then."

I sighed. If I didn't give her some sort of explanation, she might think up something closer to the truth. Or, worse, talk to Hermione about it. "Why can't I just be an eccentric genius, who is otherwise perfectly normal?"

She hummed thoughtfully. "Well, I suppose you could be, but that doesn't seem very narratively satisfying."

"Luna, this isn't a story," I said.

Luna said, "Oh. Right. I forget sometimes."

Chuckling, I slung an arm around her shoulders and canceled the Silencing Charm. The others were waiting by the door, and the dummies waved goodbye as we closed it behind us. With that, our end-of-the-year meeting of the DADASGNF OWLs came to a close.

I waved one of Dobby's cakes in front of my best minion, careful to keep it hidden from Pince's suspicious gaze. The frizzy hair parted to reveal a sniffing nose, then wide, dark rimmed eyes. Hermione Granger looked like something from the Forbidden Forest.

"Hermione," I said. "You still understand English, right?"

Hermione eyes brightened, and she indignantly said, "Of course I understand English!"

"Good, I'd begun to fear you'd gone feral," I said.

Hermione rolled her eyes, breaking a chunk of cake from the slice in front of her. She dropped it onto her tongue with a blissful sigh. I frowned. "Have you eaten at all in the past few days?"

"Of course," she said.

"Really? Are you sure you haven't forgotten? Because that seems like something you would do. You've either been here or taking your OWLs for the past week, and I haven't seen you in the Great Hall…"

Hermione smiled. "Careful there, Harry, I might start to think you cared."

"Oh, thank you for the warning," I said. I wouldn't want to give her a false impression, after all. Honesty is very important in a master/minion relationship.

"Really, though, I have eaten. The House Elves have been sneaking in food after hours."

"…and you've been sleeping here. Yes, I'm aware" – I waved off her explanations – "I admire your dedication to never leaving the library. I have similar feelings about Hogwarts. But I do need my invisibility cloak back."

Hermione rifled through her bag in search of the starry fabric. "Any particular reason?"

"Primarily that it's mine," I said.

"…Right," she murmured, handing it to me.

Hermione turned back to her open book, rapidly flipping pages. I glanced around the nearly-abandoned library and said, "The Leaving Feast is starting soon. I presume you're coming?"

"Can't. Madame Pince doesn't loan out library books this late in the year."

I scowled. "You have to come! It's the last feast of the year."

"Yes, that is what 'Leaving Feast' means." Hermione flipped another page.

"All of our friends are going to be there."

"Uh-huh."

I said, "I'm giving a speech."

Hermione ignored me.

"If you don't put down the book and come with me, I'll tell Pince that you've been eating in the library."

Her head jerked up in horror. "But, Harry –"

"So that's a yes then?"

"But I haven't figured out what's wrong with you," she whined.

"People have been trying to figure that one out for decades," I said. "You're not going to manage it in one night."

"But, your visions –"

"Can remain a mystery until September," I said. "Unless you want me to plant crumbs between some of the books' pages?"

With a pout, Hermione shut the tome. "You're evil."

I smirked. "Well, that makes two of us, then."

She chased me across the castle, hexing all the way. Still, they were only mildly painful, and we ended our flight in the Great Hall.

Dumbledore was finishing his end of term speech when Hermione and I arrived.

"Before we fill our bellies, Harry Potter would like to say a few words."

I nodded towards Dumbledore and strode to the front of the room. Smiling at the crowd's uneasy murmuring, I said, "Hello, fellow students. As you all know, Umbridge apprenticed me earlier in the school year. Since she has fled the continent, that leaves me in charge of her former duties. I've already gotten rid of the educational decrees…"

The students cheered.

"…and reinstated Professor Snape…"

A few groans responded to that statement. I had been reluctant to rehire the man, but, though there were many legitimate reasons to fire him, being a werewolf was not one of them.

"Now, it has come time to destroy the last of Umbridge's unwelcome additions to this school" – in the crowd, Draco Malfoy scowled – "I would like to officially disband the Inquisitorial Squad."

The silver I's on the members' robes poofed away in a cloud of smoke while the rest of the school celebrated.

"I have more to say," I said. "You see, I have a few last-minute points to announce…"

Albus Dumbledore had set a dangerous precedent.

"…Some students decided to go above and beyond the requirements of their professors. When faced with a terrible teacher, they chose to learn outside of the classroom. Under the tutelage of me, Harry Potter, they have learned much and are likely the only students who didn't fail their OWLs this year. As such, I would like to award a hundred points to each student who participated in my study group."

The Ravenclaw, Hufflepuff, and Gryffindor hourglasses filled with gems. I smirked. "I believe this calls for a change of decorations. Congratulations, Ravenclaw!"

With a flick of my wand, the room turned bronze and blue. There was cheering at all four tables. Presumably, this is because the Slytherins knew exactly what we were going to do to them after they won. Of course, the Weasley twins were conspicuously absent from the Gryffindor table, so the Slytherins' relief would be short-lived.

I cleared my throat. "One last thing."

The Hall immediately quieted down as I turned to the Slytherin table.

"That, Draco, is how you cheat."

"Is this place any safer, Madame Trelawney?" I asked, pacing the length of our latest headquarters. This only took about thirty seconds, and I stepped on no less than three followers along the way.

Trelawney raised a hand to her cheek. "Oh, it is difficult, you know, to call upon the whispers of fate. She is a fickle thing."

Lucius anxiously looked out the window. "My lord, I don't think that this location is particularly safe."

I waved away his concerns. "Nonsense. Our oracle will inform us of any danger."

He said, "My home has far greater protections. If we had remained there –"

"We all would have died. Trelawney saw the Grim in her teacup. We've been over this."

Trelawney danced around my followers, who lounged on the floor, and placed her crystal ball on a roughly-constructed, wooden table. She peered into its depths, humming thoughtfully. We leaned forward, awaiting her visions.

Her voice was high and breathy. "Yes. Yes, this shall do…"

Bellatrix dove for the only bed, hissing and hexing until everyone else had scrambled to the floor. Nagini had formed some sort of nest in the fireplace. Lucius summoned a House Elf to "make the place livable." Hagrid watched, bemused, from a gargantuan chair.

Trelawney's eyes were round and wide behind her glasses. She whispered, "At least, for now."

Groaning, my Death Eaters settled in for a night at Hagrid's hut.

A/N: In this chapter, Harry asserts that Remus, a werewolf, must be a Death Eater. One might assume that this is because Harry is insane (a not unreasonable assumption and one well worth keeping in mind for future events). However, it's worth noting that the Order of the Phoenix made this exact same assumption in canon.

I assume it went something like this:

"Hey, guys, I hear we've got a spy!"

"That's incredibly dangerous to us all. We'd better use Veritaserum or Legilimency to find out who he or she is so that we can stop future, traitorous deeds."

"Yeah, I guess we could do that. Or we could just stop telling Remus things."

"That is a sound and perfectly reasonable plan. How could it ever go wrong?"

...and then the plot of Harry Potter happened. Whoops.

Chapter 14: HP vs Love (Pt 1)

This chapter exemplifies a reoccurring theme in Seventh Horcrux:

People who aren't as sneaky as they think they are but are getting away with it anyway.

Seventh Horcrux

Chapter 8: Harry Potter vs. Love (Pt. 1)

Pushing through the late August crowd of students and their families, I made my way into the Leaky Cauldron. With a nod to Tom, I headed upstairs to one of its private rooms.

"Harry!" Ginevra tried to tackle me with a hug, but, thankfully, I got a shield up just in time. I edged around her, greeting Rita Skeeter as I settled into a chair.

The reporter smiled a shark-like grin, and, with a snap of her fingers, her Quick Quotes Quill started scribbling on the sheet beside her. "Good to see you. I was starting to wonder if I ever would. Your stunning, young –"

"Publicist," Ginevra said helpfully.

Skeeter's smile widened. "…publicist has been putting me off for months. So tell me, Harry, just where have you been all summer? The wizarding public is dying to know."

I said, "I've been living in a magically-expanded trunk."

Rita Skeeter gasped, and even her quill paused. "Oh, I wouldn't keep doing that. My coworker's father owned one of those. The charms broke when he was inside, and they had to bury him in it. Two-hundred people attended the funeral, social event of the season. I, of course, reported."

"I found another downside last June," I said.

Skeeter leaned forward eagerly, saying, "Really? Go on, don't keep us in suspense."

"Hermione mailed me to France. At least, I think it was France. Do they speak French anywhere else?"

Skeeter tapped her chin with a sharp, red-painted fingernail. "Well, there's Canada."

"No, that doesn't seem right," I muttered.

"Some parts of Africa, too," Ginevra said.

"That might have been it," I said. "Anyway, I tried to get back to Britain by crossing the nearest body of water, but that just put me in Asia. So, now, I've been to all seven continents…At least, presuming that was Africa, and I've made a lot of friends who I never intend to see again. But the weird part is that I don't feel like I've learned anything."

"Not every adventure has a moral lesson. Just the best ones," Ginevra said.

I shook my head. "No, I mean: I didn't learn anything. I didn't learn the Oriental mystic arts or any new languages. And I still don't know what the Americans do. This trip was completely pointless."

We all spent a moment contemplating that much of our lifetime is taken up by useless and often futile endeavors. At least, that's what I was thinking about. I don't know about Ginevra and Skeeter.

Skeeter broke the silence. "Why exactly do you think that Hermione Granger shipped you abroad? Was it a lover's spat? A shocking and unprovoked attack upon Wizarding Britain's savior? A clear sign of her growing mental instability?"

"That went really well," Ginevra enthused, nearly bouncing in her seat. "I think Skeeter likes you. I didn't even know she could do that!"

I smirked. "Of course. After all, I am a charming, adventurous, brilliant, yet completely normal Hogwarts student. What's not to like?"

She gave me a goofy smile, staring at my face for altogether too long. I said, "You can leave now."

Ginevra jumped a bit, cheeks reddened in embarrassment. "Okay. Dumbledore should be picking you up in twenty minutes."

This was the first time I'd heard of such a thing. What was the old man trying to pull now?

"He isn't trying to pull anything, I don't think," Ginevra said. "Apparently, he needs you to help him. Something about the Potions professorship."

"He's actually hiring me?" I did do pretty well on my OWLs.

Ginevra shook her head. "No, he specifically mentioned that you weren't getting a teaching post. He said it like six times."

"When did this happen?" I asked.

"July. I sent you an owl."

"I probably would have been in Antarctica, at the time," I muttered. "Did the owl ever come back?"

Dumbledore and I strolled into Slughorn's home. It was torn apart, with spell gouges in the walls, burn marks on the ceiling, and a fair bit of blood by the door. A bit like the Gryffindor common room, come to think of it.

Slughorn was in the corner, pretending to be a chair. He used to do that all the time when I was in school. Apparently, he got in trouble for it. I can't imagine why; everyone thought it was funny.

"Horace," Dumbledore said. "I know it's you. You haven't changed the pattern on the upholstery in fifty years."

Slughorn transformed back into himself, though he took up nearly as much space as the armchair had. "Ah, Albus. Good to see you, good to see you."

"You as well," he said. "And may I introduce young Harry Potter?"

Slughorn's eyes lit up, and he grabbed my hand in both his. "Wonderful meeting you, Mr. Potter. I've heard you like Quidditch. I happen to be personally acquainted with a Puddlemere United Chaser. Perhaps you would like to meet him?"

"I may be interested, in the future. I'm very busy, you know."

"Of course, of course," he chuckled. "Defeating Dark Lords and all that. Now, if that will be all, I really must be going."

Dumbledore looked around the ruined home. "I'm afraid I rarely have time for social visits lately. I'm here to offer you your old position. There's no place safer than Hogwarts –"

"Tell that to the Perks girl," I muttered.

"–and you're clearly in hiding from Voldemort."

Slughorn chortled. "Yes, well, you see…I'm actually not. I was hiding from you. An old acquaintance of mine mentioned in passing that you might be paying me this visit."

Dumbledore heaved a heavy sigh, as if he actually felt bad about manipulating everyone around him. "I am terribly sorry to interrupt your retirement, but I'm afraid we're desperate. If you don't take the post, Harry Potter will. And he's not allowed in the Potions room unsupervised."

"To be fair," I said, "no one died, and I was the one who reconstructed the floor."

Slughorn frowned, shifting his great weight from foot to foot. "Won't the Ministry give you someone, if no one else applies?"

"I think I would prefer Harry," Dumbledore admitted. "Our last replacement was less than exemplary."

"Yes, I remember hearing about that. Umbridge was such a sweet, little Hufflepuff when I taught her. Never would have imagined she'd attack the Boy-Who-Lived. Of course, the Boy-Who-Lived wasn't born then, so I suppose that's a reasonable oversight."

Slughorn chuckled to himself, ending in a nervous cough upon realizing that no one had joined him. "Surely there's someone else who can take the post…"

Dumbledore sighed. "I fear that young people nowadays just don't have the patience for potions. Hogwarts hasn't graduated a Potions Master in over a decade."

I rolled my eyes. "Can't imagine why."

Dumbledore set a hand on Slughorn's shoulder. "Horace, do not force me to hire Harry Potter."

"I'm looking forward to being the Head of Slytherin," I said.

"That isn't a requirement," Dumbledore assured him. "Severus is still on staff."

Huh. I assumed it was position-based. Why else would the Potions classroom be in the dungeons, even though it lacks a proper ventilation system and most of the fumes end up in the Slytherin common room?

Dumbledore's eyes twinkled with…Were those tears? "You are our last hope."

It seemed that I would not be on staff for the coming school year.

Hermione Granger stormed into my train car.

"I did not mail you to Algeria!" she shouted.

Well, that was quite the hello. "Really? Then who did, Hermione?"

"I don't know," Hermione said.

"I'm certain that we've established your knowledge of everything."

"Nobody knows everything, Harry."

I raised an eyebrow, and, with a huff, Hermione said, "Fine. You've been brewing several volatile potions in an enclosed space without proper ventilation. Maybe they combined oddly. Or maybe you sent yourself there with accidental magic. Or maybe your Felix Felicis attempts are finally coming to fruition, leaving you with horrible luck. Or maybe the charms on your trunk broke and this whole thing is a dying dream!"

"That last one doesn't seem very likely," I said.

Hermione's shoulders slumped, no doubt downtrodden by my criticism, and she buried her face in her hands. She trembled with laughter, finally gasping, "Honestly, Harry, you meet with Rita for an hour and somehow end up with two pages on how awful I am. How does that even happen?"

"It arose organically," I said. Hermione's growing evil is a topic of shared interest between myself and Skeeter, since I am the girl's best friend and she is an ongoing victim.

Hermione shook her head, still giggling. "Right, fine. Apparently Skeeter has decided that slandering me is okay as long as it's a direct quote. The other page is about your love life, by the way, and I don't even think you have one of those."

I settled back onto my seat. "After I defeated that dark lord in Albania, I might have been engaged to a nobleman's daughter. Or he might have been yelling at me because that dark lord was one of the good ones. I'm not sure. I never learned the language."

Ginevra walked in, flanked by Ron. "You probably shouldn't go to that country for a while, just to be on the safe side."

"I dunno about that. Is she a good-looking bird?" Ron asked. Hermione and Ginevra both leaned over to smack his arm, although Ginevra then apologized to her for the presumption.

Hermione smiled and asked, "How was your summer, Ginny?"

"Great! I think I've finally found the family Dark Magic!"

Ron gaped. "WHAT?!"

I beamed. "I always knew the Weasleys were hiding something."

"Well, it isn't the Weasley stuff, actually. I'm still working on that," Ginevra demurred. "But I did find out the Prewett Dark Magic."

"When?" Ron asked.

"Mum and I were in the kitchen" – she smiled pityingly at her older brother – "You shouldn't feel bad about it. I'm pretty sure it's only passed on to daughters."

"Ginevra, focus!" I snapped.

She nodded, and, cruelly drawing out her words, said, "It's a love potion."

"Oh." I felt rather disappointed.

Ron seemed caught between relief that he hadn't missed out on any great inheritance and misery that his family had once again failed to do anything impressive. "Well, is it any good?"

"I think so," Ginevra said, "Mum dosed Dad when they were in school, and he's still in love with her."

"You do realize that we're missing the Start-of-Term Feast, right?" I said. "I mean, I know that you love the library, but this is getting ridiculous. It'll still be here in the morning."

Hermione's voice drifted out of the stacks. "Oh, hush."

Finally, with a triumphant cry (which she hurriedly quieted), she emerged with an open book resting in her hands. "I've developed a theory for what's going on with your dreams."

"You mean outside of the fact that I'm a seer?" I asked, lounging against the bookcase.

Hermione set down her book with a thud. "I suspect that you have some sort of magical connection with Voldemort. Presumably, this is centered around your scar or the use of your blood during the Unum Corpus ritual –"

"The what?"

"The ritual Voldemort used to revive himself," Hermione said. "I looked it up over the summer. It's not Dark Magic."

I frowned. "Wait, do you mean that it's not that obscure, or that it's not evil. Because I'm never sure if you're using the correct definition or not nowadays –"

Hermione pursed her lips, snapping, "Harry. Not the time. Anyway, you clearly have some sort of magical bond. Well, either that or you're soul mates. But, if that were the case, the distance and hostility almost certainly would have killed you both by now. Regardless, I've figured out how to deal with the situation…"

She flipped the book around and jabbed its title with her finger. "Occlumency."

"I'm afraid that's not going to work for me."

She blinked. "What?"

"I'm just not any good at it. You're supposed to clear your mind and stop having emotions. But I'm always thinking because I'm a genius, and I sometimes have these sudden and inexplicable flashes of rage."

I'd tried to get Severus to train me with Occlumency, prior to my time as Harry Potter. I didn't realize, then, how bad he was at teaching.

Hermione leaned against a bookcase, looking rather pale. "But I spent the whole summer learning the techniques. I've been preparing lesson plans…"

I shrugged. "You probably should have asked me first."

She grabbed her wand from her pocket, shaking it at me. "You were in Algeria!"

"Well, not all the time. I was in Russia for a while. That isn't particularly far, I don't think."

She shook her head. "You should learn Occlumency, though. It protects your mind from foreign intrusion, and these visions are bound to get worse with time."

I chuckled. "I'll be fine."

Hermione glared into my eyes and, with a determined tilt of the chin, said, "Legilimens."

A moment later, we were roused from our mental match when Hermione's wand fell, with a clatter, to the floor. She grabbed her eyes, hissing in pain. I dove for her wand before following suit.

"For Merlin's sake, Hermione, why did you do that?!" I shouted. Thankfully, Pince was downstairs, feasting with everyone else.

"I wanted to prove how serious the situation was," she said. "What did you do, anyway?"

"Ah, yes. I neglected to mention that, while I'm ill-suited for Occlumency, I have the single-minded attitude, nosiness and disregard for others' privacy that are essential to a Legilimens. Therefore, when someone uses Legilimency on me, I use Legilimency back on them, but harder."

I waited for comprehension to dawn in her eyes, but they remained as dull as a Weasley's. Sighing, I continued, "I am reading your mind, while you are reading me reading your mind. You're technically reading your own mind, so you think you're just thinking. Then, you try to read my mind. It all goes in a loop until you either notice the problem or are forced to break eye contact for some other reason."

"Wait, was that what you guys were doing?" Ron asked. "I just thought you were having the most brilliant staring contest ever."

Hermione sputtered, "R-Ron? When did you get here?"

The redhead contorted his face into something resembling thoughtfulness. "An hour ago, I guess?"

"We arrived at 10:24 if you want to be precise about it," Ginevra said. "The Feast ended ages ago, so we borrowed the cloak from Harry's trunk and went looking for you."

Well, that explained our pained eyes. Hermione sighed. "Three hours and we still haven't figured out how to stop your dreams."

"Wait. Where did you get the idea that I wanted them to stop?"

Hermione held out her hand for her wand, which I reluctantly returned. "Well, I presumed you wouldn't want to see whatever atrocities Voldemort gets up to in his spare time."

"I don't think I've seen anything that bad yet," I said. "The Death Eaters spend most of their time squabbling about who gets the bed or who is Voldemort's most loyal servant or who Nagini is allowed to eat. Besides, they give me all sorts of useful information."

Hermione frowned. "But Voldemort could show you something specific, to trick you, and then you might act right into his hand."

"Hermione, that's deviously brilliant," I said.

Hermione breathed a soft sigh, no doubt thrilled that her plan had gone over so well. "Then you understand why you need to protect your mind from –"

"We should do that!"

Lucius looked miserable in the old Black manor, tearing at his hair with his silver hand. Several House Elves were scuttling around him, lifting his robes so that they avoided the grimy floors and leaving a trail of polish and shine in their wake.

The blond muttered, "Disgusting. At least Hagrid's wasn't booby-trapped…"

Nagini had similarly chosen to escape the filth by hiding beneath my robes. She poked her head outside to announce, "I'm hungry. I haven't eaten in days."

Right, yes. This is why I'd never kept a pet when I was in school. I mean, I haven't fed the Basilisk in…Actually, I don't think I ever fed the Basilisk. I should do something about that when I conquer Wizarding Britain.

I stroked Nagini's head, smiling fondly upon her. "Maybe, if you stop trying to devour Sirius every time he turns into a grim, he'll feed you his House Elf."

Kreacher was a wretched thing and unable to properly perform its housecleaning duties. Insane, too, if its insistence that Sirius Black was a blood traitor was anything to go by.

Of course, that might have been the result of its unfortunate former owner.

Sirius, Severus, and Hagrid approached us from another room. Those three were very close, presumably having bonded over their shared occupation as spies. When the deceased Madame Black's portrait started screeching, the trio agreed to use their charm and cunning to explain our position.

Sirius grinned, giving a jaunty wave to our assembled group. Nagini tasted the air at his entrance but stilled at my stern look.

"The old bat'll shut up for a while. We'll be better off if you talk to her though" – Severus elbowed him in the ribs, and Sirius smoothly added – "My lord."

"I can do that," I said. "Have you discovered what got her so upset?"

Severus said, "Since Black was so deeply undercover, his mother was under the false impression that he was a blood traitor."

I chuckled. "I see. How incredibly embarrassing for her. After all, you are my right hand man."

"Yes," Severus said in his usual, flat tone. "Madame Black now understands that and is very apologetic."

Sirius gave a barking laugh. "We can still take down the wall if you'd like, m'lord. Air the place out."

Severus sent a stinging hex at him, and Sirius – turning into a giant, black dog – tackled him to the floor. We watched, amused at their antics.

The two inner circle members had a rather tumultuous relationship. One moment, they were throwing curses and shouting obscenities. The next, they were whispering in each other's ears and sneaking off to a private corner of Hagrid's hut.

Young love: I would never understand it.

I wandered into the kitchen, Lucius trailing behind me like a proper minion. There, Trelawney was comfortably ensconced at a little table. She seemed happily oblivious to the dust powdering the air and settling in her teacup.

Lucius was evidently horrified.

"Have you had any new premonitions?" I asked the prophetess.

"It is difficult," Trelawney whispered.

"We can always return to my manor," Lucius said.

"So very difficult to see…"

He looked at me beseechingly. "My beautiful, clean manor."

Trelawney's head snapped up, and she peered at us through dust-caked glasses. "Have you prepared me a room, someplace where I might rest my third eye?"

"Of course," I said. "You can have the whole third floor, if you like."

Trelawney beamed, dropping the teacup in her excitement. "I have seen it…YES! This shall be a most fortunate place for us."

"I've been thinking the same thing," I said.

Trelawney said, "You have the Gift, I dare say, or are at least wise enough to understand a true prediction when you hear one."

I gave her a thin, pleased smile. Of course, Nagini's decision to emerge from my robes and curl around my neck at that moment lent a somewhat unsettling effect to the gesture.

I told the snake, "We'll be staying here from now on."

She squeezed my neck to demonstrate her displeasure. "I cannot hunt unicorns here."

I winced, tugging her free to set her on the floor. "You've been killing unicorns?!"

"I would like to," Nagini admitted, "but I haven't found one yet."

"Oh. That's alright then."

"And there were so many tasty creatures in the Forest…" she hissed wistfully.

I scowled down at her. "I'm not going to starve you."

"Then this will be a good nest," Nagini decided, slithering towards the drawing room. "It's dark, and it smells like you."

I heard a distant explosion, and the portrait began wailing again. With a nod towards Trelawney, I left to deal with Severus and Sirius's latest lover's spat.

Dumbledore had sent a summons, expecting me to walk right into his grasp. But I was not such a fool. I crept invisibly into Dumbledore's office, wand ready, and surveyed the environment in a way that would make Moody proud. Then, I exclaimed, "What is wrong with your hand?!"

Dumbledore smiled and waved with his blackened, shriveled hand. "Ah, Harry. I had forgotten that you missed the Welcome Feast. I'm afraid that I've contracted an illness that has negatively affected my hand."

"Dragon Pox? That's really been going around lately," I said.

"…Possibly," Dumbledore said.

"You should get that checked out," I said.

"I'll certainly take that into advisement," Dumbledore said, which is his way of saying that he'll completely ignore it. "Don't you have a class, at the moment?"

"It's just Defense. Snape'll fail me no matter what I do."

For once, I could go into a year of schooling unconcerned about losing my future post. After all, I already knew that Snape was a horrible teacher.

"I wish you two would work through your differences," Dumbledore said, "and I didn't intend for you to skip class."

If he had really meant that, he would have put it in the note. I asked, "Why did you want to see me, anyway? I haven't done anything yet."

"I hoped to show you a memory," he said. "Do you know what a pensieve is?"

I stumbled out of the pensieve, Dumbledore serenely following. Fawkes, of course, was watching us.

Dumbledore asked, "Did you notice anything interesting about the Gaunts, Harry?"

I channeled my inner Ron. "No, not really. Except for the fact that they're dirty, evil Slytherins."

"You do have a very extreme view of Slytherins," Dumbledore noted with a frown. "Perhaps you recognized that they, like Voldemort, are descendants of Slytherin?"

"Well, I guess. They seemed pretty awful, though. Probably a Squib line," I muttered.

"Yes…I'm afraid that Merope –"

I blinked. "Who?"

"The girl in the grey dress."

"Right," I said.

"She was Voldemort's mother." Dumbledore peered into my eyes, waiting for a response.

"Wasn't Voldemort an orphan?" – I paused for a moment – "I think he mentioned that during a monologue."

"He still had parents, if only for a short time," Dumbledore said. "Though his parents were not as brave and good as yours."

I nodded. It occurred to me that I should probably find out the Potters' first names before people realized that I didn't know them. This resolution had long been hampered by how little I cared.

Dumbledore prattled on about my family history, though I found it difficult to feign interest. No matter what Dumbledore may have thought, I'd just turned seventy years old. I'd moved on.

Sure, I had some family issues in my youth, but I killed them and got over it.

We walked down the hall quickly, eager to be away from History of Magic. Fawkes, as usual, peered down at us from a protruding gargoyle that wasn't there yesterday. We were well into the walk to our next class by the time Hermione had properly packed up her bag and latched it.

Ron turned to her. "Uh, 'Mione, I know there isn't really anything better to do during History of Magic, but why were you watching Malfoy the whole time?"

"He was watching us first," Hermione said. "He has been all week. It's suspicious."

Ron shrugged. "I dunno. That sounds pretty normal for him."

I said, "Between Malfoy and Fawkes, I assume I'm under surveillance at all times."

"Well, yes, but he's more persistent about it. Quieter, too. He hasn't called me a Mudblood at all, lately."

"And you're starting to miss it?" I guessed.

Hermione glared at me. "No, I am not! It's just odd. He goes missing for hours at a time."

"How do you know that?" Ron asked. "We've only got a couple of classes with him."

"Ginevra told me…and he hasn't said anything about his father or his money all year!"

Hermione was flushed and breathing heavily, impassioned. Ron stared at her, red-faced from our short yet brisk walk.

I said, "He's probably still shaken up from that thing with the twins last year."

"Apparently, the Slytherin common room still smells like smoke," Ron said.

Hermione hissed, "Malfoy is up to something."

I shrugged. "I'm not too concerned, really."

Hermione stormed off. It wasn't a particularly effective exit, however, because she was still going in the same direction as us. Also, I sat next to her in our next class, which was starting in about three minutes.

I frowned. "I wonder if she wants to rekindle her romance with Malfoy…"

Ron whipped around. "WHAT?!"

"You didn't know?" I asked. "Except, no, I suppose you wouldn't. They kept it pretty quiet, after all."

"Bloody hell, mate, what are you talking about?"

"Back in Fourth Year, Hermione and Malfoy dated for a while. Things got pretty intense, but then they realized that they were from two different worlds and could never be together…Draco was devastated."

"Y-you're taking the piss out of me, right?" Ron stuttered.

I shook my head gravely. "No, Ron. Even I can't make this stuff up!"

Later that evening, we were lounging in the Gryffindor common room, doing homework, when Ron stumbled over with a giggling witch hanging off his arm.

"So Lavender and me are dating, now," Ron said. "We're really into each other."

I tried my best to ignore the situation, while Ginevra was hurriedly taking notes. Hermione pursed her lips. "Really? How did you two get together?"

"Uh, I dunno. It happened pretty naturally, I guess. We have a lot in common, y'know."

"I think he's just so brave for facing his transformations every month," Lavender cooed. "Aren't you, Won-Won?"

Ron laughed nervously. "It's not like I do that much, really. I'm just a guy…who turns into a werewolf sometimes."

Lavender kissed him on the nose. "So humble, too!"

I said, "I, for one, am glad that Ron is finally being open about his werewolf status after so many years of hiding."

"I'm not a…uh, hiding. Anymore."

Lavender squeezed his arm, beaming.

Hermione raised an eyebrow. "Yes, I really admire your honesty."

"…Thanks," Ron said.

Lavender glanced at Hermione, whispered something in Ron's ear, and burst into giggles. Ron mostly looked uncomfortable, though he happily accepted her offer to snog.

In an unrelated incident, Hermione started grumbling about something (presumably Malfoy) and snapped her quill in half.

Chapter 17: HP vs Himself (Pt 1)

Seventh Horcrux

Chapter 9: Harry Potter vs. Himself (Pt. 1)

The delivery owl drifted into Hermione's kitchen, buoyed by a summer breeze. While she offered it a knut and a bit of toast, I snagged the Prophet.

"That's rather rude, you know," she huffed as the owl flew away.

I glanced up from the newspaper, frowning. "You're the one who asked me to come outside for meals."

Hermione pouted. "But you stole my paper."

"You also asked me to keep up with the news," I said.

With a groan and a muttered, "Too early for this," Hermione turned her attention to her breakfast.

I hummed thoughtfully as I skimmed the front page. "Looks like Dumbledore died."

Hermione gasped, dropping her toast, and I continued, "Some sort of wasting sickness. Probably Dragon Pox. I told him to get that arm checked out."

"Is there a funeral?" she asked, all sniffles and crocodile tears.

"Doesn't say" – I spotted several familiar names in the article below it – "Death Eaters have taken over the Ministry, too."

Hermione's eyes widened, all attempts at grief forgotten. "WHAT?!"

"It doesn't explicitly say that, but it's pretty heavily implied," I assured her. "Also, Snape's the new headmaster."

Hermione pushed her plate away. "Oh, Harry, this is awful."

"I know! Slytherin will win the House Cup for sure," I said.

"Not that!" she snapped. "Voldemort has control over Hogwarts. He hates Muggleborns –"

"Allegedly."

"– and he despises you, and I'm your Muggleborn best friend. There's absolutely no way we can return to Hogwarts. How are we supposed to prepare for our NEWTs?"

I blinked. "Really? That's your problem with this? I assumed you were talking about the murder."

She buried her face in her hands and seemed to be having some difficulty breathing.

"It'll be fine," I reassured her. "I just turned seventeen. We grab Ron, go on the run, and finish the task Dumbledore set for us."

Hermione peeked upwards, eyes alight with curiosity. "Task?"

"There are five items necessary to defeat Voldemort," I said. "We have to gather them all and use them in a Dark ritual."

It was time to collect my Horcruxes. Once Voldemort fell, who knew what would happen to them?

I continued, "They include the Gaunt ring, Voldemort's pet snake, Ravenclaw's Diadem, Hufflepuff's Cup –"

"Those are lost artifacts, Harry," Hermione said. "People have been searching for them for generations."

I snorted. "Voldemort found them. How hard can it be? We don't even have to find the last one. He's currently wearing Slytherin's locket."

"So we'll need to get it off of his neck, then?" Hermione asked.

"Not a problem," I said cheerfully. "If he has it, then it'll be there when we need it. He's actually helping us by keeping it close because he is arrogant and insane."

She rolled her eyes, but smiled. "That makes thing easier for us, I suppose. We'll need someplace to stay –"

"Way ahead of you," I assured her.

"Not the trunk," she said.

"No, not that. It's better than the trunk. I'll tell you about it once we've grabbed Ron."

I brought my trunk out from the guest bedroom. I held a hand out to Hermione, but she refused it with a tight smile. "You go ahead. I need to pack and have a talk with my parents."

With a quick wave, I apparated to the Weasleys' hovel.

Arriving at the Burrow, Hermione carefully stepped around my trunk, which was spewing a pearly mist. Soon, I would need to add fairy wings to my cauldron of Felix Felicis.

"Hi guys," Hermione said, nodding to Ron, Ginevra, and me before turning to the man beside us. "Nice to see you again, Professor."

Lupin smiled at her. "I'm not a professor anymore. Please, call me Remus."

Something deep inside Hermione exploded at the thought of addressing a former authority figure as an equal, and she devolved into stuttered protests.

Ron interjected, "Lupin's working with the werewolves now."

Lupin sighed. "They're not working with me, though. Not after all the Werewolf Rights legislation that just got pushed through."

I snorted. "It's about time, really. They were first suggested decades ago."

Lupin said, "I'm surprised you all know so much about this."

"Long-standing interest," I said.

"My ex-girlfriend was really into it." I think Ron was blushing, although it was hard to tell with the potions fumes obscuring his face.

With an arrogant tilt to her chin, Hermione declared, "Everyone should care about oppression."

"I don't actually care that much. I just like spending time with Harry," Ginevra clarified.

"That's horrible," I said. "Your brother is a werewolf."

"I am not!" Ron wailed.

Lupin slinked away during the ensuing argument. The whole incident was terribly upsetting. I was almost certain that Ron had come to terms with his lycanthropy. Giving up, I turned to Hermione. "You aren't going to believe this. Dumbledore got us presents."

I was right. Hermione didn't believe me at all. "Harry," she said delicately. "Dumbledore is dead."

I beamed. "I know. I think I like him better this way. He never did this when he was alive."

Hermione paled. "Um…"

"He left us stuff," Ron said. "Like, inheritance."

"Us?" Hermione said.

"The three of us. Not Ginevra," I said. "Hardly surprising. He's never liked her."

Ginevra pouted. "Really? I don't think we ever met."

"That explains it, then," I said.

Hermione frowned. "I've barely spoken to him, myself. Have you, Ron?"

Ron shook his head.

Her brow wrinkled. "What did he give us?"

"You got a book" – I handed it to her – "because everyone knows you like reading, Ron got Dumbledore's wand, and I got a signet ring."

Ron swished the elder wood wand, causing weak, black sparks to fall out, and I flashed the Gaunt ring at her. Ron said, "The stuff came with a note, but Harry wouldn't let me read it."

The note had said something along the lines of:

Harry,

Do not wear this ring. It is a Horcrux and will kill you. I'm speaking from personal experience. DO NOT PUT ON THE RING.

Good luck,

Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore

"He said that the ring's one of our special items and wished us luck."

"Why'd you burn the note, then?" Ron asked.

"It's sensitive information, Ron," I shouted. "If we keep it around, then anyone could find out this ring's importance!"

Ron blushed with shame. On second thought, that might have been the slowly reddening mist. I made a note to check on that potion soon.

"You shouldn't take him on your trip," Ginevra said. "I'll be a better Ron."

"Ginevra, we've been over this. We need your spy network."

Also, I don't like her that much.

"But –"

I raised a hand, though I'm not sure if she saw it in the thickening mist. "Enough. Only Hermione and Ron shall accompany me to Potter Manor."

Hermione said, "Potter Manor?"

"My ancestral home, hidden for all these years," I said.

"…You've never seen it, have you?" Hermione said.

I paused. "Well, no."

"Are you sure you have a manor?"

"Don't all Pureblood families have manors?"

"No, Harry," Hermione said. "That fad occurred during the twelfth century when wizarding families were concerned about possibly going under siege. That's why they have such extensive warding, and their larger grounds can be put to use for agricultural purposes. The Potter family isn't nearly old enough for that."

Ron asked, "What about my manor?"

"Lost to gambling debts. The Malfoys own it now," Hermione said.

My jaw fell open, and red mist drifted inside. It tasted vaguely of cinnamon. "Is that why you hate each other so much?"

Ron said, "I guess. Mostly it's 'cause they're gits."

We were silent for a few moments, contemplating the ephemeral nature of history. At least, that's what I was thinking about. I'm fairly certain Hermione was, too. I don't know about the Weasleys.

Hermione interrupted our musings, "Harry, if there isn't a Potter Manor. Then where are we going to stay?"

"The trunk, of course," I said.

My cauldron of Felix Felicis promptly exploded, knocking the trunk over and sending a rush of black smoke towards us.

Ginevra giggled. "I feel loads better about staying behind!"

I woke up, muttering, "I always hated that name."

Ron and Hermione were still asleep. The girl hugged her wand like a teddy bear while the Weasley curled into a ball, as if to take up as little space as possible.

The ceiling slid open to reveal starlight, and, dragging my cloak behind me, I trudged upwards. I waved it closed again as I settled invisibly onto the grass and said, "Voldemort."

Pop! Pop!

Two Death Eaters arrived, waving their wands around wildly in search of rebels. The taller one frowned, "There's no one here."

"There's gotta be," the second grunted.

"Maybe the Taboo machine's acting up."

The shorter one jerked his head towards my home. "Or maybe they're in that trunk there."

"It seems pretty small," he mused.

The other said, "Maybe it's one a' those magically expanded trunks."

"I wouldn't go in there if it was!" he cried. "My cousin had one of those. The thing broke and we had to bury him in it!"

The second snorted. "I know. I was at the funeral, too."

"Maybe this is a test," the taller said slowly, "from the Dark Lord. Maybe he's trying to trick us."

"Probly," the shorter said. "Bet we oughta take the trunk, though."

"I wouldn't be so sure. It could be booby-trapped."

"We can't just head back," he snapped. "I mean, somebody around here said Voldemort!"

Pop! Pop!

The two earlier Death Eaters raised their hands while their compatriots scanned the clearing for enemies.

"Woah, woah, don't shoot. This moron here said Voldemort –"

They all groaned. Pop! Pop!

One of the men from the second group raised a hand for silence. "Okay. Clearly somebody said Vol…the word that nobody's allowed to say."

They all breathed a sigh of relief. He continued, "Let's all agree to leave and not come back to this spot for a few minutes, alright?"

The Death Eaters nodded, popping away.

I wandered back into the trunk, rousing Ron and Hermione. "Fair warning: We aren't allowed to say Voldemort, anymore. So, if you really want to say Voldemort, I'd suggest you say Voldemort now because, in about five minutes, we have to stop saying Voldemort."

It was a plain barn owl, brown and plump. A ribbon on its ankle identified it as a rented bird from Diagon Alley. It dropped the letter at my feet, not waiting for a response, and didn't even twitch as it passed through Grimmauld Place's wards.

"Wingardium Leviosa," I said, the letter flicking upwards and unfolding in front of me. It read:

Dear Lord Voldemort,

You may wonder why I, Harry Potter, have written you this letter. There are a few reasons for this.

First, I would like to inform you that my associate has brewed a cauldron of polyjuice potion, while I have kidnapped several of your Death Eaters. Further, we just followed this owl to your base.

By the time you've finished this letter, it will be too late.

Love,

Harry Potter

I leapt out of bed, humming merrily to myself. Hermione, for some inexplicable reason, immediately began panicking. She nearly tripped over our lamp (better known as Trelawney's prophecy orb) on her way towards me. Funny. I thought she'd finally relaxed about sleeping in the trunk.

"Harry, why are you so happy?" she asked.

"You-Know-Who's killing his own people!" I exclaimed.

Ron groaned, dragging himself into a sitting position. "What did you do, mate?"

"I sent him a letter. He thinks we're breaking into his base. He'll probably calm down in a few days, but then I'll send him another letter," I said. "Come to think of it, we should probably break into Gringotts while he's distracted."

Ron let out a strangled squeak, and Hermione weakly asked, "Sorry?"

"That's where Bellatrix put Hufflepuff's Cup," I said.

"Okay, this is…" – Hermione ran a hand through her hair, her face gaunt under the orb's bluish light – "Okay. We can do this. Let me get the Felix Felicis."

She was clearly delusional with fear. I frowned. "Hermione, there isn't any Felix Felicis. You made me stop brewing it for some inane reason."

"Not that Felix Felicis," Hermione said. "I'm talking about the vial I got from Slughorn for brewing the best Amortentia."

Ron said, "You've still got that?"

She snorted, rummaging through her purse. "Of course. It's not like I just used it the day I got it. That would be highly irresponsible."

To be fair, that was how I found the Chamber of Secrets in four hours by skipping five hints. My original Sixth Year was quite the adventure, though it could never compare to Third.

"There it is," she cried, pulling out a golden vial. It shimmered in the light of the prophecy orb.

"Hermione, are you still mad?" I whined, following my best minion through the busy London streets.

After several tense moments, Ron answered for her, "I'm pretty sure she is."

I tossed the Cup of Hufflepuff between my hands, enjoying the familiar warmth of its golden sides. "Come on! We got the Cup, and everything went great…I know they're called the Unforgivables, but you can still forgive me. Preferably in the next thirty seconds or so."

"Get in the trunk," she snarled.

I blinked, suddenly noticing the trunk propped against a lamppost. Right, Hermione had cast a Notice-Me-Not charm on it. I followed her inside. "I mean, really, would Moody have taught us the incantations if he didn't expect us to use –"

She whirled around at the bottom of the staircase, wand aimed at my head. "You cast the Cruciatius Curse."

"On a Death Eater," I said.

Her chin trembled. Typical Hermione: only accepting violent retribution when she does it. "It was cruel and horrible and unnecessary –"

"I contest that," I said. "You were taking Felix Felicis. If it wasn't necessary to our success, the potion wouldn't have let it happen."

"I refuse to believe that torture was necessary. There were any number of options," she said.

"Come to think of it, isn't that potion supposed to give you your perfect day?" – my eyes widened – "Hermione, you don't actually like that sort of thing? In fact, you're probably still under its effects. You want this argument!"

"No, she doesn't," Ron said.

Hermione smiled. "Thank you, Ron. It's nice to see you have some faith in me."

That was probably the Felix Felicis working.

He turned red. "I know I've fallen for a lot of stupid arguments and things, but I think I know you pretty well, 'Mione."

She flushed and glanced away, probably contemplating how her entire life was a ruse constructed by the Department of Mysteries. They were silent for some time, not even looking in my direction. It irked me.

"I know you're angry, but you don't have to ignore me," I said, the Cup's handle clenched in my fist.

"Yes, we're angry," Hermione said, pulling Ron into her mutiny.

I shook my head, frustrated by her disloyalty and hypocrisy. "I don't know why this is suddenly a problem. Nobody cared when Krum cast the Cruciatius."

She gaped, surprised by my brilliant arguing tactics. "He was under the Imperius."

I snorted. "Oh, sure he was. Everyone's under the Imperius. Tell me, Hermione, who are all these wizards casting the Imperius? Maybe we need to accept that the people we're looking for are the ones crucioing people."

"So, you, then?" Ron said.

I shook my head, setting Hufflepuff's Cup on the coffee table. "No, of course not. I can't be held accountable for my actions. After all, I was under the Imperius."

Another letter sat upon my desk. I glared at the parchment hard enough to burn a hole through it, then frantically covered it with my cloak to smother the resulting flames. A reparo returned it to a legible state, and, slumping into my throne, I read:

Dear Lord Voldemort,

I see that you have once again failed to catch myself and my companions, despite killing several of your Death Eaters. I've noticed that this happens a lot with you, and I am compelled to ask if you just really like killing your own people.

Regardless, my sense of fair play urges me to once again inform you of our visit tomorrow.

Love,

Harry Potter

P.S. I would like to assure you that I shall not be masquerading as Lucius Malfoy.

"You've killed him," Hermione whispered, eyes wide. "I know he's a bigot and probably a murderer, but I can't believe you just consigned a man to death."

"That does seem pretty nasty, mate," Ron agreed.

I had no idea what she was talking about. "Hermione, I have no idea what you're talking about."

"Lucius Malfoy!" she cried. "You just set him up to be killed."

"No I didn't. I specifically said that I wouldn't be him. He's probably the only one who's safe."

Hermione huffed, placing her hands on her hips. "Harry, you singled him out in a clearly sarcastic manner."

"You're overthinking things," I said.

"Uh, that's what I think, too," Ron said, "and won't You-Know-Who overthink it?"

"That's possible, but, then, he'll probably just decide that I want him to kill Lucius Malfoy for some reason and refuse to touch him."

"But, what if he kills him just to be safe?"

I rolled my eyes. "Fine. I'll ask him."

Ron gaped. "You'll what?"

I raised a hand to silence the Weasley as I yanked Voldemort's consciousness into my head. "Yes or no question: Are you planning to kill Lucius Malfoy?"

After a few moments' listening, I said, "I'm well aware that I told you I wouldn't be him. No, I don't retract that statement."

I turned to my minions. "He said he wasn't going to kill Lucius. Clearly, I was correct and…Why, yes, that is the Cup of Helga Hufflepuff. I'm not sure why you're surprised about this; Bellatrix has always been one of ours. On that note, have you seen your Diary anywhere recently? No reason. Just curious."

Voldemort slammed my head against the wall, then fled back to his body. Hermione was the first to find her voice. "Were you actually talking to He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named?"

"I wasn't talking to myself" – I paused for a moment, realizing that I was lying – "Regardless, he's gone now. And he's really upset about something."

HOW COULD I NOT REMEMBER WHERE I'D LEFT MY SOUL?!

I struggled to calm myself, pacing Grimmauld Place's dining room. The table had been transfigured into a throne, and the room cleared for an emergency meeting of my Inner Circle. Surely, one of them had my boyhood diary.

My eyes swept over the group, smaller now than it had ever been. It was for the better, I knew, cleared of traitors and spies. I turned to the most loyal of them all, Severus Snape. "Severus, did I ever give you a Dark artifact to watch over for me?"

Severus shook his head. "No, my lord. I'm afraid I was living in the same castle as Dumbledore. The risk was too great."

"Of course," I said. "Thank you for poisoning him, by the way."

"It was my pleasure," he drawled.

"I presume you were in a similar situation, Hagrid?"

Hagrid nodded, silent as always. Some might have found this suspicious, but I knew how invested he was in our success. After all, Giants' Rights was a founding principle of the Death Eaters.

"Sirius, did I ever give you a small, black book?" I inquired.

Sirius laughed. "Nah. You gave me a necklace."

My hands unconsciously drifted to the locket around my neck. "Yes, I suppose I did…What about you, Lucius?"

Lucius said, "No, my lord. You've given me nothing at all. May…may I please go?"

I frowned. "Why?"

"I need to brush my hair," he said.

"Didn't you just do that?"

He shook his head, terribly mussing his blond locks. "Yes, but I need to do it again."

With a chuckle, I said, "You may go in a moment. Your son was trying to open the Room of Requirement, wasn't he?"

"Yes, my lord, although he gave up on it some time ago."

"Tell him to complete whatever trials are necessary," I said.

He nodded, increasingly pale as I delayed his time with a hairbrush. "Of course, my lord."

"Also, alert your sources in Hogwarts that we're moving in. This location is no longer secure, and Trelawney has informed me that the castle will be a fortunate place for us."

Having houseguests, I found, could be rather tiring. Gone were the days of lounging in my trunk, brewing a few cauldrons of Felix Felicis and plotting against Dumbledore. Whenever the silence stretched for a while and I began to drift off to sleep under my invisibility cloak, someone invariably interrupted the peace.

Usually Ron.

The redhead groaned. "Are you still reading that book?"

I dragged my invisibility cloak off of my head in order to glare at him, and Hermione glanced up from The Tales of Beedle the Bard, lips pursed. "It's very informative –"

"It's for kids!" he shouted.

She rolled her eyes. "Informative about cultural standards, Ronald. The morality tales told to children reveal a great deal about a society's values."

Ron blinked. "Wha?"

"Morality tales, Ronald," she said. "They teach Wizarding children what wizards think are important lessons."

"For instance," I said. "The moral of The Fountain of Fair Fortune is that the magic was within you all along. The moral of The Warlock's Hairy Heart is that you shouldn't care what anyone else thinks of you. And the moral of The Tale of the Three Brothers is that you should be invisible at all times."

Hermione frowned at me, as she often does. "That isn't the moral at all. It's that you can't cheat death."

"Really, Hermione? Did you even read the tale? It clearly states that the youngest brother spends his entire life under an invisibility cloak, only taking it off when he wanted to die. I'm not sure why he would have wanted that, though," I mused, pulling my cloak tightly around my shoulders.

Ron laughed. "Probly because he spent his whole life under an invisibility cloak."

Hermione's face reddened. "He did not –"

"D'ya think he had kids under there?" Ron said.

"That is disgusting and –"

"He probably kept his entire family under the cloak, to prevent vengeance from Death," I said. It was what I would do.

Ron said, "I bet they're still there."

"IT WAS A METAPHOR!" Hermione shouted. Her voice echoed throughout the trunk, and Ron paled, likely reminded of his mother's Howlers.

"Did the story say it was a metaphor?" I asked.

"Of course not," she snapped.

"Then how do you know?" I said.

"Starting to sound like a Slytherin, mate," Ron said.

I brushed him off. "Actually, I'm sounding more like Dumbledore."

"Yes," Hermione said stiffly, "and he's the one who left me the book. I think it might be some sort of clue."

I snorted, falling back into bed with a thump. "He's obviously manipulating us. He's set us up on an adventure, and we won't understand half of it until he explains afterwards."

"He can't, though," Ron said. "He's dead."

I rolled onto my side, mumbling, "He's got a portrait."

It didn't take long to settle into my new office. I was perfectly content to keep Dumbledore's knickknacks and expensive pensieve. I wouldn't have minded the phoenix, either, but it had disappeared sometime before my arrival. I took a lemon drop from Dumbledore's tin, rolling it between my fingers. After many years, I finally had the chance to test it for poison.

Severus Snape swept into my office. "It appears that the students are rebelling."

"Why?" I asked.

"Because we are Death Eaters."

"I'm not an idiot," I snapped. "…but I will admit to continued confusion. I haven't done anything worth rebelling against."

"Dumbledore filled the Gryffindors' heads with ridiculous notions," Severus said.

"Right, he always did favor them." I never understood where he got that bias. Dumbledore went to Durmstrang.

"The Hufflepuffs are following them, as they always do," he said, "and most of the Ravenclaws haven't even noticed."

"And the Slytherins?" I asked.

Severus smirked. "Passive aggressive, but that's probably because you killed their parents."

"Potter killed some of them," I said modestly.

"Potter did not publically take credit for their deaths."

In retrospect, I probably should have taken Bellatrix off of my Public Relations team prior to her revelation as a traitor.

"Have you tried taking House Points?"

Severus nodded. "I did, but they ran out."

I snorted. "There's your problem. You lose all your power when they see they can't win."

"That's probably why they're so upset," Severus drawled. "Also, the Carrows have been crucioing First Years."

I'd expected the Carrows to be incompetent, but this was actively hurting the learning environment. Clearly, they would have to go.

I scowled, waving Severus away with a request to send up Sirius and the Malfoys.

They arrived quickly. The Malfoys were pale and nervous, but Sirius retained the relaxed demeanor that had earned him his place at my right hand. I smiled, Lucius flinched, and I smiled wider in response. "Sirius, would you like to be the Muggle Studies professor?"

He shrugged. "Yeah, sure."

"Then I shall be the Defense Against the Dark Arts professor," I declared, staring dreamily at the ceiling.

"That's a great idea!" Sirius said.

Lucius, displaying his pessimistic nature, said, "Are you…sure about this, my lord?"

Sirius smirked. "What? You think he'll be a bad professor?"

"No, of course not," Lucius said. "I was simply concerned that he might be distracted from other goals. Like running Wizarding Britain."

"You underestimate me," I said coldly.

"I think you'll be brilliant, my lord!" the younger one blurted out.

I chuckled, rising from my desk to approach him. "Ah, Draco. I've been meaning to speak with you. How go the trials?"

Draco peered intently at his toes. "I'm, uh…stuck."

I raised an eyebrow. "Stuck?"

"I can't get into the Girls' Dormitory for the next key piece. There are wards."

I clenched my wand in annoyance. "For Merlin's sake, you're a wizard! Turn yourself into a girl. I can think of three ways off the top of my head."

Draco looked pale. "Oh…"

"Or you could befriend a girl and have her do it" – I waved my wand around for emphasis – "Then you'll find out about friendship or something. What's important is that you find a lesson and learn it."

"Th-thank you," he said, voice trembling along with the rest of his body.

"You can leave, now," I said.

The Malfoy clone scurried away, likely planning to join his classmates' rebellion. I shook my head and turned my attention back to Dumbledore's lemon drops.

A Bird's Eye View: Fawkes POV

I landed upon the Apprentice's shoulder. The muscle beneath me was tensed, the shiny sword raised for battle. It pleased my eyes, and I sang in support. The Red one covered her ears, revealing her corruption to the world. But the others did not understand this.

Evil filled their nest. It was in the Apprentice's nature to fight it. I am the same.

For now, I would aid him. Lunge at the evil ones. Claw out their eyes.

But the Apprentice did not need me. He was too noble. He would do the right thing without being watched.

My Old Roost was dead and my New Roost gone. The New Roost would return, as he always did. When he came, I would be there to ensure that he denied his darker nature.

I feared what he would do if I was not there. Watching.

Chapter 18: HP vs Himself (Pt 2)

Seventh Horcrux

Chapter 9: Harry Potter vs. Himself (Pt. 2)

Ron woke slowly. He found himself unable to rise and meet the day, partially because he was still drowsy and partially because he was tied up in the middle of our trunk.

"G-guys?"

I took a leisurely walk around his captured form. My invisibility cloak ensured that he heard only measured footsteps and an eerie voice. "I always knew that you would betray us. Did you really believe that we wouldn't find out, Ron?"

"Find out what?"

"You've been sneaking out of the trunk, carefully avoiding my traps. But you were foolish. Hermione saw you returning. This wouldn't have been a problem, of course, if you had been invisible."

In her ominous, shadowy corner, Hermione groaned. "You do have to take off the cloak sometime."

"Really? That's what the youngest brother did, and then he died," I spat.

Hermione stepped into the light, glaring at me instead of Ron. "Anyway, if you have an explanation, Ronald, now would be a good time."

"I know you can't see it right now, but my wand is pointing right at you," I helpfully added.

"I've been sending letters," he said.

"Traitorous letters?"

"Hush, Harry," Hermione said. "Who are you sending letters to?"

"Uh…Fenrir Greyback," Ron muttered.

"I knew it! Also, who is that?"

"A vicious werewolf who follows You-Know-Who," Hermione said, frowning.

"We're sort of pen pals, now," Ron said, struggling against his ropes (or possibly attempting to shrug). "He's got some really good points, actually."

Hermione gaped at him. "He bites children!"

"I said some. Also, he only went after Wizarding kids 'cause he wanted to change cultural perceptions about werewolves by forcing prominent Purebloods to face the issue" – Ron paused for a moment – "I think that's a quote."

"But Remus –"

"I'm writing to him, too," Ron said. "Also my Mum. She worries, and I don't want any more Howlers."

I nodded. "She almost got us killed that one time."

Ron grinned, either at my remark or Hermione's gullible decision to free him from the ropes. "I know you don't really understand parents, Harry, but she's really stressed out about all this. Especially pretending I have Dragon Pox. I bet Hermione's parents are going barmy, too."

Hermione peered intently down at her wand, perhaps checking it for tampering. "Actually, they don't remember that they have a daughter."

"Yeah, the Dursleys did that sometimes," I commiserated.

"Harry, that's horrible."

"Maybe for you. I thought it was great."

Tears filled Hermione's eyes. "It…it isn't like that! They aren't abusive like your family. I erased their memories."

Ron's eyes widened. "Why would you…?"

"They wouldn't have gone to Australia if they knew I was still in England, but they simply aren't safe here."

"Hermione…that's evil," I said.

The brunette whirled around to glare at me, wand raised. "Will you stop saying things like that?!"

"But it is. You turned them into completely different people so that you could ignore their explicit wishes. Hermione, you murdered your parents." Even I didn't murder all of my parents.

"I'll set them right afterwards," she said.

"Unless you die," Ron said.

It was as if her vocal cords had been hit with a shriveling curse, leaving her voice small and childlike. "You guys can do it, then."

"I'm terrible at memory charms, and do you really trust Ron with your parents' brains?" I asked.

"Hey!" Ron said. "…But you're sort of right. I don't know anything about memory charms."

Hermione desperately tried to justify her despicable act. "It…it's better this way. They're safe from You-Know-Who."

Her reasoning baffled me. "Hermione, the Death Eaters don't care about your parents. How would they even know where they live? I've spent a couple of summers there, and even I don't know where they live."

"But they could still be caught in a raid or something," she mumbled, hugging herself tightly.

"That seems fairly unlikely," I said.

We were silent for some time. Eventually, Ron said, "What do we do now?"

"We haven't captured Nagini yet," Hermione said. "Separating her from You-Know-Who could be difficult."

"That is a priority," I agreed. "First, however, we have to go to Australia to fix Hermione's terrible mistake."

Though our long and dangerous mission into the outback was successful, Hermione had retreated into our trunk to sob into her pillow. "I'm evil. I'm actually evil."

Ron was above us, comforting the Grangers and – if the situation called for it – obliviating them of Hermione's confession. That left me to calm down the most vicious member of our trio. "So…you're evil."

She wailed, burying her face further into the downy fabric. I continued, "That's not a bad thing. Plenty of people are evil, and they live perfectly good lives. Like Dumbledore."

Hermione lifted her head, watching me with blank, red eyes. "Dumbledore."

"Yes, he was best friends with Grindelwald when they were kids, but then Dumbledore killed him," I said. "He didn't kill any of his other friends, however, which shows his great self-restraint."

"There's something wrong with you," she said into her pillow.

I glanced around, casually checking for listeners, before admitting. "Hermione, much like you, my nature is also somewhat evil. But I channel that evil into constructive aims like murdering the Dark Lord. We should probably get back to that, by the way. It's been a few weeks."

"But what if I'm the next Dark Lord?"

"I don't think You-Know-Who will like that very much. You'll have to kill him anyway," I said.

Hermione giggled, smiling up at me. I don't know what was funny about that, but I took it as a good sign.

I continued, "You'll be fine so long as you listen to your friends when they tell you that you're committing an atrocity. Then, later, when you're the Dark Lady of Wizarding Britain, you reward them by making them the Headmaster of Hogwarts."

Sirius Black twirled his wand between his fingers, eyes making a lazy sweep over the panicked denizens of Diagon Alley. Timid shopkeepers peered at the group of Death Eaters from windows and doorways, a woman screeched and flailed under the Cruciatius, and Nagini sprawled in the sun, a humanoid bulge in her stomach.

Black groaned. "Right, five minutes and I'm already bored. Any chance we can head back?"

Voldemort said, "I'm surprised at you, Black. I distinctly recall your enthusiasm for raids."

He shrugged. "Eh, I've got papers to grade and six kids in for detention tonight. Having a job kinda sucks."

There was a loud groan from inside Nagini. At that moment, I stepped into view, and Voldemort hissed, "Potter."

"Hi, Tom," I said, approaching the Dark Lord and his right-hand man.

He sneered at me. "Don't call me by that name."

"You've made it impossible to say your old name, and I can't just call you You-Know-Who. That would be silly."

Voldemort thoughtfully tapped his chin with his wand. "You could call me 'my lord.'"

"Well, I suppose I could, but that would be untrue."

"Show some respect for your betters!" a Death Eater shouted as he jabbed his wand at me. "Imperio."

For a moment, there was a distortion in my vision and everything seemed very bright. It ended as the Death Eater barked, "Bow to him."

I gave the man a bored look. "Crucio."

He fell, wailing, to the ground. I smirked. "You should show respect for your betters."

Voldemort laughed, and Black also cracked an uneasy grin. "That was a good one. So, have you come here to protect these miserable excuses for witches and wizards?"

"Actually, no," I said. "I just needed to grab something."

Red light filled the alleyway. The Death Eaters, shopkeepers, shoppers and even I watched, stunned, as the light receded and Ron hauled Nagini up by the neck. Hermione, shaking herself into action, grabbed the snake's tail and apparated them away. With a cheerful wave towards Voldemort and his right hand man, I followed.

"Where am I?" Nagini hissed several hours later. Ron's stunner was truly astounding.

"You're at your new home," I said. "Welcome to the trunk. You're following me, now."

The snake backed up. "Why?"

"I can talk to you."

She sniffed anxiously at the air. "That is true, but you are not my master."

I raised an eyebrow. "Are you sure?"

"…Less so now." Nagini said and slithered towards my feet. I patted her head.

"You're taking the piss out of me," Ron said.

Hermione frowned. "How did you just do that?"

"I explained that I was the superior Parselmouth," I said. "She argued, but soon realized that I was right and has endeavored to do exactly as I say…I think we can all learn a lot from Nagini."

Ron laughed, still daydreaming about our successful raid. "I can't believe you were actually bait for once!"

I smirked. "I was more of a distraction."

"And you completely ignored that Imperius."

"Then crucioed the caster," Hermione said, still judgmental despite coming to terms with her own evil, "and I suppose you're going to say that you have an insane amount of willpower because you're the descendant of Merlin or something."

I chuckled. "No, no, there's a trick to it, actually. You can't be affected by two Imperiuses at once."

Ron blinked. "What?"

I attempted to lower my speaking to Weasley levels. "If you're under the Imperius from one person, then a new Imperius won't make you do things."

Hermione nibbled her lip. "You were under the Imperius?"

"I am under the Imperius," I said, pointing my wand at my temple.

"You…why?"

I stroked Nagini, who was currently curled around my leg, squeezing affectionately. "To protect me from the Imperius, of course. I just order myself to do whatever I want, so it doesn't really affect me."

Ron said, "So, when you said that you couldn't be blamed for crucioing that guy 'cause you were under the Imperius, you weren't joking?"

"Why would I joke about something like that?"

Hermione's eyes were wide with wonder and admiration. "Harry, how long have you been doing this?"

"On and off since I learned about the spell."

"Three years?" she squeaked.

More like sixty. "…Yes."

"That cannot be healthy," she muttered. "Take it off, please."

I did so, and Hermione stole my wand.

The sink unfolded, revealing the shadowed and slimy entrance to the Chamber of Secrets. Draco Malfoy peered into the darkness, keeping his feet firmly on the tiles of the Girls' Loo. "I suppose this explains a lot. I was starting to think that Potter was a pervert."

I nodded. "Yes. The current location of the Chamber is an unfortunate consequence of the constantly-shifting nature of Hogwarts."

Draco seemed troubled. "This doesn't make sense, though. How can one of the trials require a Parselmouth? The other ones at least pretended to be fair."

I snorted. "You don't need to be a Parselmouth to open it. There are only like four syllables in Parseltongue, random hissing would probably crack it eventually."

He was shocked silent at my brilliance.

"Besides," I continued, "It's not unfair that you needed a Parselmouth because one was there. Perhaps…one will always be there."

Draco took a step into the Chamber. "Thank you, my lord."

"I've told you: Call me Professor," I said. "Also, good luck with the Basilisk!"

"Hermione, please give me my wand back," I begged.

Hermione held my wand above her head, using her height advantage against me. "Not until I'm sure that you won't cast an Unforgivable on yourself."

I took a step upon the worn, wooden floor and placed a hand on her shoulder. "What? No. Why would I cast an Unforgivable on myself? That would be ridiculous. Give me the wand."

She groaned, my wand clenched firmly in her hands. "No."

"I can feel my magical core draining."

"There hasn't been a theory of magic that even postulated magical cores since the seventeenth century" – Hermione furrowed her brow – "I'm honestly not sure where you would have heard about them."

"Hermione, I am begging you –"

She glared at me. "Will you stop?"

"I'll never stop. You'll have to imperio me."

"I will not," she ground out.

"I'll set Nagini on you," I said. "Nagini, hiss at Hermione."

Nagini hissed, and Hermione swallowed heavily. "You wouldn't."

"…You're right," I mumbled.

Hermione blinked. "Really?"

I whirled around to my other minion. "Ron, give me Dumbledore's wand."

Ron's freckles stood darkly against his white face. "Uh, can't. Sorry."

"You aren't even using it!"

"It's not a very good match for me," he mumbled. "But I still can't give it to you."

"Don't let Hermione bully you into denying me this," I said.

"Honestly! Will you stop trying to manipulate Ron" – Hermione raised a hand to keep me silent – "and, no, I am not going to stop you with the Imperius just because you have some sort of addiction."

I glared at my traitorous followers. "I am not addicted. It's just that everything is terrible, now. The colors are too bright and the light is sharper and I feel guilty about everything…Oh Merlin, is this how you feel all the time?"

"Uh, no?" Ron denied his suffering, but I could see the truth in his eyes. Wait, had they always been blue?

Hermione pinched the bridge of her nose, wild hair drifting over her eyes. "I'm sorry, Harry, but you'll just have to ride out this…whatever this is."

She was wrong, I suddenly realized. I raced towards the cupboard and dug through my robes. With a triumphant cry, I unearthed a wand and held it aloft.

Hermione frowned, and, with a twirl of her wand, said "Expelliarmus."

I whimpered. Hermione examined the wand with a gentle frown. "Where did you even get this?"

"I stole it from Neville. The reason doesn't even make sense now" – I paused for a moment – "Do you think I should give it back?"

Ron frowned. "Uh, maybe when you're acting less crazy…or, at least, more your kind of crazy."

I shook my head, summoning my wand from Hermione's grasp with a flick of my wrist. "No, we have to go to Hogwarts. It's the only way to defeat the Dark Lord. He's killing people right now."

Hermione said, "Harry –"

"Right now. I can hear the screaming. It's kind of creeping me out. Besides, I really need to return Neville's wand."

Hermione sighed. "Alright."

Ron scrambled towards the trunk's desk in search of parchment. "I'll owl Ginny."

We followed Pansy Parkinson and…Crabbe through the secret passageway, Ron sulking and eying the Slytherins with suspicion. "Probly leading us into a trap, bloody Death Eaters in training."

Hermione said, "Ronald, stop antagonizing our allies."

"I don't think they're really our allies," he said. "Why would Ginny send a bunch of Slytherins to get us?"

Parkinson flipped her dark hair dismissively. "Perhaps because we're the only ones who can travel unwatched in Hogsmeade?"

Ron kicked a rodent's skull, sending it skittering into the darkness. "I'm just saying we should've gotten a passcode or something."

"Then you would be claiming that they'd intercepted our mail," Hermione said.

I trailed behind them, comfortably invisible as I pulled along our trunk. "It's possible they still did. That's why they were able to so seamlessly intercept our meeting, leading us ever-closer to our doom."

Hermione, showing a shocking lack of caution, snapped, "Harry, will you stop encouraging him?"

Ron scowled. "I just don't get why a bunch of Slytherins would help us."

Parkinson disdainfully glanced at the slime dripping from the walls and the Weasley walking behind her. "I'm beginning to wonder that, as well."

"See?"

Crabbe grunted, "The Dark Lord killed my father."

Was that my fault? That might have been one of my killing curses. I shrugged off the question. "That monster."

The hulking boy sniffled. "Everything's worse with him here…'Cept the Creature Rights' laws. Those are very progressive."

"They're a travesty, if you ask me," Parkinson said.

"Nobody did," Ron snapped. "Why are you helping, anyway?"

"I owe Ginny a favor. Besides, Harry is an honorary Slytherin."

Ron paled. "He's a what, now?"

Parkinson smirked, a slight sway in her step. "Oh, yes. He did win us the House Cup, in Third Year."

"But that doesn't make him –"

"Snape thinks it does," she purred. "Of course, he thinks that everyone who beats him at something is supposed to be in Slytherin. That man takes house loyalty way too far."

"I feel obligated to point out that, though I have the best traits of all four houses, I am more brave and noble than all of them combined," I announced.

Hermione rolled her eyes. Ron said, "That can't be it, though. There's gotta be some other reason –"

A slim figure stepped out of the darkness, red hair dazzling under our lumos. "They've been a lot more helpful since I explained that I'm the Heiress of Slytherin."

Ron's jaw dropped. "Ginny?!"

"Hi guys!" Ginevra chirped.

Hermione smiled. "How are you doing?"

"Great! We've taken back most of the classrooms, three of the common rooms, and possibly the North Tower, depending on whether or not Trelawney's still a Death Eater."

"I guess you still haven't got the snake's den," Ron said.

"Nope. That was easy," Ginevra said. "The problem is that we lost Hufflepuff."

"Castle moved after the Death Eaters showed up," Crabbe grunted.

"I had to share a bedroom with six Puffs." Parkinson shivered with perfectly justifiable disgust.

Ginevra said, "We're staging expeditions into the dungeons to find it, but no luck so far."

The Slytherins departed as we entered an enormous room. Piles of rubble leaned against its filthy walls, and beds were scattered about the rock floor, some holding bandaged and unconscious students. The Chamber of Secrets had certainly changed since the last time I'd visited.

We passed several cauldrons as we walked. I peered into one. "Felix Felicis?"

Neville approached us, grinning. "I figured we needed all the luck we could get."

"Hey, Nev!" one of the injured students yelled. "Get away from the potions before they have another go at 'cha."

"Neville makes the potions explode just by looking at them," Ginevra explained.

Neville laughed, and the Sword of Gryffindor banged against his side with each guffaw. "Came in handy in the Potions classroom that one time."

An arm crawled over Neville's shoulder and down his chest, and Lavender's face appeared in the crook of his neck. "You shouldn't stay here too long, Nevi, sweetie."

Hermione stepped forward to protect Ron from the potential explosion. Not surprising, her shield has always been superior. She regarded Lavender coolly. "You're dating Neville now."

"I think he is just sooo brave for taking on all those Death Eaters," she cooed. "Also, he's got the Sword of Gryffindor, so he's the bravest guy in the whole wide world!"

"I could have the Sword of Gryffindor," Ron muttered.

Hermione elbowed him, and he smiled nervously. I shoved Neville's old wand at his chest. "This is yours. I found it in my trunk and was compelled by my inherent nobility to return it."

Neville stared down at it, smiling softly. "Wow. Thanks. I don't really use magic much, and my new wand's a better match, anyway. But this was my Dad's. Good to have it back."

I nodded. "Yes."

Ginevra spun in place, short hair twirling around her head like a dress. "Welcome to the Chamber of Secrets!"

Hermione glanced around. "So you're really the Heiress? I'd just assumed you had caught Harry's sense of humor."

"Of course I am," Ginevra said. "I command the Basilisk."

She hissed, "Come." Or possibly "Strangle." Her accent was terrible. The Basilisk slithered towards us, students scrambling out of its way. It came to rest beside Ginevra, eyes closed and waiting for instructions.

"Go sleep twice," Ginevra said. "Only need look terrifying."

I would like to reiterate the horror that was Ginevra Weasley attempting to speak Parseltongue. The Basilisk silently accepted this butchery of the language, returning to an empty corner where it curled into a ball.

Ron had the look of a man whose entire world had been destroyed, and even Hermione appeared a bit faint. I responded in the only way I knew how, "Hah! I told you I wasn't the Heir."

What a fool I had been. I'd let my guard down in enemy territory, and, now, here I was: Cornered.

I eased my hand towards my pocket, hoping I could reach my wand before she did any irreparable damage. But, no, my plan had been foreseen and my arm grabbed.

"Harry, I just wanted to thank you for giving me a second chance," Ginevra said. "You know, back in my First Year."

I frowned, unsure of how she'd come to this conclusion. Ginevra Weasley was being possessed by my younger self while opening the Chamber of Secrets. At least, I think she was. "You remember being the Heir?"

Her lips flitted upwards, and she murmured, "Bits and pieces. The bathroom. The Chamber. Speaking Parseltongue. You."

She squeezed my arm a little tighter, and her voice softened to a whisper. "I've reformed. I really have, but sometimes I still think about killing Muggleborns."

"That's perfectly natural," I assured her.

Ginevra giggled. "That's what Pansy says, too. Anyways, I just wanted to thank you for not sending me to Azkaban and…"

Using her height advantage against me, Ginevra leaned forward. Her breath fanned my lips. "…tell you that…"

I jerked away. "You're very welcome. However, I need to go kill Voldemort. Goodbye!"

Grabbing Hermione, I fled towards the Girls' Loo.

"We should have gotten Ron," Hermione muttered as we hurried through the hallways.

I shook my head. "There wasn't time."

Hermione raised an eyebrow. "What do you mean?"

I mentally shoved away images of Ginevra, though they would no doubt haunt my nightmares for years to come. "We need to get the Diadem of Ravenclaw."

"So we couldn't wait thirty seconds to call over Ron?"

"Exactly. This is a quick, easy mission, and getting Ron would take more time than bringing him would save. Besides, someone has to watch the trunk, and, frankly, it's hard enough fitting you under the cloak." I pulled at the starry fabric surrounding us. If Hermione didn't hunch forward, the passing Death Eaters could see our shoes.

We reached the third floor, and I began pacing. Hermione asked, "The Diadem is in the Room of Requirement?"

I turned on my heel, heading back up the hallway. "Technically, everything that's in Hogwarts is in the Room, if you wish for it hard enough."

Hermione rolled her eyes. "Didn't you lock that?"

"I did," I said. "But I can get in."

I finished pacing, and an impressive, oak door shimmered into existence. A silvery lock sat in its center. I sauntered up to it. "All I need is faith in myself, which I have in abundance, and to have learned lessons from the trials. Thankfully, I set up the trials, so I already know everything."

"Of course you do," Hermione muttered from close behind me.

I turned the knob and –

Click.

I turned the knob again. And again. It didn't open.

"Alright, new plan," I said. "We need to convert Malfoy."

"WE WHAT?!"

"He's already done half the trials. With our help, he could be through the door in hours…I suppose it would be too much to ask for you to charm him with your feminine wiles?"

She groaned. "Harry, that's…no."

I leaned against the wall, the stone's chill dulled by my cloak. "Right, right. The break-up's still too fresh. That's fine. Draco is rebellious enough without your influence."

"When has Malfoy ever rebelled?" Hermione said. "He practically worships his father."

"And yet his hair tells another story," I said.

Hermione blinked, her mind slowly churning over my amazing deduction. "His…I'm sorry?"

"Lucius Malfoy is very proud of his long, luxurious hair. He even cloned himself just to ensure its continued existence, yet what has Draco done? Cut it and hardened it with harsh gels. If Draco was truly so devoted to his father, why would he spit upon his very reason for existence?"

Hermione buried her face in her hands. "I think I liked this plan better before you explained it."

I grinned and took off towards the Dungeons. "Let's go find Malfoy."

A/N: It's common in fanon for snakes to obey Parselmouths for very flimsy reasons. At first, this seemed silly. Then, I realized something:

If, while walking down the street one day, a cat turned to me and said, "Hand me your umbrella," I would give the cat the bloody umbrella. You don't just ignore the talking animal. That's the very foundation of magical girl series…

Also, I sometimes think that my Tom Riddle is merely a series of bad decisions executed well.

Chapter 20: Epilogue: Thirteen Years Later

Seventh Horcrux

Epilogue: Thirteen Years Later

The first day of school had arrived yet again.

The students were unusually awake this year, buzzing about the previous night's Sorting and constructing all sorts of wild tales. After all, it had been thirteen years since anyone had been placed in Slytherin.

As I passed the green-clothed table, I nodded to the solitary figure picking at her toast and received a weak grin in return. This set off a new round of whispering.

Sirius Black gave a large wave and beckoned for me to sit beside him at the staff table. I'm not certain why we kept him on as the Muggle Studies professor after the war. I don't think he's ever met a Muggle that he wasn't murdering.

People said that Black was a spy for Dumbledore, but I'm not so sure about that. It seems like the old man had an awful lot of spies: Sirius, Severus, Hagrid…

I'm pretty sure Lucius Malfoy wasn't a spy for Dumbledore, but he got off, too.

I avoided Sirius's gaze, still uneasy about his wild and unpredictable temperament, and he moved on to a closer target: Headmaster Snape.

I, instead, took a seat between Minerva McGonagall and Ginevra, our History of Magic professor.

The Weasley took the post after Binns passed on twelve years ago. It was completely unexpected, and, after so many years of his abysmal teaching, no one was really qualified for the job. Luckily, Ginevra had lesson plans and everything.

Many assume that Binns's unfinished business had something to do with Voldemort's demise. That seemed strange to me, since he was teaching for generations before I came along. Maybe he just longed to see one last war.

In all likelihood, he wanted something inane that no one else would have noticed.

Ginevra held up the Prophet, exclaiming, "Hermione won!"

"Of course she did. Hermione would never let anything get in the way of her ruthless ambition."

Hermione, upon graduation, returned to the Department of Mysteries. After our adventures, however, she began to find the work unfulfilling and returned to her childhood dream of becoming the Dark Lady of Wizarding Britain.

Her husband Ron became a Werewolf Rights activist. Of course, there was a terrible scandal a few years ago, when it turned out that he wasn't actually a werewolf and had been lying to us all. I, for one, was shocked.

Ginevra leaned over to straighten my tie and remarked, "Looks like Neville got engaged to another princess."

Ah, yes, my apprentice: A man lauded as the next Gilderoy Lockhart.

I tapped my wand against my chin. "Is he still fighting Dark Lords in Albania?"

Ginevra shrugged. "Hard to say. It's a Skeeter article, and Neville refuses to comment. Aside from mentioning that you were his teacher, of course."

"Of course."

At a table below, a young Gryffindor disappeared behind the latest edition of the Quibbler, and I reminisced about Luna, who set off in search of Atlantis some years ago, never to be seen again.

Some say that she found the lost city.

I prefer to believe that she's dead because that excuses her for never writing.

As for me, well, everyone always knew where I would end up…

The First Years peered around my classroom, which was decorated with souvenirs from my various victories, my Order of Merlin, a drowsing Nagini, and a phoenix tensed for attack. As minutes slowly passed by, they grew increasingly anxious.

The Finch-Flechley girl, idly tugging at her braided hair, remarked, "We should just leave."

"We can't do that," Adrian Pucey Jr. protested.

She sniffed disdainfully, adjusting her glasses. "If he can't be bothered to show up, then why should we?"

"He's probably just running late! If we run off, then we'll lose a ton of points."

"Rose isn't here," Zabini said. "Do you think she knows something we don't?"

The newest Malfoy clone yawned, reluctantly lifting his head from the table. "She's sick."

"Really? I've heard she's too afraid to show her face after last night," Finch-Flechley purred.

Malfoy glared. "She is sick."

"I bet she's crying her eyes out right now. I certainly would be, if I were her…"

The blond leapt to his feet, wand in hand. "Shut up, Finch."

She drew her own wand. "Finch? Is that really the best you can do?"

"Sorry, I couldn't think of anything stupider than your name."

The few giggling students were silenced by Finch-Flechley's glare. "Listen here, you simpering, Slytherin-wannabe –"

Her wand began to glow with a spell, so I accioed it, along with the Malfoy's holly one. The students watched, awed by my sudden appearance.

"P-Professor!" Finch-Flechley said. "I didn't see you there."

"Of course not. I was invisible. I'm always invisible. And watching you."

The students simultaneously shuddered. I sighed. "I'm very disappointed in you both for fighting like this."

Malfoy said, "But, Professor Potter –"

"Thirty points from Gryffindor for this outrageous spectacle," I finished.

The two traded a confused look, earlier enmity forgotten. The girl said, "We're Hufflepuffs."

I raised a finger to my lips. "Shhhh. Nobody needs to know that."

"This is the Hufflepuff class," Pucey said.

I raised an eyebrow. "The Hufflepuff and Slytherin class."

"Well, yeah, but Rose is out," one of the Muggleborns said.

"She's sick," Malfoy added.

I gestured towards the right half of the classroom. "Take a seat."

"Do we have to sit on the Hufflepuff side, sir?" Pucey asked as they squeezed onto the benches.

I frowned, surveying the class. Hufflepuff had benefited from Slytherin's fall, swelling to one and a half times its original size and becoming the largest Hogwarts house. In a few years, they might even have a chance at the Cup.

"I suppose not," I said. "I must warn you, however, that traveling to the Slytherin side may be considered traitorous to your house. Who's first?"

Zabini moved reluctantly, yet, soon, the group was equally split. In fairness, it was very crowded.

"That was a clever idea, Mr. Pucey. Fifty points to Ravenclaw!"

While my system isn't perfect, it's still fairer than what Snape used to do.

Fawkes landed on my shoulder as I said, "I have yet to formally welcome you all to Defense Against the Dark Arts with Professor Potter. Some of you may know me as Harry Potter, the man who defeated the Dark Lord Voldemort. If you do not know me, I'm Harry Potter. I defeated Voldemort."

There were a few appreciative murmurs, although not nearly as many as I had once received. Time, it seemed, had dulled the grandeur of my achievements. These children had only known peace.

I continued, "Now, on to our lesson: The basilisk has gone mad, attacking everyone regardless of blood status. Merely to gaze into its eyes means immediate death. Zabini, WHAT DO YOU DO?"

Zabini's black eyes widened in panic. "Wh-what?"

I paused. The correct answer was to use a mirror to Petrify yourself. Though this does nothing to defeat the basilisk, that's already a lost cause, and at least you're safe. Perhaps that was too advanced for our first class. Turning to Pucey, I said, "The Merpeople drag you into the Lake –"

Pucey wrinkled his brow in a very Weasley fashion. "Merpeople very rarely venture towards the surface. Why would they attack someone on land?"

I waved his concerns aside. "They want some sort of inexplicable vengeance. You try to ask them about it, but water floods your mouth before you can say a word. The last of your air is gone."

Finch-Flechley regarded me coldly from behind her glasses. "This is stupid. None of this will ever happen."

"You want something more mundane? Fine," I snapped. "You, Finch-Flechley, fall from the moving staircase. You have the next three seconds before your neck snaps on the stone below."

The girl gaped. "That actually happened?"

"The last incident was in May. Mr. Abbott saved himself, but you just used your three seconds to ask a question…Does anyone else know what to do?"

A timid redhead raised her hand. "The Levitation Charm, maybe?"

"Very good, Miss...?"

"Puttock, sir," she whispered.

I nodded. "Do any of you know how to perform the Levitation Charm?"

Puttock's hand darted downwards, and only a few other students rose theirs. I said, "Then I suppose we'll have to learn it, won't we?"

The Hufflepuffs nodded, some more eagerly than others.

I shall spend the rest of eternity as the Defense Against the Dark Arts professor at Hogwarts. Of course, I would have to explain my immortality to avoid the inevitable rumors…and, first, I should ensure that I am actually immortal.

Come to think of it, whatever did happen to the Philosopher's Stone?

As I weaved through my students, helping the clumsier ones with their wandwork, I decided to subtly inquire about the artifact.

"So, Snape, whatever did happen to the Philosopher's Stone?"

Severus regarded me from across the Headmaster's desk. "It is in the Mirror of Erised. Apparently, you can only get it out if you don't want it. But everyone does because it makes you immortal. Even if we don't tell them what it is, they still want it because we asked them to get it."

I frowned. "Did you try getting a student to do it?"

"You."

Hm. That hardly counted, since I was actively out to steal the Stone, at the time.

My eyes trailed across the office, now devoid of spinning knickknacks and well-polished candy bowls. The visitor's chair had clearly received a Discomfort Charm or two, and even the old Headmasters' portraits had worn around the edges after increasingly vicious attempts to tear them from the walls. Dumbledore watched us with a knowing gleam in his eyes, and, on a shelf below him, the Sorting Hat leaned forward to better eavesdrop.

Severus interrupted my thoughtful silence. "Not one day under your care, and Miss Weasley has already started skipping classes. I'm not sure why I'm surprised."

I said, "Frankly, I'm not even sure why you made me the Head of Slytherin."

"Because you are the only Slytherin on staff."

"I'm a Gryffindor."

Severus raised an eyebrow. "Potter, even the Hat thinks you are a Slytherin, and the Hat doesn't think anyone is a Slytherin."

I snorted. "It's clearly screwing with us. Hat, what house does Snape belong in?"

The Sorting Hat's face crumpled into a wide smile. "Severus Snape is a true Gryffindor."

"I very much agree," Dumbledore's portrait said.

Severus tossed a Silencing Spell over his shoulder, while Dumbledore ducked into Phineas Nigellus Black's frame.

Come to think of it, it had been a while since I'd checked in on my most active Horcrux. I held out my hand. "Accio Sorting Hat."

I grasped the Hat and deposited it atop my head. "So, how's it going?"

He hummed thoughtfully, inwardly remarking. "Better than you'd think. I pretty much have everything I've ever wanted: immortality, a place at Hogwarts, the ability to manipulate the destinies of children…"

"Yes, about that."

The Hat's fabric curled upwards to mimic a raised eyebrow, a deeply disconcerting movement for something pressed against my forehead. "You have a problem with the way I, the Sorting Hat, have been Sorting?"

I chuckled uneasily. Why must I be so brilliant and impossible to manipulate? "No, not at all. It's just that this whole Slytherin thing is getting a little ridiculous. It made sense just after the war, when no one wanted to go to Slytherin, but –"

The Hat shivered with fury. "I gave you the Weasley girl. WHAT MORE DO YOU WANT FROM ME?"

"More of them," I said simply.

"Then send me more Slytherins. We have standards, now. I've mentioned it in every song for the past thirteen years."

"Yes, I recall. Those parts don't rhyme very well."

The Sorting Hat spat, "I'd like to see you rhyme with cleansing."

He had me there, and we both knew it. I turned to Severus, who alternated between attending to paperwork and sneering in our direction. "We should probably stop before Snape destroys his office again."

The Sorting Hat cajoled, "Let's hold off for a while. I do so love to torment him until he hexes me."

"Do those actually affect you?" I asked.

"Not at all, but there's no sense in encouraging him to find something that will."

We shared a good laugh about that, loudly, before I sent him back to his shelf with a flick of my hand.

"He really is quite delightful," I informed a glowering Severus.

"Feel free to take him with you on your way out," he said dourly. "Additionally, inform Ginevra that her new lesson plan has been rejected by the Board."

I scowled. "Why should I have to tell her?"

"Potter, the two of you have been dating for over a decade."

I frowned. "Wait, really? Oh…that explains a lot. I don't suppose you could promise not to tell anyone that I didn't know that?"

"I don't have casual conversation with anyone, Potter."

"Except for me," I said. Dumbledore's portrait smiled at this pronouncement, giving me a thumbs up.

"No," Severus said. "I only brought you in here today to discuss the many complaints you've earned…"

"Like you have any room to talk. You got a dozen complaints a week when you were a professor, and those were just mine," I said.

Save for a twitch of the eye, Severus ignored me. "…at which point you started shouting about the Philosopher's Stone."

The fireplace flared up, and Fawkes beat his wings at it to establish dominance.

Hermione and Ron stepped into my office, still wearing the brightly-colored suits that were so popular in the modern Ministry of Magic. The phoenix ignored the new arrivals in favor of glaring at the defiant flames, while I welcomed them with a cheerful, "Congratulations on conquering Wizarding Britain, Hermione!"

"I was elected, Harry," Hermione said.

"Sure you were" - I winked - "I'm certain there wasn't any coercion involved at all."

She frowned, ceding my point. "Well, I suppose that depends on your definition of 'coercion.' This is politics."

Sensing the danger this conversation held to his wife's thin veneer as a "Light" witch, Ron interrupted us. "It was good hearing you'd finally asked Ginny to marry you."

Hermione beamed. "Oh, yes! Honestly, I was starting to think your relationship was entirely one-sided."

Ron slung an arm around Hermione's shoulder. "But I told her, 'Mione, even Harry isn't that dense. Don't go putting your nose in it.'"

"Yes, of course, I'm terribly grateful," I said hurriedly. "I'll admit that I was surprised to see you two for this parent-teacher conference. I don't think we've ever had one of these that wasn't a front for a Death Eater attack."

As an afterthought, I checked their identities with a covert spell.

Hermione raised her chin haughtily, declaring, "Well, we could hardly send Rose off to school without checking up on her, particularly given the circumstances."

"'Sides, you're our friend, so it's not all that bad," Ron said. "I wouldn't have gone back to Snape's office for anything."

Hermione elbowed his side, sent him a dark glare, then turned back to me with a deceptively innocent smile. I led the couple to my desk, gesturing for them to sit in the child-sized chairs. At Hermione's unamused look, I transfigured one of them into a throne more befitting her current status.

"I imagine it's quite difficult to let go of your power, even for such a short visit," I commiserated. After all, a lack of supervision had been the death of many a Dark Lord and Lady's once-successful campaigns.

"Oh, no," Hermione said. "It's more difficult getting time off for Ron than me."

Ron grinned. "Can't get away during the full moon. You know how it is, mate."

Hermione continued, "My secretary is perfectly capable of handling things for a few hours."

"Ah, yes, how is Malfoy?" I inquired.

"Still a bit upset that his son is a Hufflepuff," she admitted, "but I think he's taken some comfort in the fact that he's one of the Slytherin Hufflepuffs."

"At least Scorpius gets to be the minion of a real Slytherin," I said.

"About that" - Hermione bit down on her lip but released it a moment later, likely Malfoy's influence - "I know a decent amount about Rose's life, of course. She sends plenty of letters, but I'm just not entirely sure…I don't suppose you could tell me…"

"How's she doing?" Ron interrupted. Hermione laughed softly, gesturing for me to answer his question.

"Perfectly fine, under the circumstances," I said. "She's been gaining influence, asserting her power, preparing her lair -"

"Lair?" Hermione said weakly. The couple seemed rather pale, though that was likely because I had chosen a gloomy, prophecy-lighted ambiance over windows.

"The Slytherin dorms. It's built to house hundreds. She's already setting traps…"

Ron winced.

"…and we're in negotiations for a possible sleep-over," I finished.

Hermione smiled. "Well, that sounds nice. It would be good to get her around other children outside of classes, especially when she lacks the innate bonding of the house system."

Ron leaned back in his tiny chair, forehead wrinkled and Weasley eyes squinted. "What do you do when she gets in trouble?"

"Why would she possibly be getting in trouble?" Hermione said sharply.

He shrugged. "Dunno. Just wondering. I mean, there's not much use taking points since she's the only Slytherin and all…"

"Rose actually does have a fairly decent chance at the Cup," I said.

Hermione blinked. "I'm sorry?"

"It turns out that most students end up with a negative number of points but are dragged up by the outliers. Rose is one of the outliers, without the dead weight."

"But she's still only one student," Hermione said.

I smirked. "Also, Snape still favors Slytherin."

"'Course he does," Ron muttered darkly.

"For the moment, she's coping well," I continued. "My main concern is next year, when she'll have to be the Slytherin Quidditch team."

"...Then, as the Leaving Feast is just about to begin, I will give you exactly as many points as you need to win," I finished as we crept, invisibly, around McGonagall's chess board. The pieces knew that we were there, but they lacked the intelligence to find us.

Rose shook her head. "I don't want that. Everyone will hate me."

I sighed. "What do you want then?"

Rose looked up at me, her eyes shining. "I want to find the room that gives you everything you want."

The Room of Requirement had long since joined Hogwarts' many legends. "That can be arranged."

With a Flame-Freezing charm, we passed into the final room of Dumbledore's maze. I gestured towards the mirror.

Rose straightened her back as she approached it, yet her composure fell when she saw her reflection. "I'm with some of the Hufflepuffs, at the Slytherin Table. We're laughing and talking and…We're all wearing green!"

"Weasley, focus!" I snapped.

She shook her head, forcibly jarring herself from the enchantment. With renewed determination, Rose set about trying to steal the Philosopher's Stone, as I did at her age.

I checked the time.

9:06 AM

While waiting, I created a throne out of McGonagall's chess pieces. There was still a bit of life to them, but the twitching of spears and swords kept me from becoming too bored.

"Tempus."

9:45 AM

Rose had begun threatening the mirror in increasingly creative ways. While I suspected her mother would disapprove of such blatant tactics, she would no doubt applaud her vocabulary.

"Tempus."

11:12 AM

I finished the last of my grading, tucking the papers into a corner where they would hopefully be safe from Rose's barrage of hexes.

"Tempus."

1:00 PM

"Dobby," I called. "Get us lunch."

He fetched us the Malfoys' latest cuisine and served it on their silver, occasionally impaling himself on my throne.

"Tempus."

3:18 PM

"I GIVE UP!" Rose yelled, still glaring at the mirror. She had, I thought fondly, found her first nemesis.

"I suppose we could take a short break," I said.

"No," she said. "No breaks. I'm done. This is stupid."

I raised an eyebrow. "But what about the room that gives you everything you want?"

"I don't care anymore. I am never looking at this bloody mirror again," she hissed. "That is the only thing I want right now!"

With that, Rose's hand fell into her robes pocket and a smirk curled across her Weasley face. She pulled out a glinting, red stone and held it triumphantly in the air. "Hah! Got it."

"Very good," I said, bringing it into my possession with a lazy gesture. "One of the trials is hidden in the Fifth Year Slytherin Girl's Dormitory. It should provide clues to find the others."

The girl sprinted away, eager to begin her latest quest. Of course, the Flame-Freezing Charm had worn off, and she had no way to escape the room. It occurred to me that I should probably help her before she accidentally (or, more likely, intentionally) destroyed the castle.

Passing the object that had once guarded a chance at immortality, I glanced at my reflection. I gave a jaunty wave to my other self and shared a grin with him. It seemed that, with the loss of the Philosopher's Stone, whatever magic Dumbledore had worked on the artifact had disappeared.

It was only a mirror now.

A/N: And so it comes to an end (barring omakes).

Thanks to: My brother, for coming up with this brilliant idea and contributing many a bizarre plot point. My other brother, for keeping us grounded in the land of sanity and having the idea that spawned our Trelawney-as-a-Death Eater plot. My readers here and at Spacebattles, for their beautiful, wonderful insanity, writing several omakes, and leaving thousands of comments, favs, and follows. And, of course, myself, for actually writing the damned thing. :)

Chapter 21: Omakes!

Seventh Horcrux Omakes! (a fun mix of snippets and my rambles)

First Year: A Dream Come True

I shuffled my feet. "Erm, as long as we're down here, I wanted to ask about my summer living arrangements. I can't go back to the Dursleys. I-I might kill them."

"Surely you're exaggerating," Dumbledore said, eyes twinkling.

"No," I insisted, glancing at Quirrel's smoking corpse. "You misunderstand. I might actually murder them."

He stared at me gravely. "You aren't allowed to use magic over the summers, Harry."

I looked him dead in the eye and pushed some absolutely fascinating images to the front of my mind. "You think I need magic to kill? Muggles kill each other all the time. They've practically made an art form out of it. Besides, I live in the same house as the Dursleys. Eventually, they'll sleep. Oh, they'll sleep…"

"…and that's why I'm staying in the castle this summer," I finished smugly.

Hermione blinked, "Harry, sometimes you really scare me."

I smirked. "Aw, you're just jealous that I get to spend two extra months in the library."

Hermione denied it, but I knew the truth.

Anytime: Cognitive Dissonance

"Hermione, are you trying to imply that I can't believe two things at once? I find that offensive."

Hermione frowned. "Harry, no one can. That's a sign of insanity."

Author's Musings:

Come-uppance

The treatment of Severus Snape in canon is…weird. He spends an inordinate amount of time tormenting children and generally being nasty to everyone he meets. But then he turns out to be on the right side of the war so INSTANT REDEMPTION.

The fan fiction community is split between wanting to punish him for being such a bastard and making him earn that redemption by becoming a somewhat likable person.

In Seventh Horcrux, Severus is actually fairly likeable. He's still a jerk, but he's mainly shown being a jerk to Harry who is equally jerkish back and, depending on your view, may be twice Snape's age. When Harry asserts that Snape is his rival, Hermione doesn't argue with him.

Additionally, Severus gets to spend the rest of his life in his own personal hell, surrounded by people he despises: Harry, Harry's girlfriend, Sirius Black, Dumbledore's portrait, and Volde-Hat. Of course, as Dumbledore constantly asserts, it's possible he secretly likes them…

Author's Musings:

Sirius Business

It just occurred to me that I accidentally parodied myself.

Once upon a time, I planned to make a fic in which everyone's misconceptions about Sirius in Third Year were spot on. He was the spy, tricking everyone, betraying the Potters, and now out for revenge against Harry Potter (making him the perfect candidate for the DADA position, come to think of it). This Sirius, despite being a vicious Death Eater, would have the exact same personality as in canon. After all, being a villain doesn't mean being a drag, right?

In this fic, everyone assumes that silly Sirius Black is an evil Death Eater, and he totally rolls with it while pranking evildoers along the way.

Third Year: The Infamous Sirius Black

Black had stolen my wand. The Great Lord Voldemort had been felled by an Expelliarmus and, soon, he would be vanquished by his own deranged follower. Perhaps the Horcrux would push me into another body, but, right now, the only available options were my only competent minion, a fugitive, and the Weasley.

I had invested far too much into this life to become a Weasley.

I had to reveal my true identity. My voice shook. "Wait! Before you kill me, there's something I need to tell you – "

Black interrupted, "I'm not going to kill you. I could never kill you, Harry."

I blinked in surprise. I probably shouldn't have pressed my luck, but I always was curious. "Wait. You are Sirius Black, right? The vengeful, unhinged Death Eater who betrayed my parents and exploded some Muggles?"

"I was framed."

"Oh. That's nice. Never mind about what I was going to say before, then."

Third Year: Bloody Gryffindors…

"You should have realized," Lupin said quietly, "if Voldemort didn't kill you, we would. Good-bye, Peter."

"I'll kill him!"

Everyone turned to me in shock. "What? You can't do that," Lupin argued.

"He killed my parents. I get dibs," I said.

"You're only thirteen, Harry. Leave this to us" - Sirius flashed a feral smile - "We'll handle this."

I snorted. "Like there's an age limit on murder. Really, you're a Black. I thought you'd know better than that. Now, move aside, I've just discovered this absolutely delightful cutting curse and I'd like to put it to good use."

Lupin said, "This is wrong. We should turn him in."

"Fine," Black reluctantly agreed. "I guess I'd rather not do this in front of Harry, anyway. We'll take the rat to Dumbledore, and he will be Kissed."

They nodded and shook hands.

I stifled a whine. This was what I hated about Gryffindors. They always turned a perfectly good murder into some sort of moral lesson. At this rate, I'd never make that new Horcrux.

"Scabbers, er, Pettigrew's gone." the Weasley said. Apparently, while Lupin and Black had been making friends and sharing epiphanies, my ex-informant had scurried off into the night.

"This never would have happened if you'd let me murder him."

Third Year: Happy Memories

"Harry? How did you summon that Patronus?" Hermione was referring to the silvery snake I'd unleashed upon a crowd of dementors to save her, Black, and me. Mostly me.

Many people believe that someone as evil as Lord Voldemort could never use such powerful light magic. However, a Patronus is generated from a happy memory, not a nice one. My happiest memories just happen to involve a lot of blood.

"I defeated Lord Voldemort. I can do anything."

She rolled her eyes. "Right, sure, now tell me how you really did it."

Sometimes I hate having clever minions.

I shrugged. "The school was besieged by dementors. I wanted to protect myself."

"And you didn't tell me?" she whined, eyes big and tearful. It was scary how good she was getting at manipulating people. I suspect I may be a bad influence.

Oh well.

"What about that time turner of yours? You didn't tell me that you had control over the very fabric of reality. We could have done such glorious things…" I said.

"That's exactly why I didn't tell you," she said with a smirk.

Oh, she was evil…

Fifth Year: Career Success

(In the first draft of the Department of Mysteries break-in, Ron was dragged off after being mistaken for Percy, leading to…)

Hermione glanced around the Ministry, as if expecting an alarm to go off at any moment. "We're getting Ron now, right?"

I smirked. "I don't know why we would. He's got a cushy Ministry job now. He's doing better than either of us."

"Y…You're joking right?"

"I should think that would be obvious."

She shrugged. "Well, if it was anyone else, it would be. But, when we first became friends, I thought you had a really dark sense of humor. Then I got to know you and wasn't sure you knew what jokes were. So this is a nice surprise."

Fifth Year: It's Ruined Forever!

"I feel pretty good about how that went," I said, "even if I did just ruin the House Cup forever."

Hermione wrinkled her brow. "What do you mean?"

"Now, everyone knows that anyone can give or take points."

Hermione said, "Harry, no one knows that. Is that true, or are you doing that weird argument thing again?"

"No, I legitimately had no authority to do that. I don't think the Inquisitorial Squad did, either."

"Oh," she said weakly. "So it's completely run on the honor system, then?"

I shrugged. "Presumably. You shouldn't tell anyone, though, or it will ruin the House Cup forever."

"I'll keep that in mind," Hermione said, clearly scheming about how to use this information to her advantage.

Anytime: Perfectly Natural

I said, "Who do you trust more: Me or Ron?"

"Ron," Hermione said.

I nodded. "Exac…Wait, Ron? You came to that conclusion surprisingly quickly considering he is an idiot."

"Ron is not an idiot," she said. "He's simply immature, which is perfectly natural for someone his age."

"Mione, we're the same age," Ron said.

"Quiet, Ron."

I smirked. "As a Department of Mysteries employee, she's probably in her mid to late thirties –"

"Quiet, Harry."

Fifth Year: Grey!Indy!Harry or Luna Reads Fanfiction

Luna flagged me down, asking, "Harry, when you were younger, did you realize that everyone was secretly manipulating you, and that the only way you could survive to adulthood was if you forged your own, independent path? And could you only do that by becoming dangerous through illegal potions and time turner abuse?"

"No. I would have liked to do that, but Hermione is selfish," I explained. It really was a pity. We could have been great…well, greater.

Luna nodded with sympathetic understanding. "I see."

"How'd you come up with that one?" I asked.

"You publically denounce Dumbledore a lot, and you keep mentioning how you're neutral against Voldemort…which I think makes you a Grey Wizard."

I frowned. "I'm not familiar with the term."

"Now and again, one of them emerges to destroy both the Dark and Light Lords, restoring balance to the world. But, mostly, they don't do very much. We had an article about them in last month's Quibbler."

(P.S. Luna couldn't appear in the Epilogue because she had to move on to her next fanfic, where she joins a harem and acts incredibly out of character. It's a little embarrassing, but, hey, it's a living.)

Author's Musings:

Ship-Sinking

Seventh Horcrux stuck to canon pairings primarily because this is not a shipping fanfic, so a strong romance would have seemed fairly derailing.

However, there are other reasons that certain ships didn't occur.

Hermione is a tertiary main character, behind only Harry and Voldemort in terms of narrative weight. This leads to extra character development and the screen time necessary to bond with a character - always good in a love interest.

However, Harry and Hermione take turns being each other's mentor/parental figure. They're constantly in teacher mode, explaining why this is so or why that is irrevocably evil (and why would you do that?!). While their friendship is bloody heartwarming, in my humble opinion, Harry sees Hermione as his young, evil apprentice and Hermione sees Harry as worryingly immature. As she puts it, "Harry doesn't even understand what being a girl means."

Hermione deserves a mature, adult relationship, and Harry could never, ever give her one of those.

There was also noticeable support on Spacebattles for the Harry/Luna ship (…Larrymort? Insanity Shipping?). I understand where this comes from: Harry shows legitimate concern about Luna's feelings and Luna is both curious about Harry and comes closest to recognizing his particular mess of issues.

However, it is worth noting that both characters are insane. Due to Harry's propensity for accepting the views of whoever he is speaking to at any given moment, he would soon adopt many of Luna's beliefs. Eventually, they would begin to orbit around each other's madness, spiraling deeper and deeper into outer space while the baffled citizens of Earth could only watch in confusion.

…Besides, can you imagine either of them having the interest or attention span required to start dating?

Sixth Year: Summer Vacation in Antarctica

It was a perfectly reasonable plan:

I'd been going in circles for weeks, and none of those circles were taking me anywhere near England. So I decided to go in one direction, south, until I hit the southernmost part of the world. From there, the only place I could go would be north.

Mind you, that just landed me in Canada. But at least that was the correct hemisphere.

Sixth Year: Negotiations

I surveyed the dementor floating in front of me. "Two victims for every minion you return with a soul."

It stared at me.

"You drive a hard bargain," I acknowledged. "Three."

Lucius frowned. "My lord, I don't think it speaks English."

I snorted. "I won't debase myself by using French. You deal with it."

I stalked off, leaving a rapidly-paling Lucius with the advancing dementor.

Author's Musings:

Ship-Launching

Harry believes himself to be a seventy-year-old man. So pursuing teenage girls is creepy.

Harry is Voldemort, a mass-murdering snake-dude and villain of the series. So pursuing teenage girls is creepy.

Harry is mildly insane, narcissistic, self-centered, expects to be pursued and wooed (not the pursuer and wooer) because he is clearly the desirable one, and is vaguely suspicious of all love-shaped feelings. So pursuing teenage girls is…incredibly out of character.

Suffice it to say, I realized fairly early on that the only way Harry would end up in a relationship was if he had zero involvement in the process.

Under the circumstances? It was either immortal bachelorhood or a…relationship is certainly the wrong word…with the ever-energetic and obsessively devoted Ginevra Weasley.

It's cute, in a creepy sort of way, and isn't that what Seventh Horcrux is all about?

I would also like to take a moment to contemplate our beta couple: Hermione and Ron.

While I didn't mind this ship in canon, the whole "opposites attract" thing always gives me a bad feeling. In this fic, however, they have a bit more in common. First and foremost, they've spent the past seven years bonding over their bizarre friend and how to keep him from dying in a trunk.

Additionally, they grew as characters. Hermione learned to loosen up, that authority figures are shockingly bad at everything in Magical Britain, and that genocide is not okay.

Ron, meanwhile, benefitted very much from Harrymort's existence. In canon, Ron's jealousy sprung from his belief that Harry had everything Ron wanted (money and fame) even though Harry was just an ordinary bloke, and then the guy had the gall to be ungrateful for it.

Harrymort, in contrast, is a genius who knows all these crazy spells and he clearly adores both attention and his (long-lost, Dumbledore-stolen) riches. Ron's jealousy is further lightened by the fact that Harry includes him in adventures that he really shouldn't be involved with. After all, Ron had his dozen chances with the Goblet of Fire, too.

There is no way that Ron can compete with Harry and Hermione, but, because they're his best friends, Ron at least attempts to keep up with them (though he gets no respect for this, on Harry's end). Even unintentional cruelty on Harry's part, such as the stunner thing and declaring Ron a Weasley werewolf, caused the redhead to improve himself and find new interests. He even becomes a Werewolf Rights Activist, a sure plus in Hermione's books.

Also, Hermione did get Ron eaten by a werewolf that one time, so she kind of owes him.

Sixth Year: Inside Luna's Head

Ginny just apologized for Harry. They're dating; she's been saying so for years. Only when he's out of the room, though, because he fears commitment. Clearly, boyfriends and girlfriends can apologize for each other's rudeness.

Hermione is being rude to me, so either she has to apologize or Ron does. After all, everyone knows they're together. Ginny's been saying so for years

Seventh Year: Poor Planning

Hermione gingerly stepped into the waterlogged house, the floorboards groaning underneath her. Shattered and water-stained pictures of a fat, blond boy littered the floor and glass had been banished to the corners. Several members of the Order of the Phoenix milled about the abandoned home, whispering in anxious clusters. A pink-haired woman walked towards Hermione, apparently tripping on thin air shortly before reaching her.

"Wotcher, Hermione."

Hermione smiled. "Good morning, Tonks. Do you know why we're here instead of the Burrow?"

The older girl shrugged. "Some sort of rescue mission."

Moody stomped over to Hermione, his peg leg sending worrisome shudders through the house. He glared at the space next to her. "Potter, why is your house destroyed?"

I said, "I haven't lived here in years."

"Your family moved?" he asked.

I shrugged. "They left after a flashflood. I've been living in a trunk."

Tonks gaped. "That Skeeter article was true?!"

The Weasley twins grinned, slinging their arms around my shoulders. "Harry, we came to rescue you –"

"–but it turns out that you weren't here to be rescued –" the second twin said.

"So why are you here now?" the first finished.

"Hermione mentioned an Order meeting. I was bored," I said.

Fleur Delacour flounced over. "Eet is fine. We came to rescue ze little boy, and he eez here. So we shall do zat."

Moody snorted. "Right. I've got the polyjuice here. We all turn into Potter and –"

"Wait, why would we all turn into someone they want to kill?" I asked. "That seems like a terrible idea."

"You've got a better suggestion, do ya?" Moody growled.

I said, "I leave under the cloak, and the rest of you wander off looking vaguely confused."

I smiled at their dumbfounded faces. They took direction easily, a clear sign that Dumbledore had trained his minions well.

Anytime: Various Reasons, Really

The problem with Wizarding Britain is that the people are afraid of change. That's why I, a man supporting many sensible yet liberal policies, faced so much resistance from the public:

Fear of change.

Also the murder…

A Fun Fact

Up until the final scene of Fourth Year, I hadn't decided if Voldemort would be identical to canon, meaning that Harry was a shoddy copy job, or if they would be exactly the same person. I'm immensely pleased with my decision.

Clap Your Hands if You Believe!

Voldemort, from a very young age, had an affinity to magic. This was because he never even considered the possibility that reality would refuse to bend to his will. That it cheerfully went on to obey his every command was…unfortunate for his development.

In contrast, Neville assumed that the world would actively sabotage everything he did. It was happy to oblige.

Childhood Habits

Picture this: A young boy enters the wizarding world. He is cunning, ambitious, and unreasonably fond of snakes. One day, that boy will grow up to be a snake. He is, you see, a shoo-in for Slytherin.

He also appears to be a mudblood.

He is never going to fit in, so he has to be better, smarter. Scarier.

He certainly can't be asking questions. That makes him look like an idiot and showcase his shameful, Muggle past. So the boy figures things out on his own.

But he can't get things right all the time. Despite his arrogance, he knows this. When someone says something that seems untrue, he assumes they know what they're talking about and rolls with it, going to insane lengths to prove that he knew it all along.

…this is how Harrymort ends up engaged to Ginevra Weasley.

Seventh Year: Confrontations

Mr. Granger exclaimed, "Erasing people's memories?! Is that the sort of thing you've been learning in that school of yours?"

"Um, no," Hermione murmured. "Hogwarts doesn't teach that, and I'm not even going there anymore. I left last summer."

The Grangers shared a concerned look. Mrs. Granger took a deep breath. "Sweetie, you know that we love you even though you dropped out of school, right? You didn't need to make us forget that we ever had a daughter. We're still proud of you."

Mr. Granger cleared his throat.

His wife said, "Maybe a little less proud, after this memory-erasing thing."

I could see Hermione's hand trembling, longing to grab her wand and obliviate them again. She would then repeat this conversation, again and again, until she found a scenario in which her parents accepted being murdered. This would presumably occur due to Oblivation-induced brain damage.

To resist her horrible impulse, Hermione jumped into my trunk and locked herself inside.

Romcom Trailer

*Funky music plays*

*The camera sweeps over the Great Hall*

She was a girl still longing for the boy who possessed her body

*Ginny Weasley walks through the halls, chatting with friends and casting longing looks in Harry's direction*

Literally

*Young Ginny stands in the Chamber of Secrets*

*The camera zooms in on the diary in her hands*

He was an Imperioed boy dodging love potions

*Harry pushes away his plate*

"Ginevra, did you put love potion in my eggs?"

And love

*Pan over the Gryffindor common room where Harry is gesticulating wildly*

"Eventually, you become nauseous the second you feel the effects of a love potion."

*Hermione frowns*

"So…anytime you feel love, then?"

Could one great journey

*Ginny dodges spells, throwing her own back at the enemy*

*Harry is invisible*

Bring them together?

"I would do anything for you."

*Ginny leans in to kiss Harry*

*Harry is invisible*

This Christmas

Will they be able to overcome their many…

"I command the Basilisk."

*A giant snake looms over Ginny*

…many, many…

*Hermione groans*

*Harry is invisible*

"Harry, please take off the cloak."

…MANY issues?

"Look, Ginny, we have enough Weasleys. I don't need the two of you stalemating."

*A single tear falls down Ginny's cheek*

"But I'm different from my brothers!"

A Very Harry Romance

Directed by: Rita Skeeter

*Ginevra is enjoying a picnic on the war torn Hogwarts grounds*

*Harry is invisible*

Author's Musings:

More Than Just Parseltongue…

In Third Year, Harry accuses Ginevra of being a Legilimens after she comments on his loud conversation about time travel. A few chapters later, I realized that I wrote her as one: She knows everyone's secrets and blithely responds to Harry's internal monologue.

Could Diary have left more behind than a few words of Parseltongue and a twisted worldview?

Dumbledore's Office, after the final battle:

"…so we were hoping that you could explain your master plan," I finished.

Dumbledore's portrait peered down at our expectant faces and exclaimed, "I'm even more baffled than you are!"

(It's all after the epilogue from here on out)

If I were to make a sequel to Seventh Horcrux, I would call it:

The Adventures of Rose Weasley

The Last Slytherin

The First Slytherin

The Only Slytherin

…I'm so Lonely

Yet Another Trailer

She was chosen

*The Sorting Hat's eyes widen*

"You are like me. You are…a SLYTHERIN!"

She faced her greatest fears

*Rose stares desperately into Harry Potter's eyes, a teacup clenched in her hands*

"Uncle Harry, what if I'm the only Slytherin because I'm the only student who's evil?"

She faced adversity

"Look, kid, we're the real Slytherins around here."

*An older Hufflepuff shoves Rose*

She faced isolation

*Rose Weasley stands up from her seat at the empty Slytherin table*

"SCREW THIS! I'm sitting with the Hufflepuffs."

But can Rose face…

*In the depths of the Lake, a merman's eye snaps open*

…Her greatest challenge yet?

*Harry Potter paces his classroom*

"A merman drags you underwater…"

"Why?" a student asks.

"They want…"

*The camera pans over the Lake as creatures begin to surface*

"VENGEANCE."

*Music grows dramatic*

This summer

*Rose clutches her wand, eyes wide*

"Uncle Harry, why are we doing this?"

*Harry laughs*

"Because Neville is still in Albania!"

Join the adventure

*Rose gasps, taking a tentative step towards something we cannot see*

"Aunt Luna?"

The Adventures of Rose Weasley:

In Atlantis

*Hedwig's Theme Plays*

*The camera comes to rest atop the placid lake, Hogwarts towering above it*

*FADE TO BLACK*

An Unfortunately Typical History Class

"Um, Aunt Gi…I mean Professor Weasley?" Rose said softly.

The woman turned from staring dreamily at her left hand to staring dreamily at the wall behind Rose's head. Rose spent a moment convincing herself that that was a good thing. Aunt Ginny said, "Yes, Rose?"

There were a few titters from the Ravenclaws, and Rose felt a flash of indignation. Aunt Ginny had promised not to treat her differently from the other kids, yet here she was calling her by her first name. Rose stifled her frustration, however, because something was clearly very wrong. "Um, aren't you going to teach us history?"

Her smile widened to an unsettling size. "Who needs history? Last night was history. We should have a party!"

Rose looked around, but it seemed that the other students had left her alone to deal with her crazy aunt. "What happened?"

Aunt Ginny's elbows rested on the table, and she cupped her face in her hands. "Harry finally noticed me!"

"But you've been together forever," Rose said.

"I know! Nobody ever told him, though."

Rose's eye twitched. "You didn't –"

Aunt Ginny hopped from her seat and squealed, "We're engaged now!"

To the Dungeons with Ye!

I smoothed down the fabric of our couch, avoiding my mother's eyes. "Um, it's just…Sometimes, I feel like, on my first day, I was singled out and banished to the dungeons."

"And why do you feel that way?" Mum prodded.

I thought about it for a minute. "…Probably because I was sorted into an empty house and then banished to a lonely life in the dungeons. I mean, it's cool to have the space and everything, but it's kinda cold. Also, the common room gets all foggy, so I'm not really sure if it's safe to stay in there. But it's not like I can ask anyone because no one lives in the dungeons."

"The Puffs used to," Dad called from the kitchen.

I strained my neck to see him over the back of the couch. "Really? Why did they move, then?"

A voice echoed from the floo. "Because the castle wished to torment them, as is only natural."

I leapt from my seat, racing to the floo. "Uncle Harry!"

Hiring is Hard

"Rose," Uncle Harry said, "You have to remember that your professors may wish to kill you."

"W-what?" I squeaked. "Why?"

"You see, many of our current staff were hired when Voldemort conquered the school. No one was ever replaced, however, because it's very difficult to find good teaching staff."

I was pretty sure this was one of those times when I wasn't supposed to listen to my uncle. Mum always said that Uncle Harry lies a lot, but we shouldn't judge him for it because he doesn't usually know that he's lying.

Still, I didn't want to die, and Harry did know a lot about Dark wizards. "Really?"

Uncle Harry nodded. "Of course. Even I was hired by a Death Eater."

The Sorting Hat's New Song!

For those who are quite brave, or just wish to look cool,

The red and gold of Gryffindor is your place in this school.

And Ravenclaw tower, home of the birds,

Makes room for the mad and for the nerds.

For those who have no talent or simply feel divided,

If no one else will take you, then it's Hufflepuff decided.

Finally, there's Slytherin, who wanted Purebloods who were cunning and ambitious, but apparently eleven-year-olds don't usually have those qualities. So, mostly, he just got Purebloods, no matter how terrible. Fortunately, we have standards now.

…Wow!

The New Heiress of Slytherin

The newly-crowned Aunt Hermione Granger-Weasley, Dark Lady and Minister of Magic for the British Isles, smiled at my progeny. "She's adorable, Harry. What's her name?"

"Well, we decided that she needed a grand and terrifying title, much like Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore. So I named her after all of my greatest enemies."

Ron Weasley, conman and former werewolf, gaped at my brilliance. "You WHAT?"

Hermione pinched the bridge of her nose. "What did you end up with?"

"Her name is Severus Albus Lily Luna Lord Voldemort Potter."

Ginevra smiled. "We call her Sally for short."

"That's as many syllables as she can remember," I said fondly.

Ginevra giggled, kissing me on the cheek and not minding in the least as I flinched away.

Hermione frowned and said, "How are your mother and Luna considered enemies?"

I shrugged. "They don't precisely fit the theme, but Ginevra insisted."

Although, Lily did slay me when I was a dark lord, and I'm pretty sure Luna tried to kill me once or twice.

Ron grinned. "We're real happy for you, mate."

"And we're always willing to watch her for a while," Hermione said, "since you're keeping an eye on Rose."

I nodded, pulling on my invisibility cloak. "Right, that reminds me. I should probably get back to Hogwarts and check on Rose's lair."

Hermione appeared concerned. "Her what?"

But it was too late. I was already gone.

Author's Musings:

A Paradigm Shift

Seventh Horcrux is the story of Harry and his similarly insane friends in the somewhat silly world of Hogwarts. They proceed to take over that world, becoming professors, explorers, and the reigning Dark Lady of…ehem, excuse me, Minister of Magic.

The majority of these characters are not responsible adults, yet they all end up incredibly influential.

Rose Weasley would be the story of a fairly sane girl in Harry's mad world.

Professor Black is so Unfair!

I don't think Professor Black likes me very much, which is weird because I've never talked to him. He only teaches Third Years and above, after all. I think it's because my parents were war heroes who killed the Dark Lord Voldemort, so being mean to me is a form of petty vengeance.

Scorpius thinks it's because I call him a Death Eater in public a lot.

I'm not sure why that would be a problem, though. Uncle Harry says that Professor Black is really proud to be a Death Eater, since he was Voldemort's right hand man.

Author's Musings:

Dealing with Draco

There's this really cool OC that pops up in a lot of HP fics. He's suave, snarky, handsome, a bit of a git, but super good-looking. For some reason, people keep calling him Draco Malfoy.

In canon, Draco is none of those things. He's whiny, spoiled, lacks willpower, rushes into dumb plans with a brashness that completely defies Slytherin claims of cunning, and fails at literally everything he tries. Sure, there's some hints of an angsty redemption arc, but he never does all that much. At the end, we get a vague impression that he's okay now for an ill-defined reason…a lot like Snape, actually.

The way I see it, there are three ways to deal with Draco in fanfics:

1) Just swap him out for cool-guy OC up there.

2) Make him a total git. This is probably closer to canon than the previous option, but it strays into bashing way too easily.

3) My preferred method: Try to keep Draco as close to canon as possible, then give him some vague redemption primarily in the background. Do not take this redemption, or Draco in general, seriously.

Scorpius Malfoy: Bringing Shame upon the Malfoy Name

"You've got to" – I tripped over a flagstone – "slow" – my shoulder smacked a wall – "down!"

Scorpius Malfoy abruptly did so, dropping the arm he'd been dragging me by as he pushed me into an abandoned classroom (a weirdly common thing at Hogwarts). He turned to the door, casting several charms to protect against nosy passersby.

"What's up with you today?" I huffed.

He hurried towards me. Wide, grey eyes stared into mine from way-too-close a distance. Finally, he whispered, "You can't tell my father about this."

"O…kay," I said.

He peered around the classroom, as if afraid of invisible eavesdroppers. This was ridiculous, of course. Uncle Harry had a class that period. "I think I'm a Hufflepuff."

I stared at him. "You're just noticing this now? It's been two months, Scorp, and I've seen your dorms. They're, like, bright yellow."

Scorpius groaned, leaning back and out of my personal space. "Not like that. I mean…I don't think that I'm one of the Slytherin Hufflepuffs. I might just be one of the Hufflepuff Hufflepuffs."

I gasped. "No."

"I mean, I'm not really ambitious or anything. Father's always talking about how I should aspire to be some great politician, but I'm cool with just coasting by on my money and good looks."

I raised an eyebrow. "What good looks?"

"I'm a Malfoy!" Scorpius tilted his head up arrogantly, but all it did was emphasize his pointy chin and too-long neck.

"…anyway, I don't think being lazy is a very Hufflepuff trait, either," I pointed out.

Scorpius's head fell so quickly that I almost expected a snap or crack to accompany the motion. "Uh, maybe I'm one of the leftovers?"

Wincing, I put a hand on his shoulder. "Scorp, don't say stuff like that."

Tea and Emotional Crises

"What if I'm the only Slytherin because I'm the only student that's evil?" I asked, wide eyes staring up at my uncle.

He chuckled. "Rose, if being evil were the only thing necessary to get into Slytherin, it would be the largest house."

I bit my lip, a frown furrowing my brow. "Huh. That makes me feel better about myself but worse about everything else."

Uncle Harry ruffled my hair. "Good, that means you're growing up."

That made me feel even worse.

A/N: It's been fun, guys.

For any Naruto fans out there: You might want to give me a follow. The future holds silly things for you...